[engine revs]
[tires screech]
That's a bit more like it. This is fun.
[sighs] All right. That's fun over.
Was that any good or not?
-I'm dizzy!
-Oh no!
I think we should do
a donut challenge here.
[laughter]
[woman] Please, guys,
just so that we can put the one here.
-Hey, what's up, man? Good?
-You good?
But I think also that we have...
Ah, here. Lewis.
[man 1] I think, uh, the best
is to begin with choosing the keys.
-Yeah.
-[man 2] But we mic you up first...
Let's get on with it.
-[man 2] We mic you up first.
-Way too much doo-dallying.
-[woman] So, uh, yeah...
-Let's go.
[Hamilton] I've been with Mercedes
since I was 13,
so perspectives just shift.
This year, my contract is up for renewal.
I left my house at five fricking 45
this morning.
Did you? Oh, my alarm
was at quarter past eight.
-[Hamilton] Quarter past eight?
-[laughs] Yeah.
What's this with timings?
He left at quarter past eight.
-That's why you get the big bucks.
-He's younger. He doesn't need to sleep.
-They can have it back. I want my sleep.
-Give it to me. I'll take it. [laughs]
Follow me if you like.
My mindset's really like,
"Okay, we've had two difficult years."
So my goal is to get back on the top.
I'm trying to win
a world championship again.
But...
then we get in the car in 2023
and it's the evil sister. [laughs]
Yeah.
[tense music plays]
[Hamilton] All right,
let's quickly do this part.
-[Russell] You getting fed up?
-[Hamilton] Yep.
[woman] Everyone ready?
[man 1] So I think the only thing missing
is the drift challenge, so...
Shall we just direct it ourselves?
[chuckling]
[Patrick] With everything
that Lewis has accomplished,
the one thing
that's stopping Lewis from being done
is winning the eighth championship.
To be the best
that Formula 1 has ever seen,
with the most amount of championships
of any driver ever.
They're such eavesdroppers, Netflix.
[woman laughs]
You can be on the toilet,
you look over your head,
and there's a fucking boomstick.
You're like, "How did you get there?"
I've been on the toilet with a mic on,
and it was only after I flushed, I was...
-[Hamilton] A number two?
-[Russell] Yeah.
-[Hamilton laughs]
-[woman] Wanna tell us...
Really? [laughs]
-And he was there with the headphones.
-[laughs]
[Patrick] But to really turn a car around,
sometimes it can take years.
And of course, the... the clock...
Like he's, you know... He's getting older.
How many more seasons is he gonna have?
Camera's in position.
George, you start.
Lewis, you have to wait
until George comes back, okay?
I can't really remember winning
if I'm really honest.
Uh, it's been, like, a minute,
so I don't remember what that feeling is.
[man 1] Now, Lewis, stop. Just George.
[Hamilton] But it is what it is.
You just have to take it on the chin
and just acknowledge
that we did not get it right,
we took the wrong decisions,
and start really making big strides
in the right direction.
[woman] Lewis, wait!
[Hamilton] Before it's too late.
[engine roars]
[woman] Lewis!
[man 1] Lewis, please come back.
Lewis, can you get back in position?
[wheel gun whirring]
[engine revs]
[tense music plays]
[commentator 1] Once again,
Max Verstappen leading a grand prix.
But behind him in second,
the oldest driver on the grid,
Fernando Alonso,
enjoying another brilliant race.
[Cronin] Okay, Fernando.
Very good job. Head down now.
[Alonso] Copy.
[commentator 1] Lewis Hamilton is back
in fourth, chasing Esteban Ocon in third.
[Bono] Ocon, gap 1.7.
Close that gap.
[commentator 2] This is Lewis Hamilton's
chance to get past Esteban Ocon
and onto the podium.
[Hamilton] Can't get closer, mate.
[tense music plays]
[Hamilton] It's impossible
to get close and pass.
This car is slow, mate.
[Hamilton] When the car is terrible,
I feel helpless.
I can try and deliver each weekend,
but you can only do so much
with what you got.
[commentator 3] On the streets of Monaco,
Max Verstappen wins the Monaco Grand Prix!
It's second place
for Fernando Alonso and Aston Martin.
[Alonso] Woo! That's a podium, baby.
P2!
[Alonso] Well done, guys. Bravo!
That was a tough race.
What was the finishing order?
[Bono] Uh, so Verstappen,
Alonso, and Ocon podium.
And then yourself, P4.
George P5.
[Hamilton] Shit.
The Monaco result will be, uh,
a massive disappointment to Mercedes.
But it's really indicative
of where they're at
because P4 and P5
is actually their new reality.
[crowd cheering]
[Hamilton] Fernando,
he's really made a great decision.
On one side, this is really inspiring.
Um...
Yeah, and then on the flip side,
it's obviously... frustrating for sure.
[Williams] Lewis
will be watching Fernando
and thinking, "Why is that not me?"
The Mercedes is not the best car,
so Lewis has a decision on his hands.
Does he stay?
Or does he leave Mercedes
and make that leap?
[cheering]
[Williams] Fernando Alonso
has pivoted a lot in his career.
He's always looked to travel to the team
who he thinks is going to give him
the fastest race car.
[commentator 2] Fernando Alonso
is on the podium for Aston Martin!
I felt that it was necessary for my career
to gamble a little bit more.
[commentator 2] Yet again,
Fernando Alonso on the podium.
[Alonso] And to take some risk.
[commentator 1] Fernando Alonso
will take another podium.
[Alonso] I think this year,
with the results that we're having
and, uh, being competitive,
reaching podiums...
[announcer] Alonso of Spain!
...proves it was a good decision
to join Aston Martin.
[Russell] I don't know
if times are different now
compared to, let's say,
when you had the glory years,
but the braking is still a real limitation
with the car sort of bouncing at the rear.
[Wolff] George, I think
from our perspective...
Sorry. We have a bit of a delay.
From our perspective now,
obviously we are not in the car
and don't know how it feels,
but we can see that it's getting
two or three tenths less good
against the competition.
Nobody on the team is impressed
with the results so far.
We have a car that's not
where we would like it to be,
and then obviously,
Lewis is not impressed.
The weakest part of our car
is the rear end.
That wing is...
It's really a barn door.
It's very, very draggy.
Um...
Last year was the same.
The year before that was the same.
Last year, I remember complaining
to the team
and being like,
"Look, we have to make these changes."
"Like, otherwise, this is
the trajectory we're gonna go on,
and this is where we're gonna end up,
and it's... it's..."
"Please do something about it."
And I remember that they said, like, um,
"We know what we're doing."
Um, "You're wrong."
And that was definitely
an interesting moment.
I mean, I just... I was like, "Okay."
I'll step back.
Don't wanna step on anybody's toes and...
And then, uh, yeah...
[chuckles] ...when we got into the season,
then we spoke again.
Like, "Oh, maybe you were right."
[chuckles]
So, um, yeah.
[Susie Wolff] Here we are, Jackie.
Are you excited to drive, Jack?
-You wanna go for it?
-Yeah.
I'm gonna crash you off the track.
You're gonna crash me off the track?
That's not very nice.
-[Wolff] You can't do that.
-No.
[Wolff] Anyway, we don't want
to be a racing driver.
That's only third option.
Uh, yeah, third option.
We want to save animals,
or be a Scottish rugby player.
Maybe I'm gonna do all three.
[Susie laughs] Okay.
The most important is you enjoy it,
and you have fun.
-[man 1] Ciao Jack!
-[Jack] Ciao.
-[Susie] Good morning.
-[man 1] Morning.
[woman] Good morning.
-[man 1] Toto, good morning.
-[Wolff] Good morning. Ciao.
[woman] Morning.
[man 2] Jack, your car is ready.
-[Jack] I'm gonna win. I'm gonna win.
-[Susie] You're gonna win?
[Susie chuckles] Look how small he looks.
[Wolff] I think he's gonna complain
it's too slow.
[Susie chuckles]
[Susie] I think Toto has
a certain amount of patience.
But when he sees
there's not being any progress made,
that's where you can definitely see him
switch into a different mode.
-[Wolff in Italian] This is full.
-[man 1] Let's change the engine?
[Wolff] Yes, let's stop the car.
[in English] Put the bigger engine in.
[in Italian] Let's bring him in
to make changes.
[Susie in English] Racing's tough.
There's only ever one winner.
You gotta learn how to cope with losing.
[Wolff] You need to cope with pressure.
Look where we are this season.
You know, the expectations of everyone.
When is Mercedes gonna come back
after eight world championships?
[Jack] Why is my kart so slow?
But that's racing.
You can't win everything.
You can't win always.
It goes in cycles.
No, you can break cycles.
We're not in a cycle.
You've seen the Schumacher years,
then Vettel, then Mercedes,
and now it's two years in a row,
uh, Max, but...
you gotta break that.
The Mercedes team really started
to go from strength to strength in 2013.
It was the time when Lewis and I joined,
and we came from two different worlds.
My background was more finance,
and he's been, all his life, a superstar.
[announcer] Let the celebrations begin!
[Wolff] That year, we finished
second in the championship.
And from 2014 until 2021...
[Hamilton] Woo-hoo!
[Wolff] ...we won
eight Constructors Championships in a row.
[commentator 3]
World Championship record is equalled!
[Wolff] Seven Driver Championships.
[commentator 3] Lewis Hamilton
is a seven-time champion of the world!
[Wolff] Lewis beat the all-time record
of 100 race wins.
I can't believe that we're at 100.
I'm ecstatic, like it's my first.
[Wolff] These records
were very satisfying.
But Lewis is much more than my driver.
Lewis is a friend.
This is his family and his home.
And therefore, I wouldn't want
to have any other driver in the car.
[Susie] We have not discussed
if Lewis will re-sign.
It will either happen
because it's meant to happen,
or there will be a feeling
that the journey's come to an end.
[Wolff] Put your hand on my shoulder
like you have pity with me.
[both chuckle]
[Susie laughs]
[gentle music plays]
[man 1] Are you ready, Jack?
[Susie] Toto knows he's responsible,
so it's just having belief.
"Okay, we got it wrong, and we need
to get back on track and turn it around."
And he will.
[hopeful music plays]
Yeah, you see the acceleration.
[Wolff] For Lewis to win an eighth
championship and George to win his first,
we owe it to them to provide them
with a good car. That's the minimum.
[man 1] He's fast.
[Wolff] That's a big upgrade.
And if we're able to achieve that,
we will be
a championship-winning team again.
[Wolff laughs]
[phone rings]
[receptionist] Reception.
Yeah, I have given him the message.
I do apologize.
I think they're just really busy.
Okay, thank you. Bye. Bye.
A winning team
is a combination of several factors.
It is the right people, the right place,
the right mindset, the right values.
Our main problem
is just the lack of performance.
Obviously, there is drive
to make the car faster,
but we didn't change the concept,
so we have to live with what we have,
find out where it is we can optimize,
and try to make inroads.
So there is a bracket now
that is offset ten mil.
[Wolff] Our sport is a data-driven sport,
but data don't make decisions.
It's people that do.
[man] At the moment, that thing needs
a definite fuel-system swap.
[Wolff] With a single upgrade,
you can unlock the potential in a car
and suddenly fight for podiums.
[man] The little things
that find you half a tenth.
[Wolff] I don't expect this to be easy,
but I have ultimate faith in the team.
We just gotta give it everything
to get the season back on track.
[cheering]
[upbeat music plays]
[crowd cheers]
[Alonso] In Spain,
there is always this feeling
of it's once a year
that you have the home grand prix.
This year is the 20th anniversary
of my first win in Formula 1.
[fan] Fernando! Fernando! Fernando!
And 20 years later,
I'm still, uh, fighting for wins.
[upbeat music continues]
[Russell] Good morning.
[fan] George! George,
what do you think of beans on toast?
Beans on toast? I like it.
Pre-race prediction? Yeah, gonna win.
-[man] Pre-race prediction.
-Yeah, I'm gonna win. Yeah.
[reporter] And if it's not you?
Fernando.
I wanna see Fernando win a race.
Who doesn't?
[man] Thanks for joining.
Who would like to take the first question
for Lewis from the floor?
[reporter 1] I think Toto said
after the last race
that he doesn't expect to clear,
um, Aston Martin and Ferrari here,
so is that your feeling
and the general feeling of the team?
I... I really don't know what to expect.
I'm still hopeful that we can compete
with them this weekend,
but it's a big hope.
I just feel so incredibly hungry to win
and willing to sacrifice
pretty much everything, um,
in order to get...
to... to get to where I need to be.
[tense music plays]
[reporter 2] Silly season hasn't begun,
there's already a lot of noise
around Lewis Hamilton's future at Mercedes
and a possible move to Ferrari.
[reporter 2] Thinking about Lewis
in a red suit...
You know, he's obviously been
at the same team for so long.
I think change is always exciting.
[reporter 3] Lewis,
can we bring you in on this?
What about these Ferrari stories?
Yeah, I think naturally, uh,
when you're in the contract negotiations,
there's always gonna be speculation.
And I think ultimately, that's, uh...
Unless you hear from me,
then that's all it is, speculation.
-[reporter 3] Have Ferrari been in touch?
-No.
[Buxton] Rumors don't come
from nowhere in Formula 1.
Of course, there's gonna be question marks
over whether Lewis
will re-sign with Mercedes.
But if you're not talking to every team,
then you're not doing your job.
[intriguing music plays]
-Don't speak. We are on Netflix.
-No, no, I know.
[Vasseur chuckles]
[in French] I don't want to talk.
There's Netflix.
[laughs]
[producer in English] So, uh, I'm not
allowed to ask you about Mercedes, am I?
[laughs]
You will ask Toto about Mercedes.
[Wolff] I completely understand
that Lewis needs to look out
what is the best opportunity for himself.
But what we agreed very early on
was that we wouldn't talk to anybody else
without being transparent
and honest with each other.
[Russell] With Lewis, if he were to leave,
that would put Mercedes
in a bit of a tricky spot
because it would almost look like
he's lost faith in the team.
[Hamilton] Every time you do a contract,
I think you'd be an idiot
if you didn't analyze
where you currently are
and what other opportunities there are.
Then you have to make a decision
whether you explore other alternatives
or you just continue on
with what you're doing.
[team member 1]
So, Barcelona then, this weekend.
We've closed the gap to second
to one point.
The big questions are obviously gonna be
around the effectiveness of the upgrades.
So it'll be fascinating to see
where we go from here.
Um...
We're not expecting to see
a big shift in performance.
[team member 2] I think downplay.
[both team members]
Under-promising and over-delivering.
We're still determined.
We're not defeatist. But we're realistic.
Um, and then the track changes.
[dramatic music plays]
[commentator 2] Here we go once again.
Welcome to Spain.
It is time for the 53rd World Championship
running of the Spanish Grand Prix.
With Hamilton starting in fourth,
the question is,
will the new upgrade be enough
to take the fight to Aston Martin
in the battle for second place
in the Constructors?
-Radio check.
-[Bono] Radio loud and clear.
Thirty seconds. Fire up.
[Wolff] The team have worked flat out
to bring an upgrade.
[Hamilton] I hope the car's gonna be a lot
better. Whether it'll work, we'll see.
[Russell] We're there to fight, to win.
And we will need to raise our game.
[Wolff] We believe that the upgrade
is gonna function well.
But there is no guarantee.
[tense music plays]
[Hamilton] Been hit.
[commentator 3]
Hamilton and Norris make contact!
[Hamilton] Might have
some damage on the car.
[Bono] We'll check everything.
[Michell] So, Lance,
that's Hamilton in front of you.
[tense music continues]
[commentator 2] And the Aston Martin
is ahead of the Mercedes.
[Michell] Great work, Lance.
You know what to do. Settle down into it.
[tense music continues]
[Bono] Stroll, 0.7 ahead.
Data looks all good with that contact.
-What position are we?
-[Dudley] P7.
Gap ahead to Alonso, 0.9.
[commentator 3] Fernando Alonso's
fending off George Russell here.
[Cronin] Russell, 0.6 behind.
[Alonso] Understood.
[dramatic music plays]
[Cronin] Russell, 0.5.
[Dudley] Gap 0.4.
[Cronin] Russell, 0.2.
[dramatic music continues]
[music fades]
[commentator 2] George Russell
gets ahead of Fernando Alonso.
[Bono] Pace is looking really good, Lewis.
Stroll, 1.3 ahead.
[Hamilton] Tires still good.
[dramatic music plays]
[commentator 3] We saw Fernando Alonso
getting passed by Mercedes,
and we're seeing Lance Stroll
getting passed by Mercedes.
[Bono] Nice one, Lewis. Sainz, gap 1.1.
[dramatic music continues]
-[Hamilton] Tires are still really good.
-[Bono] Let's keep it that way.
So currently P2.
Nice work, Lewis.
[dramatic music continues]
[Dudley] This is good. If we can
keep this pace up, we can keep extending.
[commentator 1] The Mercedes
is absolutely flying.
[Dudley] Okay, let's go flat out.
Flat out.
[commentator 3] George Russell
has just got past Carlos Sainz
and moved himself up
into the podium places.
[Dudley] Solid work.
[Russell] Just solid?
[Wolff] It was pretty good.
[commentator 4] Both Mercedes
have absolutely come alive.
[Bono] Lewis, we're still P2
and two laps remaining.
We're slowly progressing.
[Wolff] Now we just need
to bring them to the end.
[Hamilton] We were so strong for so long.
But the last couple of years
has been tough on everyone.
[dramatic music plays]
[Hamilton] So it felt so good
to get a second place.
[commentator 2] Lewis Hamilton
comes round the final corner.
[Hamilton] I can't put into words
how much it means
to finish the race
with a smile on your face.
[Bono] Great work, Lewis.
What an awesome drive.
[commentator 3] This has been
a super performance for Lewis Hamilton
and for Mercedes today.
[Hamilton] Mega job, guys! Mega job.
Super grateful for all the hard work
everyone's put in to bring this upgrade.
[commentator 3] And George Russell
is gonna hold off Sergio Pérez
to get third in this race.
Woo!
This sport's a bit more fun
when the car's fast, hey?
[commentator 3] And that's a huge boost
for a team that's had to dig deep
and rebuild their season.
[uplifting music plays]
Everyone to the podium, please.
Everyone to the podium.
[applause]
[Cronin] P7. Lance P6.
[Alonso] Lacking a little bit of pace,
but Mercedes, a little bit too fast today.
[commentator 1] Disappointment
for Aston Martin,
and they'll drop behind Mercedes
in the Constructors Championship
as a result.
[Wolff] Getting better, no?
But you see the gap?
You see the gap to the front, no?
Yeah.
[Susie] I don't think there was ever a
feeling like, "Okay, we've got this now."
There was a feeling
that we're going in the right direction,
but there's still a long way to go.
[Wolff] Step by step, yeah.
Bravo. Ciao, ciao, ciao.
-Come on!
-[woman] Come on!
[man] Get down there, Danny.
[Wolff] Doesn't look
like shitters anymore.
So good.
No more complete wankers.
[announcer] Well done to George.
[cheering]
[Wolff] The sheer effect of a podium
and seeing the drivers up there
is great for the team.
[announcer] In second place,
Lewis Hamilton!
[Wolff] Now we need to be able to channel
that positiveness in the right direction.
[cheering]
[announcer] Well done to Max Verstappen.
Fanboys, first row.
[Wolff in German] Do you think
we should take a team photo?
[man] No. I don't think so.
-[Wolff] No.
-We...
[in English] We don't lower our standards.
No, I think we need to be...
I know we need to celebrate the moment.
Yeah, but you're absolutely right.
No team photo for second and third.
[Wolff] Barcelona was one race.
I don't wanna grab on to one single straw
and see all the positiveness in that.
[reporter] Do you see the light
at the end of the tunnel?
Um...
[Patrick] The person with the most amount
of pressure on them is going to be Toto.
He can't promise that, you know,
we're gonna win the championship again.
He can't promise we're gonna win races.
The best thing
that Toto can guarantee Lewis
is that he's gonna listen to him.
[Hamilton] Boss.
Got good pictures around.
Who would've thought we would be
where we are in the world today?
Last year, the development of the car,
you weren't happy with me.
[both chuckle]
Yeah.
You know, sticking to the concept
from last year,
holding on to it because of
the encouraging results at the end...
-That's the biggest failure.
-[Wolff] The biggest.
Um...
Because last year
lead us in the wrong, you know...
Yeah.
[Wolff] The time has come
to cut our losses
and say that the concept of this car
is never gonna work.
We gotta change it for next year.
For me, personally,
you know, when you see the step
that Aston Martin made over the winter,
shows that if we get it right
with the concept of the car,
you know, the aero and the balance,
we can win a championship.
But I don't want to wait until 2026
when we have the new engine regulations.
[Hamilton] Frick, me neither.
You can be here for, like, 20 more years,
30 more years.
I can't. [laughs]
Well, who says that?
This is precious years for me.
I don't know.
Lewis, you're much more
than a racing driver.
Much more
than the seven-time world champion.
You are one of the... the people
that lead this team forward.
[camera shutter clicks]
[melancholy music plays]
[Hamilton] I've worked with Toto now...
Uh, I think this is my tenth year
with the team.
[melancholy music continues]
[Hamilton] I've learned
a huge amount from him,
and I'd like to think
there's at least one or two things
that he may have learned from me.
[Wolff] In every relationship,
you will have moments
where your objectives may differ.
It's just part of how life goes.
In the context of our relationship,
he's a loyal guy.
[Hamilton] Toto and I
have a lot in common.
We're both massively competitive
and hate losing.
Okay, we've had two difficult years,
but... I still have so much belief
that Mercedes
and all these people within this team
have the ability to build a great car.
You've just got to take a leap of faith.
[cell phone chimes]
[reporter 1] Lewis Hamilton
has signed a new two-year contract.
[Wolff] The thought of Lewis at Ferrari
in a red overall,
it wouldn't suit him.
[reporter 2] The seven-time world champion
has signed a new two-year contract
with Mercedes until 2025.
[Hamilton] Toto, he's listened.
And there just never feels like a time
where I'm not gonna be a Mercedes driver.
That's my home. It's my family.
[woman] Bye-bye.
-[Hamilton] Let's go. See you next week.
-[man] See you next week. Take care.
[Wolff] If I would have a glass ball,
to say to you,
"I am delivering the eighth title,"
would be foolish.
Um, what I can guarantee is
that the team
is gonna be giving its utmost
to bring that eighth title to him
that he deserves.
But at the moment,
the most important thing
is to finish second
in the Constructors Championship.
Beat Aston Martin and Ferrari.
And... And that will be the aim now.
[Szafnauer] Our season so far
has been disappointing.
[commentator 3] There's contact!
[Ocon] I got hit, guys.
[commentator 3] Double DNF for Alpine.
[Gasly] For fuck's sake.
[Szafnauer] I have to do better.
The buck will stop with me.
[producer] Three, two, one, go.
[Ricciardo] I'm back.
It was good.
I got nothing to lose.
The dream for me is to...
to get back at Red Bull Racing.
[Padros] Be careful.
[commentator 4] The worst thing Ferrari
could do is start racing each other.
[commentator 3] And Leclerc locks up!
We need to get results
if we want to survive.
[closing theme music plays]
[music fades]