All right, Father Christmas, one minute
and then I'll get you to ring the bell.
-[Father Christmas] Yes.
-And then we'll get them in.
-Get them in, brilliant.
-[Horner] Very good. Excellent.
Guys, listen.
-[bell rings]
-[Monty] Oh my God!
[Horner] He's here! Quick, quick!
[bell rings]
-Wow, here he is!
-[Horner] Oh!
Hello there, Monty.
[Geri] Lovely.
Just go and say hello. Come on.
-Hi, Father Christmas.
-Lovely to see you.
-[Geri] How are you doing?
-I'm very good.
We're very excited to see you.
-I hope you don't mind me dropping in.
-[Geri] No, it's really fine.
Can I ask, has Dad been good this year?
[Olivia] Let me think about that.
Let me think.
What do you mean, "Let me think"?
-He won a championship.
-I think you've been amazing.
-He's superfast.
You know, apart from me, this man's
the fastest person in the universe.
I think Max Verstappen
might be quicker than you.
[Father Christmas] I travel three times
the speed of light. How fast does he go?
Probably four.
[upbeat music plays]
Right, these steps here, bit icy.
Okay?
We are alive.
[music fades]
[Horner] Who do you think
this horse would be if it was a driver?
-[Olivia] I have no idea.
-[Monty giggles]
-[Horner] Who's your favorite driver?
-All of them.
-[Horner] All of them?
-In Red Bull.
-Who's first place in your heart?
-[Horner] Daniel Ricciardo.
[laughs]
Daniel was a product of our junior team.
He drove for us for five years.
[Rennie] Daniel, you're doing
a really good job. Very impressive.
[Horner] Seven grand prix victories.
Un-fucking-believeable!
Over 20 podiums.
Daniel Ricciardo, you are our hero.
All achieved in Red Bull racing cars.
Then he left.
I felt disappointed
about him walking away from the team.
He went to Renault.
[commentator 1] And Daniel Ricciardo
losing his front wing going into turn one!
No!
[Horner] That didn't work at all for him.
And then moved to McLaren.
And that was disastrous.
[Stallard] Okay, Daniel, that's not
the race we wanted, to be honest.
[Ricciardo groans]
All sport is... is a confidence business.
You could just see
the confidence sapped out of him.
[reporter] Formula 1 star Daniel Ricciardo
has been axed by McLaren.
I don't believe the Daniel we've seen over
the last couple years is the real Daniel.
It's not the Daniel I can recognize
from his time at Red Bull.
-[Olivia] Daddy, go!
-Shh.
[Horner] As soon as McLaren let him go,
I picked up the phone to him,
and... and we just had a chat.
If the team in the background
aren't doing their bit,
the driver will never succeed.
[Geri] Yes, that's so true.
That's a lot of pressure, isn't it?
He just needs a good old hug,
and he'll be all right.
That's all.
[laughs]
I said, "Well, why don't you
come spend a year with us on the bench
and just find your love
for the sport again?"
[tense music plays]
Whether it'll help him
or lead to something, I'm not sure.
Ultimately, Daniel might have to accept
that his time in Formula 1 is done.
[wheel gun whirring]
[engine revs]
[upbeat music plays]
Where's the Statue of Liberty?
-Did we pass it?
-[man 1] Yeah.
[Horner] I missed it.
Okay.
Missed it.
[upbeat music continues]
[man 2] We are live here in New York.
Nobody pushes the limits
quite like Red Bull.
Now, we're gonna hang out
with a very special person.
And we're gonna welcome him back home
to the world of Red Bull Racing.
It's our boy,
and we're happy to have him back.
[interviewer] Nice kit by the way.
Thanks.
What do they say, "Look good, feel good"?
I feel good.
[upbeat music plays]
[Ricciardo] I'm back with the family
that it all began with,
so I'm really happy about that.
[Horner] Daniel Ricciardo
is our third driver.
He's gonna be working,
doing a lot of marketing stuff.
He's gonna be kissing a lot of babies,
shaking a lot of hands.
He's gonna be doing events.
He's gonna be, um,
you know, opening stores.
He's gonna be working
with all of our... all of our partners.
But not racing.
That'll be a lot of, uh,
let's say, my work and my contribution,
and I'll be working behind the scenes.
[Buxton] For as much
as it's a lovely story,
going from full-time race driver
to a third driver is a fall from grace.
It's a step down.
[man] Thank you all so much
for joining us today
for the Oracle Red Bull Racing
season launch.
[applause]
Daniel Ricciardo goes from being
a race winner at Red Bull
to many years later, now coming back
in essentially a marketing role,
which just must be
such a hard pill to swallow.
In my head, I'm just not done.
Um, I feel like
I've still got more to... more to give.
I just don't know
how I will get back to an F1 car,
but I know that that's something
I want again for sure.
What are you, 32?
[Pérez] Three.
Thirty-three. Oh, yeah, you're 1990.
You just turned 33? Yeah.
[Pérez] You are 33?
I'll be 34 this year.
[Horner] This year,
we're genuinely very lucky
to have some great, great talented drivers
at both of our race teams,
Red Bull Racing and AlphaTauri.
Good morning.
Ready to go.
Let's make up some time.
I think we're a little late. [chuckles]
All right, I'm Nyck de Vries.
I'll do it again.
I'm Nyck de Vries,
racing for Scuderia AlphaTauri.
And it's my first year in Formula 1.
How... How far are we away?
-[driver] Fifteen minutes.
-Fifteen minutes away.
[Horner] Nyck is
a Formula E world champion.
A Formula 2 champion.
He's got a huge amount of experience.
[commentator 2] Excellent stuff
from Nyck de Vries.
[Buxton] Nyck's been rapid
in everything he's ever driven.
He's the Formula 2 champion.
He's a Formula E champion.
Kid's incredible.
But he's had to wait for this opportunity.
28 years old,
Nyck's finally got his shot in Formula 1
with Red Bull's junior team, AlphaTauri.
And he has to make it work.
[jaunty orchestral music plays]
-[man] Next one. Are we ready?
-[man 2] Ready?
-[man 3] Yeah.
-[man 4] That's right on.
[gunshot]
[jaunty orchestral music continues]
Just pull up there.
Go to there and pull up at the side.
[Horner] At Red Bull,
our philosophy is all about winning.
And any driver needs to demonstrate
that he's got that firmly in his mind.
You were driving your one.
Yeah, exactly. We've done the whole tour.
-Haircut?
-[Horner] Yeah. Tom Cruise, huh?
[laughs]
That winning mentality, I don't just
expect from our Red Bull Racing drivers,
but also our junior drivers at AlphaTauri,
Yuki Tsunoda
and the new guy, Nyck de Vries.
[man on video] Get yourself ready.
Put the cartridge in the gun,
and think to yourself of the visualization
of the gun smoking a target.
The focus, hard focus, concentration,
and that rhythm and timing.
[gunshots]
AlphaTauri's there to train
and develop talent for Red Bull Racing.
Well done, guys.
I look at those drivers
as are they candidates
for Red Bull Racing at any point in time?
[de Vries] Thank you.
If they're not,
then what's the point of them being there?
[man] Drive over.
Guns down and unload, please.
Well done, guys.
I taught 'em all they knew.
All they knew or all they know?
-[man] All they know.
-All they know.
I don't really have
any experience with guns, in all honesty.
-I... I... I...
-It's just this.
I rather prefer harmony
than fights and aggression.
Nyck, he's got
a huge amount of experience.
One would expect him to...
to really take the lead at AlphaTauri.
[de Vries] That was mine.
[Horner] Also, he knows
eventually there could be
a chance for him at Red Bull.
[man] Um, could I please ask the drivers
to come down and join me?
[de Vries] Um, Christian, thank you
very much for hosting this great event
at your, uh, lovely house and estate.
I just want to wish you all a great event
and weekend, this, uh, this week,
and hopefully Red Bull
can continue its dominance,
and we can try and score some points.
[man] Thanks, Nyck. Very well said.
[de Vries] I had to wait to be on the grid
for a very long time.
But I believe
I'll reach the pinnacle of our sport.
[laughter]
[upbeat music plays]
-[Horner] How you doing? All right?
-[Ricciardo] Good.
-A good friend of mine, Paul.
-Hi, Paul. Enjoy.
-[Horner] See you later.
-See ya.
[Horner] Yeah.
So he... he's... he's our reserve.
So he's taken a lot of the weight
off the shoulders of, uh, Max and Checo.
[man] In terms of PR?
Yeah. Tough for him, 'cause, obviously,
he's used to being sat in a car.
But he's making the best of it.
[woman 1] You'll do the meet and greet
first and then go on stage.
[woman 2] Please put your hands together,
and give a huge round of applause
to Daniel Ricciardo.
[applause]
Very exciting to see you here.
It's great to see you back in blue.
[Ricciardo] Thanks.
Can you tell us
a little bit about your role?
Yep. Um, I'm preparing
all of Max and Checo's meals.
[laughter]
Um, what else? Yeah. [laughs]
-Fabulous. I know you're really busy, so...
-I'm not really.
It's gonna be strange for Daniel
to come back into the paddock
without a race seat.
He's there just to do interviews
and smile and be Daniel Ricciardo.
You know, put the mask on,
do the functions,
and keep the crowds happy.
[cheering]
I'm sure that stings.
[fan] Daniel! Daniel! Daniel! Daniel!
Going to races, there's certainly still,
like, that competitor in me.
That fire is still there, so it's tough.
I haven't forgot how to drive.
[interviewer] Where's the seat
gonna come from?
No idea. [laughs]
[man] So this will be the new experience.
Um, it's... You know,
so it's great to be here. [chuckles]
I'm Peter Bayer,
CEO of Scuderia AlphaTauri.
[Buxton] This year,
there will be changes at AlphaTauri.
Yeah.
[indistinct chatter]
[Buxton] There's going to be
a new CEO coming in,
who's looking to make changes
to secure the team's future.
Good morning, everyone. Questions for him.
Ian Parkes, New York Times.
Why have you decided to join this team?
I'm coming to a team
which has extremely solid foundations.
As a CEO of a Formula 1 team,
I'm responsible to deliver results.
The expectation is really to score points
and to fight for a top midfield position.
[man] Um, worst-case scenario,
we, uh, abort the scrub,
and we go straight into the soft.
Okay.
There's only one reason
you race at AlphaTauri.
You race for AlphaTauri
because you want to race for Red Bull.
Knowing that that is a step away,
it puts a lot of pressure on you to...
To number one, beat your teammate.
[de Vries] Yuki is a...
a very quick driver, but...
How should I phrase this?
Um...
I am a little bit more experienced,
more mature,
and more complete.
The achievements he did in the past
is, uh, is really big,
so he's a good driver.
But anyway,
it won't be easy, but I'll beat him.
[de Vries] Game time.
[tense music plays]
[dramatic music plays]
Radio check, radio check.
-[Hamelin] Radio is good.
-Okay.
[commentator 2] Nyck de Vries starts 18th.
His teammate, Yuki Tsunoda, starts 16th.
[Spini] Last car forming.
[De Vries] It feels
like living on a cloud.
It's just a privilege to be there.
I just need to seize that moment,
and then who knows what is possible?
[tense music plays]
[music builds]
[commentator 3] That's a slow start
from Nyck de Vries.
He's been beaten off the line
by Lando Norris.
What happened?
[commentator 1] Nyck de Vries
sadly down in 19th.
[tense music continues]
[Spini] Okay, Yuki, Bottas in front.
Overtake available.
[Tsunoda] Okay, let's go.
[Spini] Push now, flat out.
Good job.
[Michell] Lance, stop
in a safe position on track. We see smoke.
Stop in a safe position on track.
Stop the car.
[Hamelin] Stroll stopped
in turn 13. Let's make it count.
Copy.
[exciting music plays]
[Albon] Oh my God, brake failure.
Jesus Christ, man.
[Hamelin] Overtake available if you need.
[commentator 3] Nyck de Vries
taking advantage. He's now in 15th place.
-[Hamelin] We can push more.
-[de Vries] Yeah, copy that.
[dramatic music plays]
[Hamelin] Head down.
Overtake available.
Okay, good job, Nyck.
[commentator 1] Going into the hairpin,
de Vries manages to dive down the inside,
up to 14th.
[exciting music plays]
[Spini] P11.
[Tsunoda] Good one, good one.
[Hamelin] Okay, so that's P14.
[de Vries] Yeah, I was not, uh, efficient.
I struggled a little bit.
[Hamelin] We know what to work on
for the next race.
[de Vries] Copy.
The potential was... was there.
Um, but, uh,
we just didn't quite get it together.
It is the way it is,
and, uh, we'll move on.
[de Vries] When you live in a small space,
it's important to keep it tidy
'cause otherwise
it feels very messy quickly.
This is my kitchen.
Wanna see what's in the fridge?
Actually, my diet is very boring.
Is this extreme?
It's more peaceful when it's tidy.
I love my Dyson.
I actually do. I love cleaning.
I've always enjoyed precision and order
because that's just always who I've been.
I do apply
that kind of mentality in my work,
and I think that is a... a strong asset
and a strength for me.
I think that will do.
I got into racing
at the age of five years old.
My father was involved in racing,
and he was really keen
to get me into the sport.
Racing, that has been basically my life,
and it's been a long and tough journey,
but all the stars kind of finally aligned
and all the waiting and all the hard work
you've put in, uh, kind of came together.
Yeah. [chuckles]
-Vamos.
[upbeat music plays]
-What do... I don't like this.
-Nah.
-It's not for me. No.
-It's not my style.
I mean, it's Dubai style.
-It's flashy.
-Yeah.
[upbeat music continues]
The spot is already waiting for us
in the shade.
Super.
[de Vries] We good?
Yeah.
Perfect. Let's go.
-[Pulcini] Good day to play.
-[de Vries] Very nice.
Mamma mia! Disaster.
[Pulcini] How are you
getting along with Yuki?
-Yuki is a very quick driver.
-Yeah.
[de Vries] And so far, he has beaten me.
Clearly, the start of the season
hasn't been what I've hoped to show.
We've had five races so far.
I've had a bit of a challenging start.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 1] Contact!
[de Vries] Ah, fuck.
I made too many mistakes,
haven't really able to put it together
and execute a good result.
[groans]
Mamma mia.
-[Spini] Yuki, that's P10.
-Congratulations, guys.
We got the points.
From the start of this season,
from race one,
we've seen Yuki Tsunoda
consistently beating Nyck de Vries.
The expectation was
it would be the other way around.
[commentator 3] Nyck de Vries.
Oh, he's in the wall!
-Oh my God.
-[Hamelin] Retire the car.
[Spini] Checkered flag,
checkered flag. P10, Yuki.
Yes!
Good job, guys.
[de Vries] I was in Formula E
for three seasons.
The car is a bit different,
and I'm struggling to deal with it.
We should not forget it's also
your first year in Formula 1, huh?
[de Vries] Honestly, I'm really excited
for Monaco this weekend.
-It's just so special, I mean...
-So unique, right?
Match point.
Fuck!
-Sorry for the swearing.
-[chuckles]
[in French] What do you think?
Rain or no rain?
[man] One forecast is saying rain,
the other is a bit of rain.
[upbeat music plays]
[in English] What's up?
What's going on?
[music fades]
It's weird being here and not racing.
[reporter 1] And the news
coming in from Red Bull,
well, indeed the Red Bull family,
for this weekend,
is that Nyck de Vries
is under real pressure.
The Dutchman is yet to pick up a point.
Good morning.
Wow, the last time I saw so many people
was last year.
[reporter 2] It's been
a busy couple of weeks
in terms of speculation
about your future and everything.
What conversations have you had
with the team about
"Where am I at? What's my status?"
We didn't particularly speak very much
in the... in the last couple of weeks. Um...
And honestly,
that's really what I can say about it.
Is there something obvious you're doing
that Yuki's doing differently?
Or is it just inconsistency as you, uh,
as you get your head around things?
I acknowledge my mistakes,
and... and obviously I want to do better.
So, um, yeah, I'm...
I'm not someone who is quickly satisfied.
[ominous music plays]
[Wolff] Formula 1 is brutal.
You have the...
the stopwatch that never lies,
and you just gotta deliver.
You know, it's a tough business,
Formula 1. It's not for the fainthearted.
You have to face
all the criticism in the world.
[Wolff] If you're not performing,
you're being ejected from the system.
That's something
you need to always bear in mind.
It's no bullshit.
[Gasly] You know, as much as I know
how good of a driver he is,
uh, Red Bull doesn't have time.
They... They got no patience,
they got no mercy, and,
good or bad,
that's just the way it works there.
[Albon] At Red Bull,
your seat is never safe.
There are so many drivers in that program.
So as soon as you don't perform,
there's a replacement for you.
And that's where the pressure comes from.
There still seems to be
quite a bit of chatter around de Vries.
Oh, really?
What's happening there?
I think, unfortunately...
I think the pressure's building on him.
-[Ricciardo] How are you, buddy?
-What's up?
-When are you coming? Come on.
-[Ricciardo] Mate.
Watching your onboards
looks pretty good. [laughs]
-Good move as well.
-Yes. Oh, it's... it's good racing.
-[Ricciardo] How are you, boys?
-[man 1] Yeah, all right.
-[man 2] You, mate?
-Have a good day. All right see ya.
[Horner] They're desperate
to get you in a NASCAR.
[Ricciardo] Yeah. I know.
I just don't wanna...
Because I honestly don't feel done yet.
I don't wanna start deviating
and then just...
[Horner] Have you had anybody else come
out of the woodwork in the paddock yet?
Has anybody started...
It's still very early though.
I certainly don't wanna make plans.
Yeah. Take your time.
Cool, let's see what we got.
Enjoy.
[Horner] All righty.
Are you out tonight?
Yeah, I'm on the 9:20 with fucking
half the Formula 1 paddock, I think, so...
-Quick exit.
-Yeah.
So as long as I haven't got Helmut
farting in front of me, I'll be fine.
[all laugh]
Good morning.
Buenos días.
-Buen día. Good morning.
-Buen dia.
[de Vries] You're ahead of us already.
What is this?
-[Pérez] Where did you end up?
-Uh, P12.
[Pérez] Ah, good improvement.
-Yeah.
-[Pérez] From where you were.
So close to Q3 though.
-[Pérez] Yeah, anyways...
-Half a tenth would've done the job, but...
But it was decent. It was decent.
[Pérez] If you finish,
you will finish in the points.
I think that's what we got to do.
We just go to execute our race.
Not try and create opportunities
or force opportunities.
Just let the others do the job for you.
And keep it clean.
It's not straightforward.
At Red Bull, the pressure
is tremendously high,
uh, at all levels.
It doesn't matter if you are
a Red Bull driver or AlphaTauri.
And you don't quite appreciate
how bad it is
until you've gone a little bit through it.
-[woman] Good luck today. Both of you.
-Thank you. You too.
[Pérez] Thank you.
I try to watch you too. Good Luck.
[Pérez] It's a good opportunity for you.
Just make sure you finish.
[de Vries chuckles] Yeah.
[Pérez] You've got to deliver.
You've got to live up to expectations.
Not many can cope with... with that
sort of pressure in this environment.
[Horner] Nyck, he was expected
to go into that team
really to be the lead driver,
and Yuki is taking that role.
[team member laughs]
[Horner] You can see the pressure,
unfortunately, building on Nyck,
but he needs to demonstrate
that he's got the ability.
Just deliver. Just perform.
[tense music plays]
[helicopter whirring]
[Buxton] For Nyck,
this could be a huge race.
[Hamelin] Ten seconds.
[Buxton] An opportunity to score points,
prove that he belongs in Formula 1.
He just needs to get into the top ten.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 2]
Nyck de Vries starts in 12th,
his highest position
on the grid this year.
[de Vries] To be a Formula 1 driver,
you need to be able to switch yourself off
from all the noises and everything
that is happening around you.
[exciting music plays]
[commentator 3] De Vries gets away well.
[exciting music continues]
[music fades]
[Hamelin] P11.
Good job. Keep the position.
Piastri coming now.
Argh! He got me.
[Hamelin] Focus on the race.
Still a lot of laps to go.
Nyck, we are going slow.
Bottas directly behind you.
Head down. We'll catch the cars ahead.
[tense music plays]
This is getting frustrating.
This is so slow.
[Hamelin] Focus on the pace.
What lap times am I doing?
[Hamelin] 19.7. Yuki, 19.2.
[commentator 3] Oh, and it's definitely
getting grayer out there.
[Verstappen] Weather. How is that looking?
[Lambiase] Some pockets of rain.
[commentator 2]
Everyone checking the radar.
It could yet have a huge impact
on the outcome of this race.
[tense music plays]
-I have some raindrops on my visor.
-[Hamelin] Copy.
[commentator 3] It's all about
driver instinct now.
How much are you prepared to risk?
-[de Vries] I have zero, zero grip.
-[Hamelin] Box, box.
[tense music continues]
-[de Vries] Where's the tire switch?
-[Hamelin] Physical switch.
How do I do that?
-[Hamelin] Bottas behind.
-[de Vries] Wait.
-Tire switch to which color?
-[Hamelin] Don't worry.
-Focus on Bottas, please.
-[de Vries] Where is he?
-[Hamelin] Behind you.
-[Chan] Use overtake now.
[tense music continues]
[de Vries] Ah, fuck.
How many laps to go?
[Hamelin] One more lap.
One more lap. Keep the focus.
[tense music continues]
[Hamelin] P12. We really
have to understand what's happened there.
[de Vries] Yeah, copy.
[commentator 2] He started 12th,
but he finishes 12th.
Another race without points
for Nyck de Vries.
[de Vries] Too much time to get into
the rhythm, wasn't attacking enough.
But, um, yeah, I should've just
done a better job initially to attack.
He's having difficulties
in adapting to the car
and to the Formula 1 reality.
He has to improve.
He needs to deliver points.
Nyck's seat is under threat.
[Hamelin] Keep the position.
[de Vries] Argh!
The difference between being a hero
and a zero are just very fine.
[upbeat music plays]
-[Hamelin] P18.
-[de Vries] Fuck.
[upbeat music continues]
[Hamelin] You're good to push.
You attack everyone.
[de Vries] Copy.
[upbeat music continues]
[de Vries] Argh, fuck.
He needs to remember
how it feels to be quick.
how it feels to stand on the podium.
[Hamelin] Okay, so that's P17.
[de Vries] Very difficult.
You always got to keep believing
and keep pushing.
It's not done till it's done.
[Hamelin] Okay, Nyck,
Yuki is currently seven tenths faster.
[Horner] Nyck,
he's a really nice young man.
And Formula 1 is a fairly simple business.
Everybody loves you if you're quick.
If you're not,
then you can be as nice as you like,
it's not gonna guarantee you a seat.
[de Vries] Mistake. Fuck.
[tense music plays]
[Hamelin] That's P17.
[commentator] That is a very disappointing
weekend for Nyck De Vries of AlphaTauri.
[Horner] I think it's... it's clear that
Nyck's not quite hitting the mark, so...
We were hoping that,
because he knows the track here,
that would give him the confidence,
but he seems to struggle.
[Horner] Question, whether or not
we make the change or not.
I know it's harsh,
but I think he's had long enough.
[Bayer] Yeah. Yeah.
[Horner] Hey, Daniel, it's Christian.
Something I wanna put to you
that I think could be...
could be very interesting for you.
Yeah.
Well, you focus
on getting yourself sorted.
What time are you on track from?
-Is it 9:00? Track's open at 9:00?
-Track's 9:00 to 6:00.
Yeah.
[Horner] We got the opportunity
to put Daniel in a Red Bull car
for a few laps around Silverstone.
And that is gonna be the litmus test to...
where is Daniel?
How does he compare
to our current drivers?
[chuckles] How good's driving
after having eight months off?
I know.
I'm gonna be carried out today.
It's all right.
[Horner] Nyck's not really getting
the job done, so if the test goes well,
there could be a chance for Danny
in the AlphaTauri.
I think once I put the helmet on
and stuff, I'll be like...
Get a first lap under my belt.
-It'll be good.
-Yeah.
[Ricciardo] I know AlphaTauri
are not completely happy
with how things are currently going
in the team.
So if this test goes well,
I could be back in F1.
[Friend] Know what time
Christian arrives?
[Ricciardo] Probably first thing
in the morning.
[tense music plays]
Can't be Silverstone without a cup of tea
in a paper... paper cup. [chuckles]
[tense music continues]
As long as he delivers today,
I think in your environment,
new start, new beginning,
he's still part of the Red Bull family.
He's gonna see that as an opportunity
to get back into Red Bull Racing.
And he knows this is it.
-This is make-or-break for him.
-[Bayer] Yeah.
[Friend] Let's go, mate.
[Ricciardo] With the test I'm doing,
there's so many unknowns
and, of course, some fears or doubts.
I haven't been in the car yet.
I've driven the sim many times.
Uh, which is
a great simulator and whatever. [chuckles]
But it's...
I haven't driven the real car yet.
-G'day.
-How are you?
-They... They fit still, huh?
-Yeah.
-I know.
-It suits you.
-A little... A little tight.
-[Bayer] How are you, mate?
-[Ricciardo chuckles]
-Yeah.
-[Ricciardo] A bit impatient.
-Like going back in time.
-[Ricciardo] I know.
-[chuckles]
[Horner] Looking at your smile,
it doesn't look like you're done yet.
-[Ricciardo] All right, I'll see ya later.
-Suits you.
[Ricciardo] I love racing, and it's all
I've really ever done and all I've known.
I think this is really pretty much
my last chance to be back on the grid.
I want this seat.
[Rennie] Okay, so we won't do any
procedures. We'll just go straight out.
-[Ricciardo] Yep.
-[Rennie] Let you have a feel for it.
Okay, so it'll be straight out.
And track is clear. Track is clear.
[Horner] Daniel knows everybody's
gonna be looking at that data.
Everybody in the factory,
everybody trackside,
is gonna be looking at that data
to say, "Where is Daniel Ricciardo?"
[Rennie] Okay, Daniel.
Comments, please.
[Ricciardo] It's not perfect conditions.
There are still some damp spots.
[brakes screech]
[Rennie] Everything okay, Daniel?
Daniel?
[tense music plays]
[Ricciardo] All good. Just a little spin.
[Rennie] Okay.
[Ricciardo] After everything
that's happened,
I know I have a point to prove.
-[Horner] Is that 28.4?
-[Rennie] That's a lap, yeah, so...
So he's on it.
[tense music plays]
[music fades]
[Horner] Are you and your, uh, cohort...
-Available?
-Available.
-Yeah.
-[Horner] Let's have a cup of tea.
Okay, so, um, that lap he just did, um,
would've put him next to Max on...
on the grid.
He's... He's...
Looks like he's the Daniel
that we recognize
rather than the one I've seen
the last couple of years.
Interesting to see what Peter says
from AlphaTauri's point of view.
We'd like to see him in the car
from the next race.
I think, Peter, you're in agreement with...
But then, after eight months
not being in a car,
is, uh, is quite impressive.
And, you know, as we discussed earlier,
for us, is... is, uh, you know...
It's not only, you know,
that it's a fast driver.
It's also that, I think,
we can learn a lot from him.
-Peter.
-[Horner] There you go.
-[man] I'm very excited.
-[Friend] Thanks, mate.
[Horner] Everybody's aligned,
so as long as you're up for it...
-[Ricciardo] Cool.
-You happy with that?
You got the mojo back. Yeah. Good.
All right.
-[Ricciardo] Thanks.
-Back on the team. Well done.
[Ricciardo] Thank you.
Just don't fucking crash it.
[Ricciardo laughs]
[rock music plays]
[Ricciardo] A year ago, I wasn't sure
if I would race again in F1 or not.
It's exciting. I'm really happy.
Just give me the car,
and I'll show you on track.
[rock music continues]
[music fades]
It... It hurts
that something you've dreamed of
and worked towards for so long,
that it ends, uh, prematurely.
I was aware I wasn't where I wanted to be,
but, um, yeah, I guess
such a call always comes, somehow,
by, yeah, by a little bit of a surprise.
-[Norris] What's wrong with my car?
-[Joseph] Box now.
It's garbage.
It's rare one driver sticks
with the same team their whole career.
Hearing a lot of rumors around Lando.
Lando, you know,
we'd certainly be interested in him.
The most excited people
when Danny Ric came back was Netflix.
I literally think they had to change
their pants three times.
-[Hamelin] Watch out, turn 10.
-[Ricciardo] Fuck! My hand.
We expect both drivers to work together.
[commentator 1] Contact!
[Ocon] Oh my God.
Fuck!
[somber music plays]
[music fades]