[Ocon] Very nice to meet you.
How are you doing?
-Good. How are you?
-Very good.
[Ryan Reynolds] It's the most exciting
sport. It's crazy how fast it's growing.
-[Ocon] It is.
-[Reynolds] It's also the...
The documentary
has been a gateway for so many people.
You've seen it?
-[Reynolds] Every single episode.
-Okay.
[Reynolds] My kids always laugh
because they go,
"Dad, you say you wanna relax.
All I hear is..."
-[Reynolds imitates an engine revving]
-[Ocon laughs]
[Ocon] Oh no. There's a new season coming.
Where are they?
-You are gonna be in the Netflix series.
-Hi!
-Finally!
-Finally. [chuckles]
Someone else's documentary.
[reporter] Hollywood actors Ryan Reynolds
and Rob McElhenney
are joining an investor group
taking a 24% equity stake
in Alpine Racing.
[man] Let's just take a picture
with Cosmopolitan magazine.
[Szafnauer] Oh wow.
Do you want my good side
or my really good side?
[woman laughs]
Any level of significant investment
into your team
is so extraordinarily welcome.
But of course they're not just doing that
for the love of the sport.
They're not only doing it
for the love of your team.
They are doing it because they want
a significant return on their investment.
And that brings so much pressure
on a Formula 1 team principal
to perform immediately.
What was your reaction when you heard
that you were gonna have
some Hollywood stars involved?
Well, I know more about the car
and performance than I do Hollywood stars,
but they're a welcome addition.
Those investors have come in,
so it's important
to hit the targets that we set.
-There we go.
-Oh yeah!
[Szafnauer] But, uh, our season so far
has been disappointing.
[commentator 1] Esteban Ocon
has been retired from the race.
[in French] When we make the same mistakes
twice, that is not acceptable.
[commentator 2 in English] Pierre Gasly
coming home in 19th.
[commentator 1] I mean, seriously,
could it get much worse?
[in French] There is a state of mind
which is not up to
the level of what has been done
in the past by the same team.
[commentator 1 in English]
There's contact!
-Agh, fuck!
-What the fuck?
[commentator 3] Both Alpines are out.
[in French] We are concerned and focused.
[Szafnauer in English]
I can sense the pressure.
If we're underperforming,
it's not good enough.
I have to do better.
The buck will stop with me.
[wheel gun whirring]
[engine revs]
[funky music plays]
[in French] Hey, Tony.
We just arrived and we got my ticket.
And we're waiting for you.
I can't wait, to be honest. I'm excited!
[funky music continues]
-[in French] So nice to see you!
-Hey, how are you?
-It's good to see you. Yes, I'm great.
-I'm trying to remember the last time...
Yeah, that's crazy.
When was the last time we met?
I think it was in Miami
when I came to see you.
That was just a quick visit.
[Parker] How is your season going?
The season? Well, there's some good
and some less good.
[in English] This clearly hasn't been
the start that we would have liked.
I think, objectively,
we haven't been competitive enough.
The target is fourth.
And, at the moment, it doesn't look like
we're gonna be able to achieve it.
[in French] For my career,
I need things to be better right now.
[Parker] Is that possible?
[Gasly in English] Something
is not clicking somewhere.
Clearly, the communication
hasn't been to the best level.
And, um, I think it's something
very important, as a team principal,
is to understand
what your drivers actually need.
[Gasly in French] Let's go, guys.
[in English] So, uh,
now need to do the work and... and deliver.
[in French] How are things in the team?
I'm just in the middle.
How do you stay focused, Esteban?
It must be hard.
Well, it's... it's... There are always
things going on in the team.
I'm just focused on my role.
[Ocon in English] It's important
to work well, you know, inside the team.
To be... To have a close relationship,
in a way.
To... To talk about the things
that are important.
At the moment, we are not... doing that.
No one is happy inside the team.
I think Otmar needs
to find out some solutions.
[Buxton] It's about
halfway through the season,
and Otmar has two drivers
who are not happy.
He needs to turn this season around.
[dramatic orchestral music plays]
[commentator 1] Welcome to Silverstone.
Wherever you're watching in the world,
the very best of British for you.
[man] Bollocks.
[orchestral music continues]
[fans cheer]
[fans] Daniel! Daniel! Daniel!
[fan] Otmar, which of your drivers
do you prefer?
The one I prefer, and it changes,
is always the quicker one.
You know what I mean?
[in French] We're aiming for fourth place,
but we're fifth.
A long way off
in terms of performance and points.
That isn't what we were hoping for.
We have to correct the situation
as soon as possible.
[in English] Gentlemen. Good, thank you.
In Formula 1,
transforming a team to be
a, uh, championship contender takes time.
Where's our hospitality?
Yeah, just keep going.
[Szafnauer] Success in our game
doesn't happen overnight.
You have to put
the building blocks in place
to be able to have that success.
It takes time.
[commentator 1] Well, it's race day,
and what a special race day it is too.
It's the British Grand Prix.
[Brown] Let's get together.
[Gordon Ramsay]
Are you breakfast, or lunch, or...?
-I'm all of the above.
-[Ramsay] Red wine?
All the above. [laughs]
[tense music plays]
-[Jason Oppenheim] Good luck today.
-Okay, thank you.
Are they footballers?
Uh, no, Selling Sunset
or some shit like that.
[tense music continues]
[commentator 2] We are ready to go racing.
-[Loos] Pierre, radio check.
-[Gasly] Yeah, all good.
[commentator 2] Pierre Gasly
starts in tenth place.
[Gasly] I know what's required to perform.
I need to be on top of my game
for everything.
[commentator 2] Esteban Ocon
disappointed to start 13th,
but a good chance to get in the points.
[Ocon] A difficult start.
But I know I have to perform.
I need to make it count.
[Loos] Full focus.
Make sure we get some good points.
[Gasly] Let's go, boys.
Be sharp and we'll get them.
[commentator 1] We are ready to go racing.
[commentator 2] And the grand prix is go!
[commentator 1] Lando Norris
leads the British Grand Prix!
You can hear the roars!
[commentator 2] That's Hamilton.
Goes very, very wide.
[commentator 1] Gasly making up places.
[Loos] Hamilton 0.5 behind.
Doing a good job.
-[Gasly] I'm feeling good on these tires.
-[Loos] Yeah, copy that.
[Peckett] Good start.
Currently running P11.
Next car, Stroll.
-[Ocon] Copy.
-[Peckett] Okay, let's push.
[tense music plays]
[Ocon] I have a problem, guys.
For fuck's sake.
[Peckett] Box the car, please.
Box, box, box. Box, box, box.
[Ocon] Okay, what's wrong?
[Peckett] We're concerned
it's not gonna last more than another lap.
[foreboding music plays]
[Peckett] Esteban,
we are retiring the car.
Switch off, please. Switch off.
And be ready to jump out, please, as well.
I'm very sorry.
[dramatic music plays]
[Loos] So, for info,
Esteban is out of the race.
What's our position?
[Loos] Uh, P6.
Piastri one second behind.
[Gasly] Yeah, he's got fucking DRS!
So we've got to react now.
[commentator 1] Here comes Oscar Piastri
on Pierre Gasly.
[dramatic music continues]
[Gasly] We are losing a lot of time
on the straight.
[Loos] Understood. We're on it.
Boxing this lap, boxing this lap.
[commentator 3] Gasly into the pits.
It will drop him down to P11.
Alpine need to salvage some points
from the race.
[Loos] P11 at the moment.
All we got.
Behind, you've got Stroll.
[Gasly] Copy.
[commentator 2] Stroll going around
the outside of Gasly.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 1] Stroll moves up
into 11th place.
[Gasly] He was off the track.
He needs to give me back
that fucking position now!
[Loos] Yeah, we're on it, mate. Stay calm.
[Gasly] I am in that mindset,
"Okay, I need to fight."
[Loos] Eight laps to go.
-Let's get him, mate.
-[Gasly] Push, push, push!
[exciting music plays]
[commentator 1] Round the outside
there goes Pierre Gasly.
[exciting music continues]
[Loos] Beautiful, mate.
[commentator 1] Gasly up to 11th.
[Loos] So Sainz, one second.
Overtake available.
[Gasly] Copy.
[commentator 1] Gasly's now on the tail
of Carlos Sainz!
[exciting music plays]
[commentator 3] Around the outside
once more.
And Gasly takes tenth place.
[exciting music continues]
[commentator 1] Carlos Sainz
tries to get back that place.
And does so.
[Gasly] Gotta be fucking kidding me.
We need more straight-line speed
if we want to fight.
I passed the guy, then he's passing me
like a joke on the straight.
How many laps to go?
[Loos] Eight. Eight laps to go.
Stroll 0.3 behind.
[Gasly] I need more power!
[exciting music plays]
-[cars thud]
-[tires screech]
[Gasly] That fucker
didn't give me enough space!
That's it. Stroll broke the suspension.
[commentator 1] It is a double DNF
for Alpine here at Silverstone.
[Loos] Ah, sorry, mate.
Can't believe this.
[Szafnauer] Keep your heads up.
Thank you very much for the hard work.
These weekends happen
every once in a while.
So don't worry. Let's move forward.
You know,
if something could go wrong, it did.
And it happened in a weekend
where you're really punished.
So just... don't worry about it.
Keep doing a good job.
Don't let it get you down.
And that's all I wanted to say.
Thanks again.
Yeah, thanks again.
[team member] All right. Thank you, guys.
[Famin in French]
It's a real disappointment.
We shouldn't be trying to find excuses,
and we simply need to work harder
to correct things and improve quickly.
[tense music plays]
[Williams in English]
So for the Alpine board,
poor performance cannot
all be down to bad luck.
It's normally because
things are going wrong in your team.
[tense music continues]
Otherwise, you would say,
the guys who are winning everything,
all of that success is down to good luck.
[tense music continues]
[Gasly] I'm not a rookie anymore.
I have some experience under my belt,
and I just want results.
Clearly hasn't been the season that we had
hoped for at the start of the year.
Every team manager is under pressure.
It's a sport where you gotta deliver.
[bells toll]
[commentator 1] So here we go, then,
for the 38th World Championship
Hungarian Grand Prix.
[commentator 3]
After Alpine's double DNF in Silverstone,
they can't afford
to not get big points today
in their battle with McLaren
for fourth in the Constructors.
[Szafnauer] You know,
nobody wants to have a DNF,
but if you looked at the positive side,
uh, the... the performance, the race pace
was actually pretty good.
So there... there were some...
some, uh, positives.
But overall,
not scoring points is a negative
that, uh, needed to be fixed.
[crowd cheering]
-Radio check?
-[Peckett] Yes, radio check.
[Loos] Let's stay focused
and try to get in the points.
[Gasly exhales slowly]
[commentator 1] It's lights out,
away we go.
[exciting music plays]
[commentator 1] Racing, then,
towards the first corner!
[exciting music continues]
[commentator 1] And there's contact!
Fuck!
-He's fucked it up.
-That's it.
[Ocon] Fuck's sake.
I got massively hit, guys.
[Gasly] I don't understand.
[Loos] Too much damage.
[Peckett] Esteban, this is gonna be
terminal, please. We're retiring.
[commentator 3] And that's a second double
"did not finish" in a row for Alpine.
Disaster for Otmar.
[Szafnauer] Every weekend, things happen,
and you learn from 'em, and you move on.
But, uh, you have to focus on the things
that, uh, you're in control of.
[Buxton] You're only as good
as your last race.
It's all about results.
The two double DNFs in a row
took a huge number of points
off the board.
And the team's really struggling.
The buck always has to stop somewhere.
[somber music plays]
[Szafnauer] Nobody wants to,
uh, have a DNF.
We've truly been unlucky this year.
To have a, uh, a result slip away
due to circumstances out of your control...
Yeah, I don't worry about those things.
[Famin in French] I don't like
to bring luck into things.
Bad luck goes hand in hand
with not being good enough.
Starting from the middle of the grid,
you're more at risk of being involved
in collisions on the first corners.
We're trying to fight
for what few points we can,
and two double DNFs
is extremely frustrating.
The pressure is, of course, on Otmar
because he is the team principal.
[in English] To have
two race weekends in a row
where neither of your cars finish,
I mean, that's almost unheard of
in Formula 1.
Allez. [clears throat]
[man 1] Everyone has suffered.
Everyone in the garage,
the office, the drivers.
It's how we can... combat that.
If times don't change,
we're gonna be facing
the same thing, aren't we?
[man 2] It has been a focus point for us
and a sort of request and requirement
to try and improve
over the course of the last few months.
[Famin in French] When you do worse
than your competitors,
it's extremely frustrating.
We need to help the team progress.
We know we have to change something.
[commentator 2 in English]
Welcome to Spa-Francorchamps.
It's the Belgian Grand Prix.
With unpredictable weather conditions,
it's one of the most unforgiving places
on the race calendar.
[tense music plays]
[reporter] Breaking news here
in the paddock at the Belgian Grand Prix,
and it involves the Alpine F1 team.
And we are waiting
for an official announcement
from Alpine.
[news alert whistles]
I don't know what the fuck's going on.
Very strange.
[news alert whistles]
[Brown] Never a dull moment.
-[man] I know.
-[Brown] Crazy.
-[man] What a fucking...
-[Brown chuckles]
[Steiner] What a shitshow, huh?
I called you.
I know, I know.
I saw, but I couldn't talk.
I was in a precarious position.
Sorry to hear how that's played out.
Yeah, don't worry. Not to worry.
-You okay?
-[Szafnauer] Um...
This was very sudden,
so I... I don't have a plan B, so to speak.
-[man 1] Otmar.
-[man 2] Boys.
[man 1] No way.
You know that was never
a mutual agreement.
But I'm sorry to see you go.
-[Szafnauer] It won't be forever.
-[man 1] No, I know.
In some respects, it seems like a bit
of a shit show at the moment.
You're probably better off out of it.
[Williams] It's highly unusual to do this.
I'm not sure that I could ever recall
a time in Formula 1
where a team principal has been dismissed
halfway through a race weekend.
That's where it is.
Yeah.
I tried. I mean,
last year, we were fourth.
Yeah, yeah, exactly. It's, like...
Not all of it,
but a bit of that was because of me.
[Famin in French] When we realized we were
very far from our performance goals,
we talked with Otmar
and the top management,
and we realized
we weren't on the same page
about the way we had to change things.
So we agreed
it was better to go our separate ways.
[Famin in English] Otmar!
-[Szafnauer] Good luck.
-[Famin] I will need it.
No, no, I'm sure you'll be fine.
All the best.
Yeah, thank you. We'll see.
[Famin in French] That's life.
[in English] Good luck.
[tense music plays]
[Szafnauer] Alpine could have been
much more honest and transparent.
Sometimes, you take
two steps forward, one step backwards
before you get to where you're going.
[man 1 in French] Who's with Bruno?
Christian Horner?
[man 2] Alunni Bravi,
Christian Horner, and Mike Krack.
-[Famin] I know Mike.
-[man 2] Alunni Bravi, he speaks French?
[Famin] Yes, yes,
he speaks very good French.
[man 2] Christian...
Christian, I have more doubts about.
-Bonjour.
-[Famin] Bonjour.
[in English] How are you?
Still alive.
-[both laugh]
-Hello.
-Hi. Morning.
-Very good.
So, the new boss, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah. Okay.
[Horner] It's a punchy decision.
But Alpine is a mystery in many respects
in terms of how
that team runs and operates.
I mean, let's see how that works out.
-[man 1] Bruno.
-[Bravi] Has he offered it to you?
With Bruno coming in, everyone
wants to see how the new guy operates.
[Williams] You're coming in
halfway through a year,
and, by the way, you've never run
a Formula 1 team before.
Not easy.
That's a really difficult gig to take on.
And that team is gonna be
on its knees right now.
One of Bruno's first focuses
will have to be
how does he improve that morale?
He's not gonna get a morale boost
from performance on the racetrack.
It's gonna have to be done in another way.
[Famin] Okay, let's go.
-[man] After you.
-[Famin] Thank you.
-Good morning.
-[woman 1] Morning.
-[woman 2] How are you?
Okay. So far.
[both chuckle]
[Famin in French] My goal is to change
the dynamic and morale of the team.
My leadership, the way I do things,
is I want to be close to the people.
Close to the team, and to stay in contact.
[Famin speaks French]
I need everyone to follow me
on this project
so we can perform as good as possible.
[Famin in English]
So, um, good afternoon, everyone.
Happy to be here.
Um, we are not making one step backward.
We are making a step forward.
We are pushing.
We have a lot of talented
and motivated people here,
and we need to design the best car
and to race it in the best way.
Together, we work and we race as one.
But I am super optimistic.
Working all together,
being always better,
uh, never satisfied,
and fighting like hell
for improving our results.
Thank you.
[Gasly] Okay. Allez.
[Famin in French] The situation
between Esteban and Pierre,
I realized that I had to do something.
[Ocon] Bonjour.
[Gasly] Bonjour.
We talked.
In talking about it quickly
between the three of us,
it allowed us to clear things up
and move on.
And there aren't going to be
any problems between them anymore.
And that gives us a very positive dynamic.
[tense music plays]
[Buxton in English] Bruno Famin
has a massive job on his hands.
[Famin] Messieurs.
The longer you go
without scoring points in Formula 1,
the... the more the pressure's gonna ramp up
on you, on the team.
[tense music continues]
[Buxton] He needs to turn around
what's been a very difficult season.
[Famin in French] There are
a lot of people in an F1 team,
but you have to know everybody,
and know their needs,
what their job is, and what it entails.
What are their difficulties
and how can you help them?
Make sure that everyone has what they need
in order to work well together.
We have a plan,
and will execute it and move forward.
But we know that the following races
will be difficult.
[commentator 1 in English] Zandvoort is
a sea of color today
for the Dutch Grand Prix.
But for the majority,
it's all about one man.
[commentator 3] But eyes will also be on
the new Alpine team principal,
Bruno Famin,
who will be hoping to score
some much-needed points
at one of the trickiest circuits
on the calendar.
[tense music plays]
[Gasly] I must say, this place is crazy.
I've never seen that much orange.
I'm so excited.
Yeah, no problem. No problem. Ciao.
Bruno came with very good intentions
and a very good mindset
and brought some fresh ideas
into the team.
We have a common, uh, target
with the team,
and... and we're both working really well.
I wanna win,
so let's just fucking do it, you know?
-Ready?
-Uh-huh.
'Ave it.
Let's get this one done, shall we?
Where do you think we'll finish?
[Famin in French] I've always enjoyed
leading teams. It's something I do well.
Project Alpine is a huge responsibility,
so the pressure is there.
But I have faith
in the ability
of all the people from Alpine
to outdo themselves
and give their all
to improving the team in the long run.
[tense music plays]
[Gasly in English] I'm going into the race
knowing I wanna get
the best result I can for the team.
My ambition is clear.
To bring Alpine to the top
and become world champion one day.
[commentator 3] Ocon starts in 16th.
-[Peckett] Ready for radio check?
-[Ocon] Good radio.
[commentator 3] Gasly in 12th.
[Loos] Last car is on the grid.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 3] Good start from Gasly,
up a place already
after overtaking a Williams.
[Loos] Nice work, mate.
[Gasly] Lots of rain starting.
[commentator 1] What was dry
is now heavy rain and a very wet track.
[commentator 2] It looks like
a lot of teams are holding their nerve
and keeping their cars out on track.
[Gasly] Box! Box, box, box, box.
-[Loos] Box, box.
-Copy.
[Loos] Tires to inters.
[commentator 1] Pierre Gasly
coming into the pit.
They've decided to take the gamble.
-[Loos] Okay, head down, mate.
-[Gasly] Copy.
[commentator 2] Gasly comes
out of the pits in 16th place.
[Loos] Overtake available.
[tense music plays]
[Loos] Keep pushing, mate.
You're making places.
Good job.
[commentator 2] With wet-weather tires,
Gasly is flying.
He's up into fifth place.
Alpine's gamble is working.
[dramatic music plays]
[Loos] Okay, mate. So P4.
-[Gasly] That's what I like!
-[Loos] Nice work, mate.
And how's the track?
-Pretty dry.
-[Loos] Copy.
[Peckett] Okay, Esteban,
keep your pace up.
[commentator 3] Esteban Ocon
currently running in tenth place,
just inside the points.
[Peckett] DRS enabled.
[commentator 3] Yuki and Ocon
wheel to wheel in the battle for ninth!
-[Peckett] Okay, let's keep going.
-[Ocon] Copy.
[commentator 2] Can Ocon
stay in the top ten
and secure precious points for Alpine?
Here comes the rain again!
-[Loos] This rain could get very heavy.
-What's our current position?
[Loos] Currently, we are P4.
Pérez P3.
[Bird] Okay, Checo, we have a five-second
penalty for speeding in the pit lane.
[Pérez] Fuck!
[man] Yes!
[Loos] All right, mate,
so Pérez has a five-second penalty.
Six laps. Stay within five seconds
if you can.
[commentator 2] If Gasly can
finish the race within five seconds
of Pérez's rapid Red Bull,
he'll be on the podium.
Could be good news
in Bruno Famin's
first race as a team boss.
[Gasly] It's been a tough season,
but I have extreme motivation
and this will and desire.
At this moment, there is a lot at stake.
I know there is a chance at the podium.
And I wanna deliver.
[Loos] Full focus.
[dramatic music plays]
[Bird] Gap to Gasly 2.6.
[dramatic music continues]
[Loos] Time to gain turn one and two
compared to Pérez.
[Gasly] Just give me the gap.
[Loos] 3.1 seconds.
[commentator 3] Pérez
is starting to pull away.
[Loos] Last lap. He was
a bit quicker than us in sector one.
[dramatic music continues]
[commentator 3] Gasly across the line!
[Loos] P3, baby. P3!
[Gasly] Let's go!
[triumphant music plays]
[Gasly] Let's fucking go!
Woo-hoo-hoo!
[Loos] Amazing, man! Amazing!
[Gasly] What a race! What a race!
[triumphant music continues]
[Peckett] That is the checkered flag. P10.
[commentator 2] Double points for Alpine.
[Peckett] Pierre third,
so he got a podium.
[Ocon] Oh, guys!
Yes!
[Gasly] Fuck yes!
That's what I like, baby!
You guys can be proud. Very well executed.
[Loos] Awesome job. Awesome job.
[Gasly] Thank you.
Come on!
[Gasly] Everything was great, so...
Really stoked.
Really, really good car, so...
Very happy for all of you guys.
[triumphant music continues]
[music fades]
[man] Yeah, boy!
[announcer] Pierre Gasly.
Well done to him.
This podium is the result
and the reward from all the hard work,
um, that we... we've been putting in
with the team.
[cheering]
[Gasly] We just stayed ice-cold
the whole race and managed to get that P3,
so that was incredible.
[Ocon] We all celebrated, like you should,
you know, after the race,
so I think the morale is... is really good.
[man] Yeah, man. Congrats.
[laughter]
[in French] Are you happy with the trophy?
It feels good.
It's a piece of plastic, but...
Is it microwaveable?
Yeah, it can be a big glass at home.
[Famin] So the priority was
clearly to change the team's mindset.
And now,
it is together that we will succeed
in increasing our results,
progressing, and achieving victories.
[cheering]
[Buxton] Ferrari wanted a new direction,
and Fred represents that.
[commentator 1] Sainz locks up!
They avoid contact.
Watching your two drivers
battle on the track,
the TP needs to tell their drivers,
"Dial it down a bit."
[Ricciardo] Fuck! My hand. [groans]
There is no way that you come back
from that injury quickly.
[Williams] And they've got
to plug the gap.
I'm Liam Lawson,
and I'm an AlphaTauri reserve.
[commentator 1] Liam Lawson
for his first ever Qualifying!
[Ricciardo] What does this mean for me?
[closing theme music plays]
[music fades]