[producer] If you could just...
Your collar is just stood up at the back.
-Just pull it out.
-This here?
Is that any better?
My name is Otmar Szafnauer,
Team Principal
of the BWT Alpine Formula 1 team.
[man] T-shirt size?
Uh, XL.
Got it.
Uh, sorry, I'm miked up.
Ask me that again.
Uh, what T-shirt size?
-[Szafnauer] Medium.
-There you go.
[upbeat music plays]
[man] On behalf of Columbia University,
our entire sports-management program...
it is an incredible pleasure to welcome
a 26-year Formula 1 veteran,
Otmar Szafnauer.
Thanks for your time
and thanks for coming.
How do you choose
which drivers will join an F1 team?
You want the fastest drivers.
You also have to choose
from those that are available.
We already have Esteban Ocon.
And this season, I'm excited
because Pierre Gasly joins us.
Usually, I always read what I sign.
Should I?
[laughter]
[team member] So you guys
are gonna be a great team?
[Szafnauer] We have great drivers.
I just need to get everyone
to pull in the same direction.
Species that collaborate
survive.
Species that are selfish go extinct.
High-performing teams are the same.
If you get it wrong, it bites you.
[wheel gun whirring]
[engine revs]
[tranquil music plays]
Hello.
It's Pierre Clooney.
Let's go, Netflix.
[in French] Do you prefer
high or low angle?
I prefer it like this. A little higher.
[photographer] Okay, that's good.
[in English] Coming into the 2023 season,
it's a huge change
for me personally and in my career.
I've been with Red Bull Racing
or AlphaTauri for ten years.
[upbeat music plays]
My first win with AlphaTauri.
[cheering]
[Gasly] I scored the most points
of any driver in that team
in the entire history of Formula 1.
But...
[commentator 1] And that's Gasly.
Gasly's out of the race.
[Gasly] ...ultimately, as a driver,
what you want is a competitive car.
And I'll stop here.
It's impossible to win a championship
with... with AlphaTauri.
So I'm starting
this new project with Alpine.
Full of excitement
about this new chapter in my life.
[in French] I'm gonna take a selfie.
[Gasly in English] It is
a very unique story
to be able to come from Normandy,
where I'm from,
make it to Formula 1,
and after five seasons in F1,
join the only French team on the grid.
I really see huge potential in Alpine.
I think these opportunities
come along the way
as you reach the top of your sport.
-I see you focused, but not stressed.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, like, super focused, right?
-Uh-huh.
I got everything under control,
and I'm just excited to perform
and, uh, and to race.
[Gasly] Can't wait
to just get this season started.
What do you think of Agent 0010?
[in Portuguese] Beautiful. I love it.
-Very beautiful?
-Very beautiful.
[Gasly in English] We got another race
up the red carpet tonight.
[upbeat music plays]
[Gasly] Driving for Alpine
brings you to these places
where you're just... in a dream.
You think everything is surreal.
When you're going to Cannes
and you see all these people
going with incredible dresses,
like, insane watches,
and now, I've got the watch,
I've got the bow-tie.
-Got...
-I knew it! I know you so well!
-I've got the best girlfriend in town.
-I know you so well.
[photographers shouting]
[Gasly] Okay, so you're gonna
go first, babe.
It's just that I need to be on your left.
Ah, let's go then.
[upbeat music continues]
[Gasly] My sporting heroes are Zidane,
Ayrton Senna,
Michael Schumacher,
and Michael Jordan.
All these champions
became bigger than their sport
thanks to the success they had.
I do have a will to be, also,
more than just a sportsman.
But you don't become an icon
without the results.
So I need to be fighting for race wins.
[camera shutters click]
[Gasly] Crazy!
Welcome to my life.
[Buxton] For Pierre,
moving to Alpine is a huge opportunity.
But he's gonna have to
mark his own territory,
because Pierre is stepping
into Esteban's playground.
[tense music plays]
-Morning.
-[woman] Good morning! How are you?
-Very good. You?
-[woman] Very well, thank you.
[tense music continues]
[in French] All right, let's go.
A new season is starting.
[producer in English]
Number one, here he is.
Number one. First one of the year.
-Here we go. [chuckles]
-[producer] The main man.
The main man? I don't know.
You tell me. [chuckles]
I'm Esteban Ocon,
racing for Alpine F1 team.
Clap.
I feel good at Alpine.
You know, I've been since 2020.
I won a race. I finished on the podium.
And they count on me to be that leader.
[Buxton] Esteban Ocon is a shrewd operator
who, when it comes to his teammates,
doesn't always play nice.
We've seen that
at every team he's raced for.
[commentator 2] The two Force Indias
scrapping away. Pérez and Ocon collide.
There it is. Big damage!
Both damaged. To Pérez's front wing.
[Pérez] What did Esteban do, guys?!
What happened today
is totally unacceptable for the team.
That's how not professional he is,
and, yeah,
I think I will go tell him the truth.
It didn't end well with Pérez.
It didn't end well with Alonso.
[commentator 3] The Alpines going for it.
Fernando Alonso almost in the wall.
[commentator 4]
Fighting between teammates.
[commentator 3]
Not helping each other, are they?
[Alonso] Sometimes it's very competitive
inside the team,
and on the positive side,
it's over, uh, finally.
[Ocon] I'm a competitor,
and I like to win.
[tense music plays]
[Ocon] Of course,
I've got a new teammate this year.
Pierre. Obviously, he's someone I know.
But I don't have my say
on these decisions.
[tense music continues]
[Gasly] Yeah, I know Esteban.
I know him like a younger brother.
The only thing is, with Esteban,
there are a lot of problems and tensions.
We both know we'll never be best friends.
[Gasly in French] How are you?
All good, thank you very much.
I was telling them
that we've known each other for 20 years.
Fuck, you're right. More than that.
We were six, seven?
I was six when I started. Six years old.
I told them that it's not often in life
you've known someone for that many years.
[in English] Ultimately, the decision to
put these two drivers together is Otmar's.
-Come on, boys.
-[man] Daddy is here.
Giving Alpine the PR masterstroke
of an all-French lineup at a French team.
[laughter]
[Buxton] But Pierre and Esteban
don't necessarily always see eye to eye.
They have a history of not getting on.
-Great.
-Perfect.
Now we'll take the two of you
to the staircase.
[Szafnauer] I know about the animosity
between Pierre and Esteban,
but you don't need drivers to be friends,
and I can manage tricky drivers.
It's not easy to do.
It takes a certain leadership style.
But I'm confident in myself.
You want serious or smiling or...
[Szafnauer] A bit of both.
Same thing. I just smile now.
[Szafnauer] At Alpine,
there is a common goal.
We expect both drivers
to work together
to maximize the team's performance
in the Constructors Championship.
[tense music plays]
I'm Laurent Rossi. I'm the CEO of Alpine.
Last year, we were in fourth.
Naturally, you wanna climb the ladder.
What we need is
to make as much progress as we can.
Progress that will take us to...
I hope, closer to the third position
or the podium, if you will.
Obviously, Otmar has
a lot of responsibility.
[Szafnauer] This year, there is definitely
more pressure from Alpine's leadership
throughout the organization to do better.
[tense music continues]
[in French] Bruno Famin,
Executive Director of Alpine Racing.
I'm more of a person
who works in the shadows.
The spotlight, like this, is not my thing.
The pressure is, of course, on Otmar
because he is the team principal.
In 2023, there is Red Bull,
there is Ferrari,
there is, of course, Mercedes.
And our goal?
To be part
of those two, three, maybe four teams,
that fight for titles.
To develop the Alpine brand,
which is legendary in France,
around the world.
-[in English] Hello.
-[woman] Morning.
-Morning. How we doing?
-[woman] What time do you call this?
-[Gasly] Pierre's time.
-[woman laughs]
[woman] Get your race suit on.
We'll see you on track. Thanks.
[Ocon in French] Hello. You all right?
I'm good, I'm good.
-I'm glad to see you.
-Yeah, it's been a few years.
[man] We prepared a great kart for you,
with your colors.
-[Ocon] Oh, really?
-Yes, we've gone to great efforts.
[Ocon] There's even the logo.
That's amazing!
[Otmar in English] The plan today
is to take Pierre and Esteban
back to their old days of karting.
We want to show the world
that they can work together
and put the past behind them.
[tense music plays]
[Gasly] The story with Esteban is, uh...
There could be a movie about it.
You know, we're both coming
from the same part of Normandy,
living 20 minutes from each other.
[reporter speaks in French]
[Gasly in English] Growing up,
from six years old until ten,
we used to spend so much time together.
We would practice together.
We would race together.
And we were very close.
[Ocon] Yeah, we were very close,
you know, friends when we were younger.
The first time he... he stepped in a go-kart
was in my go-kart.
[reporter speaks French]
[Gasly in English] My first year or two,
Esteban was slightly better than me,
and he would just, like, go behind me,
and try to overtake me,
and play
these sort of psychological games.
And then after, I kicked his ass,
and he didn't like it. [laughs]
[reporter speaks French]
[Gasly in English] I remember it was one
of the biggest national competitions
of the year at that time.
I think it was 2008.
I had a fantastic race on that day.
And on the last lap,
I'm fourth, Esteban is third.
Both side by side, to the line.
And then, I just, like, pass him
just literally on the last corner.
The friendship we had,
it just went downwards from there.
[Ocon] It is true. That's what he did.
You know, overtake on the last lap.
But, um, I can tell you that he wasn't
racing the way he should have done.
[Gasly] Ultimately, I got disqualified.
[producer] Who's better at karting?
[chuckles] I have, uh, won more titles.
[laughs]
[tense music plays]
[Gasly] Um, I know
I've given Esteban many, many chances
to make this relationship work,
but if someone doesn't wanna be friends,
then that's fine to me.
[producer] Your relationship
with Pierre, the disconnect,
are you able to expand at all on it?
Not really. I think it's...
There's a lot of personal reasons,
um, you know, for these things.
[reporter speaks French]
-[Gasly in English] Enough talking.
-[man] Come on, yes.
[woman] Now talk on the track.
[rock music plays]
[Alpine PR] We're gonna just do two laps
where you're a bit together...
[Gasly in French] Two laps, but slowly.
Yes, I know,
but the season starts in three days.
-[laughter]
-[exciting music plays]
[Alpine PR in English] I'm trying
to get Pierre to slow down.
[man] Pierre's not gonna slow down.
[exciting music plays]
[Alpine PR] Overtake?
[exciting music continues]
[tires squeal]
[man shouts in French]
[Alpine PR] I think
he hurt his, uh, neck crashing.
-[Gasly] I didn't touch!
-[group laughing]
My front spoiler is clean.
[laughter continues]
He looked at me,
and then he went in the grass.
[Buxton] Yes, it's only karting,
but Pierre and Esteban
fighting against each other that hard,
it's definitely not ideal.
You hope it's not an omen.
[upbeat music plays]
[commentator 2] From Melbourne,
welcome to
the Australian Grand Prix of 2023,
the third round
of the Formula 1 World Championship.
[music stops]
Coming into the Australian Grand Prix,
we're fifth place in the championship.
We're already behind
some of our competitors.
Ferrari are ahead of us in fourth,
then Mercedes as well.
At least we're doing
a better job than McLaren!
-[Zak Brown] Morning.
-[man] Morning.
But, uh, we have to get
a little bit closer to the top three.
It's important to hit
the, uh, targets that we set.
-Bonjour, bonjour.
-[team member] Comment vas-tu?
Oui, et toi? Bien, bien.
[Alpine PR] How's it gonna go today?
It's gonna go fucking amazing.
Trophy time.
Trophy!
[tense music plays]
[commentator 2] Esteban Ocon starts 11th
with his teammate, Pierre Gasly, in ninth.
[Gasly] I feel I've got a point to prove.
I know Esteban wants to beat me
every single time we're on the racetrack,
but there's no way
someone should be better than me.
[Ocon] I'm not afraid of anyone.
I don't care who it is.
I want to win.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 3] It's lights out,
and away we go!
[tense music plays]
[commentator 3] The two Alpines there,
Gasly and Esteban Ocon,
very, very close together!
[Peckett] Okay, Esteban.
Pierre now the car ahead.
[tense music continues]
[commentator 3] Ocon's gonna
try and make a move!
[commentator 2]
Whilst those two are squabbling,
there's concern on the pit wall
from Otmar.
[commentator 5] Ocon having another go.
[Gasly] Got a bit squeezed there.
[Loos] All right, buddy. Full focus.
Still a long way to go.
[Peckett] Okay, Esteban, let's box. Box.
[commentator 3] Esteban Ocon
coming in for an early pit stop.
[commentator 1]
That will cost him track position.
[Peckett] Okay, mate.
So currently, we're in P15.
[commentator 1] Gasly up to fourth. He's
having a superb race here at the moment.
[Loos] Gap to Sainz 1.6.
[commentator 3] Here comes Carlos Sainz
on Pierre Gasly.
[Loos] Sainz 0.9 behind.
Sainz a little bit closer now. 0.3.
Let's keep pushing.
I'm trying my best.
[Adami] Okay, try to overtake.
You can go. You can go.
[commentator 1] Carlos Sainz,
this time has got Pierre Gasly.
[Peckett] Okay, Esteban, push from here.
[commentator 3]
Esteban Ocon on Oscar Piastri.
He's gonna try and go the long way round.
And he makes the move around the outside.
[Peckett] Well done. Let's push.
[commentator 3] There goes Esteban Ocon
on Yuki Tsunoda.
[Peckett] Back in the points.
Let's push up.
[exciting music plays]
[commentator 3] Ocon currently tenth.
He really is flying at the moment.
[Peckett] Well done.
Hülkenberg four seconds in front.
Let's push.
[exciting music continues]
[music fades]
Whoa, whoa, fuck!
[tense music plays]
[Slade] You've got damage.
Right rear puncture.
-[Peckett] Safety car, Esteban.
-[Ocon] What for?
[Peckett] We've got Magnussen stopped.
[commentator 2] And they have
red-flagged the race.
That means a restart is coming.
[Loos] Okay, mate, so restarting.
And we expect a standing start again.
[Gasly] How many laps?
[Loos] Two laps all out.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 1] Pierre Gasly, P5.
Esteban Ocon, P10.
[Szafnauer] Both our cars are
in good point-scoring positions.
Great opportunity for us.
[Ocon] I'm gonna do everything I can
to get, uh, as many points as possible.
[Gasly] It's gonna be hectic.
I can either lose everything,
or potentially have a massive reward.
[Loos] Last car is on the grid.
[commentator 3] It's chaos!
And there's contact!
[tense music plays]
-Agh, fuck!
-What the fuck?
[deep breathing]
[Loos] Are you okay?
[Gasly] Oh my God.
[Peckett] Are you all right?
[tense music plays]
[Ocon] That's it.
Need extinguisher. Extinguisher fast.
[team member] What a fucking shit weekend.
[Szafnauer] Oh, that was terrible.
This is a fucking misery.
We gotta bounce back,
gotta do a better job.
[reporter 1] What happened
at the crash with Pierre?
[Ocon] Pierre basically
came from the gravel.
There was basically no room
for me to be on the right,
and, uh, we collided.
But was it just a careless rejoin?
I don't need to comment. Uh, I think
it is... it is quite, uh, quite obvious.
Everything was going extremely well
until that last red flag.
[reporter 2] And the crash?
How it came off?
I can't really believe what's happened,
uh, at the end of the race,
but, uh, yeah.
-I don't really wanna comment on it.
-Okay, thank you.
-[reporter 3] Can I ask you about...
-I'm... I'm sorry.
[whistles]
[reporter 4] Do you see it as equal blame
or does it not matter
because they both had a part to play?
You know, it was just chaos out there.
It's a shame that they came together.
As far as trying to blame
one or the other,
I don't think
that's the right thing to do.
[reporter 4] Thank you.
[Szafnauer] The crash was unfortunate
because we lost good points
with two laps to go.
But look at the circumstances.
Standing start restart.
Everybody's all over the place.
You can't predict that.
There's no finger pointing.
Let's just solve problems
so we get better.
[tense music plays]
[Buxton] Let's make
one thing crystal clear.
I think a crash like this is a disaster.
It's an absolute disaster.
And Otmar's style of management
doesn't necessarily come up to scratch.
Otmar's gotta
pull his drivers back in line,
And who knows?
Maybe all they need
is their heads knocking together.
Because division within the team
can poison the garage
and rip it apart at the seams.
[tense music continues]
[Famin in French]
It's extremely frustrating,
but I'm counting on Otmar to double down.
He is the one
who is responsible for the team
and who leads the team into races.
[in English] One more on this
and then we'll move on to something else.
Okay. Ready to go?
Keep the rib cage down.
[Ocon] Australia really
showed our weaknesses.
No one... No one is... is happy.
[man] Okay, we'll go for 60 seconds.
Try and keep that same position.
[Ocon exhales]
We haven't had
the best start of the season.
Um, you know,
we are not where we want to be.
[man] Thirty to go.
[Ocon] They decided to choose Pierre.
And in Formula 1,
you want to beat everyone.
You know, you need to be careful,
uh, with your teammate
once you are racing very close.
But, you know,
you want to score more points than him
at the end of the championship.
[man] You know, we only need to focus
on ourselves, really.
[Ocon] Yeah, exactly.
[man] At the end of the day,
it's just you in that car.
[commentator 1] It is
the grandest setting of them all.
Welcome to the Monaco Grand Prix.
-Well, hopefully this one's a bit better.
-Yeah, that'd be nice.
It's just stay out of trouble.
[notification alert chimes]
[reporter in French] How has what happened
at the end of the Grand Prix in Australia
impacted your momentum this season?
There was a lot of,
I'm sorry for saying this, amateurism,
which led to
a disappointing result for us.
It was mediocre, poor.
I told them it was the first
and last free pass of the season.
[In English] Were you surprised
that Laurent went public
in his criticisms of the team?
Well, I read it just like you did.
Um, so, uh, I...
I didn't have an idea beforehand.
Uh, he used words like "dilettantes"
and "amateurish"
to describe the team.
Well, you know, when we make mistakes
or when team members make mistakes,
we have to, uh, make sure we understand
the root cause of those mistakes.
Laurent did say
that the buck stops with you.
The team is your responsibility.
There was the inference within it that
your position
is under threat, effectively.
I've been doing this for 25 years
at a very senior level,
um, and, uh, know what it takes
to move a team from, say, last to fourth.
Um, so I... I have an understanding,
and, uh, you know, the plans are in place.
[Famin in French] So before Monaco,
we are clearly not competing
at the level we had hoped for
at the beginning of the year.
We're in sixth place.
And that's a real problem.
[crowd cheers]
[commentator 2 in English] High risk.
Peak adrenaline.
Nowhere on Earth moves a driver
like this place.
Welcome to Qualifying
for the Monaco Grand Prix.
It's the pole-position shoot-out
at the venue where starting up front
is more important than anywhere else.
Watching Pierre Gasly
with interest on the track at the moment.
He is no slouch around here.
[Loos] Okay, mate.
Middle sector very, very good.
Let's keep the speed up a bit.
[exciting music plays]
[Loos] So let's push, mate.
[exciting music continues]
[Gasly] Where are we
at the moment? Position?
[Loos] P5.
[Gasly] That was a decent lap.
[commentator 3] We focus here
on Esteban Ocon.
[Peckett] Let's make this lap count.
We are currently P6.
Pierre is P5.
Everything you've got. Let's push.
[Ocon] In Formula 1, the most important...
What we all want, as drivers, is to win.
You want to score
more points than your teammate.
Competition is definitely
something that motivates me.
[commentator 3] Ocon now picking up pace.
Grazing the wall almost on the exit.
[exciting music plays]
[Peckett] P3. Well done.
[team member] Yeah!
[Ocon] Well done, guys. Well done. Yes!
[Ocon laughs]
[commentator 5] That was
a bit of a special lap from Esteban Ocon.
[commentator 2] Ocon will start
in third place tomorrow.
[commentator 3] Solid drive from Gasly.
He'll start seventh on the grid.
[commentator 2] Esteban Ocon
outqualifying his teammate.
That was absolutely outstanding.
[woman] Well done!
It's a huge amount of work, you know,
to get to that moment,
and I am very pleased
to have built the weekend the way we did.
Yeah, it's a hell of a moment
for everyone,
and let's see what we can do tomorrow.
A good start and, hopefully,
you know, some fighting in front.
[man] Well done!
[Szafnauer] Thank you.
For Esteban, plan A is try to undercut
as many cars as possible.
Um, we need to push
and try to get some points.
[Szafnauer] I can sense
the pressure to deliver,
but both our cars are in good,
point-scoring positions on the grid.
I think we got a good chance
of getting both of 'em on the podium.
[man] Good to see you, man.
[Gasly] Yeah, okay.
-[woman in French] How are you, sweetie?
-[Gasly] I'm fine.
-How are you?
-[woman] Weird seeing you in that gear.
[Gasly] I'm just such a fan
of Esteban Ocon!
Apparently, he got third today.
But they showed me a strategy for tomorrow
where I can...
where basically, I help Esteban win.
[Buxton in English] Formula 1 history
has show us that when two teammates
become fixated on beating each other,
rather than everybody else,
it can do untold damage to the team.
[commentator 3] Here in Monaco,
one of the most iconic tracks
on the Formula 1 calendar,
it's round seven
in the Formula 1 World Championship.
[Peckett] Two minutes until fire-up.
[Loos] We've got some rain
about 30 minutes away, potentially.
[Ocon] I haven't
got on the podium this year,
so, uh, I need that feeling again
to prove, you know, I'm the best.
[Gasly] I don't care about Esteban.
I just wanna beat him the same way
I wanna beat all 18 other drivers.
[Peckett] Let's go, mate.
Stay focused and sharp.
[commentator 1] And we're racing
on the streets of Monaco!
[commentator 2] Aggressive defending
from Ocon on the inside!
[Peckett] This start so far
has been very good.
Sainz the car behind.
[tense music plays]
[Peckett] Gap to Sainz 1.2 seconds.
[tense music continues]
[Ocon] Yeah, I got hit.
It's crazy. I had nowhere to go there.
Tires feel very fragile at the moment.
[Peckett] Box, box.
[Loos] Esteban in.
[commentator 3] Ocon now pits
from third place.
[tense music continues]
[commentator 1] Gasly goes through
past his Alpine teammate,
goes up into third!
Esteban Ocon down
in fifth place at the moment.
[Peckett] Okay, we need
to push now, Esteban.
[commentator 1] Pierre Gasly
is absolutely charging.
[Loos] Pierre, P3.
Keep your nose clean, stay focused,
and there's some good points here.
Possible rain about 16 laps from now.
-[Gasly] I wanna go long.
-[Loos] Copy.
Box, box.
[Gasly] So give me rain tires.
[commentator 2] It looks like Alpine
are not giving Gasly wet-weather tires.
They're giving him dry tires.
That's a real surprise
given there is forecast for rain.
[Gasly] I don't get it.
[Loos] Copy that.
Really not much rain on the radar.
[Gasly] It better not increase.
[tense music plays]
[Loos] Some reports
of very light rain at turn three.
[Gasly] Yeah, I know. That's why I don't
understand why we put on dry tires.
[Gasly] It's raining a lot now.
Turn eight, there is water.
For fuck's sake.
[dramatic music plays]
[commentator 3] Look at the spray.
Absolutely treacherous.
[Ocon] Raining heavy now. I need to box.
[Peckett] Okay, Esteban.
Let's box for inters.
[Ocon] Okay, good.
I need rain tires.
[Loos] Box, box.
[commentator 2] Another pit stop
for Gasly.
This could have a massive impact
on his race.
Oh, if only he was given
the right tires earlier.
[Loos] So currently, you're P7.
[Peckett] Esteban, you've got this
under control. Keep it up.
Okay.
[dramatic music plays]
[music fades]
[commentator 3] Esteban Ocon
comes home to take third place.
[Ocon] Yes, guys! Yes!
[laughs]
-[Peckett] Well done.
-[Ocon] Oh my God!
[laughs] Woo! Yes!
[Loos] That's the checkered flag and P7.
[Gasly] What the fuck was that?
[Gasly] That decision to not give me
the right tires for the rain
was a mistake.
It cost me the third place.
Pretty painful, because this would've been
my first podium with Alpine.
You know, as a team,
we still got one car on the podium.
But on my side,
I just felt like we gave it away,
and I just felt,
yeah, very... bitter.
I want a shower, so I'm gonna leave.
Did you speak to Pierre?
-I haven't. Not yet.
-He's around here, perhaps...
[Szafnauer] I'll go grab him.
He won't be in the best of moods.
We need to just go through that with him.
[in French] Will we see you
on the podium next time?
[Gasly] I don't know.
-[Rossi] You're holding it.
-[Ocon] No, no, it's you!
[Patrick in English] If drivers
put their rivalry with each other
in front of the success of the team...
[in French] That's pissing me off a bit.
We could have reached the podium.
[in English]...that animosity
creates a lot of negativity
and a crack
that can rise to the top level,
creating a real breakdown within the team.
-[in French] I will dine with you tonight.
-That will be my pleasure.
-Well, bye. See you!
-See you soon.
[Gasly in English] Every weekend,
it's disappointment and frustration,
and I joined the team to
fight for podiums, to fight for...
Bring the team to the top,
be able to close the gap
to fight for wins at some point,
and, uh, since the start of the year,
I have been doing, like, two steps back.
I'm pissed off, but I'm just gonna show
that I'm the best driver in the team.
Let's get on with it.
-My contract is up for renewal.
-[man] Lewis, please come back.
[Hamilton] Car's slow, mate.
It's impossible to get close and pass.
When the car is terrible,
you can only do so much.
[Buxton] Will Lewis resign with Mercedes?
[Szafnauer] We're underperforming.
[Gasly] Something is not clicking.
-[Ocon] Otmar needs to find a solution.
-[Szafnauer] I sense the pressure.
[Elvis impersonator] Baby,
what's goin' on?
Las Vegas, baby!
[Leclerc] Oh fuck!
Fucking hell! What was that?
[closing theme music plays]