[producer] I'm gonna
ask you some questions.
[Vasseur] Okay, but I'm not
in the police station. [chuckles]
[producer] This is our first chat together
on the show. We're gonna start.
-Okay.
-[producer] Yeah.
Fred Vasseur, team principal, Ferrari.
[dramatic music plays]
[Buxton] Ferrari is more than
a brand. It's more than a car company.
For Italians, it's life.
There are two religions in Italy.
There's the Catholic Church,
and there's Ferrari.
[crowd cheers]
[dramatic music continues]
[reporter in Italian] Ferrari have
confirmed that they have appointed
Frédéric Vasseur
as their new team principal.
[mechanic 1] Jesus Christ.
[mechanic 2] Fuck's sake.
[male fan 1] He's never done this job.
What the heck did he come here to do?
[female fan] He doesn't
even speak Italian.
Exactly.
A team like Ferrari that is a family.
It's important.
[female fan] Exactly.
A top team like Ferrari can't afford
to make those kinds of mistakes
in front of the whole world.
[male fan 2] This guy has to make it work.
[male fan 3] The team principal before
was Binotto.
Let's hope that Vasseur
manages to be a little better.
[Buxton in English] The role of Ferrari
team principal is a poisoned chalice.
[clicks his tongue]
[Buxton] It's the most pressurized
position in world sport.
Does he know what he's let himself in for?
I have to be serious.
[producer] No, please don't be serious.
We wanted the real you.
[blows raspberry]
[laughs]
[engine revs]
[tense orchestral music plays]
[Buxton] Ferrari is passion and history
and elegance and glamour,
Italian style,
and speed.
The only team
that's taken part in every year
of the Formula 1 World Championship,
all the way back to 1950.
They are the most successful team
the sport has ever known.
[commentator 1] Michael Schumacher
takes his 85th Formula 1 win.
But they've not won a championship
in a decade and a half.
Ferrari, in 2022,
made countless mistakes,
handed away so many advantages.
-[Padros] Stay out, stay out.
-[Leclerc] Fuck, fuck!
No!
[commentator 2] For the third time
this season,
Charles Leclerc, when leading a race,
won't go on to finish it.
[Buxton] And that's something
that a new team boss
will need to change.
[Vasseur in French] I joined Ferrari
over the winter.
It all hit me like an enormous wave.
I didn't have time to anticipate it.
It was just there.
[Williams in English] Fred's
quite a surprising choice for Ferrari.
Ferrari would normally choose
a very serious individual.
Fred is a unique character.
I've known Fred for 25 years.
He's straightforward, no bullshit.
But he can also be a bit cheeky.
[producer in French] A bit higher.
Like that. And look at me.
Like that. [chuckles]
[in English] You couldn't have
a less Ferrari person running Ferrari.
And he's not even Italian.
[in Italian] Today,
I need to speak Italian to the press.
-Yes.
-[in French] So...
[in Italian] We can start.
[in English] In French...
[laughs]
Fred Vasseur was team boss
at Alfa Romeo for six seasons.
And it's a big step up
for Fred to move
from a back-of-the-grid team
to Ferrari.
But he's not
some wet-behind-the-ears greenhorn.
He has been involved in motorsport
for over three decades.
Half the grid
owe their careers to Fred Vasseur.
Ferrari wanted a new set of ideas,
a new direction,
and Fred represents that something new.
[in Italian] For the fans, it's important
to say something in Italian.
Forza Ferrari...
-Okay.
-This always.
[in English] At the end of each sentence,
"Forza Ferrari."
[in Italian] Yes. Very good.
Perfect.
[Vasseur] Forza Ferrari.
Forza Ferrari.
-[producer in English] How's your Italian?
-I won't speak Italian today.
-[producer] Okay.
-[laughs]
[tense music plays]
[Vasseur] I know the pressure
from the press and the media is on me.
It's something I have to learn
to work with.
[reporter] Fred, now, uh, I also
want to hear how is it going so far?
So far, it's intense. [chuckles]
As you can imagine.
But, uh, you can feel
the responsibility for the team.
It's a great honor,
but at the end of the day,
I think the most important
is to be successful.
That, uh, we will have to... to deliver.
[Vasseur] So far, it's not the best start
for the season, for sure,
and, uh, we made mistakes.
[Leclerc] No, no, no, no. Come on.
Guys, no power.
[commentator 2] And there's contact!
[Leclerc] That's it.
[Sainz] We're gonna crash.
[Adami] Yeah, copy.
Definitely the worst start
of... of a season ever.
Clearly, the objective of Ferrari
is to win.
You need to get results
if you want to survive.
[interviewer] Hello, Charles.
[Williams] Coming in and taking over
somebody else's team,
which Fred has effectively done...
That's been Mattia's team
for quite a while.
That's not an easy situation,
because this is not his car.
Fred is inheriting the team, the car,
and two incredibly competitive drivers
from his predecessor.
[Sainz] My objective
is to be world champion.
And your teammate is one more of those
who you want to beat.
[Leclerc] I know that he's my teammate,
but I also know I want to beat him
as much as he wants to beat me.
I just want to win and beat everyone.
It won't be, uh, an easy season for me.
[dramatic orchestral music plays]
[commentator 1] Welcome to one
of the great theaters of motor racing,
the 2023 Italian Grand Prix.
[man] Welcome to the best country
around the world.
Monza.
Bellissimo.
[operatic music plays]
[commentator 3] The passionate tifosi
absolutely desperate
to see Ferrari
back at the front of the field.
[operatic music continues]
[Buxton] Monza is the home of the tifosi.
Fred knows what the expectations are,
and bare minimum is winning races.
Italy expects.
The tifosi expects.
The board, crucially, expects.
[radio host in Italian] From a performance
point of view,
Ferrari could do good things
here in Monza.
[radio host continues speaking Italian]
Coming into Monza,
Ferrari currently find themselves fourth,
and it's definitely not
where the tifosi would expect them to be.
We want to do a better job
with better results.
[Vasseur in French] Now we're going
to Monza at a difficult time
because Ferrari wants to win again,
and it's been a while since we have.
We have a bit of hope
because Monza is a fast race
and that suits our car better,
but we're still going into the unknown.
There will be a lot of expectations
from the tifosi, the sponsors,
and Ferrari in general.
It's another pressure for us.
[crowd shouts]
[fans shouting in Italian]
[Leclerc in English] It's been
a very difficult season.
There's a lot of work to do
in order to catch up.
[crowd shout]
And we've got a whole nation behind us.
[Sainz] It would mean everything
to win at Monza.
-Grazie.
As a Ferrari driver, it's the race that
you wanna perform at your highest level
In front of the tifosi.
-[engine roars]
-[door slams]
[crowd shout]
[Sainz] Grazie.
[shouting continues]
[Reyes in Spanish] Holy mother, Carlos,
what an experience.
They're all tifosi.
I feel like crying, Carlos.
They all say hi to you
with such emotion. It's incredible.
Are you okay? Relaxed?
Hmm.
[rock music plays]
[music fades]
[reporter in italian] Here he is,
Frédéric Vasseur.
-Hi, Fred.
-[Vasseur] Good evening.
[in English] We just want to know which
kind of feelings did you have this morning
coming here at the track,
seeing all the red tifosi around
cheering for you.
I wanted to avoid
to have an extra pressure on the team,
but I think that we have to stay calm
and focus on what we are doing,
not to overshoot any expectation
or something like this.
There's always hope at Monza
of a Ferrari victory,
but in 2023, Red Bull have won
every single grand prix.
Where is the TV pen?
I don't know.
Paul, where are we going now?
[Paul] Going back in,
then we'll go up to the paddock.
-I thought Fred was just following me.
-[all laugh]
[Vasseur] We are following each other.
[Buxton] And so the question now
is how do you beat Red Bull?
And you then have Mercedes, who are second
in the Constructors Championship,
doing... [chuckles]
...so much better than Ferrari.
That's massive pressure on Fred.
[commentator 1] It's Monza.
It's Qualifying at the home of Ferrari.
The grandstands are packed with fans
expectant of a Ferrari pole.
[tense music plays]
[Padros] And we need to go. We need to go.
[Leclerc] Copy that.
[exciting music plays]
[Leclerc] I cannot go faster.
[Padros] Understood. Mode push.
[exciting music continues]
[Padros] Go.
[commentator 2] Pole for Charles Leclerc!
But can he hang onto it?
[Lambiase] Leclerc currently P1.
You're quite close.
[Verstappen] All good.
[exciting music plays]
[commentator 2] Verstappen
crosses the line! He's on pole!
[in Italian] It's not over yet!
[exciting music plays]
[Sainz in English] I think
I can go quicker.
[in Italian] Okay, one more lap.
[exciting music continues]
[in Spanish] Let's go, Carlos!
[in Italian] Carlos, let's go!
[in Spanish] Let's go! Let's go!
[exciting music continues]
[Sainz in English] Tell me we have it.
Tell me we have it.
-[Adami] Yes, P1.
-[Sainz in Spanish] Let's go!
[cheering]
[triumphant music plays]
-[Adami in English] Enjoy your pole.
-[Sainz] Okay, okay, let me enjoy a bit.
[triumphant music continues]
[Lambiase] Wowzers. Sainz has
pipped you by one hundredth.
That was a hell of a lap.
[Verstappen] They are quick over a lap,
but let's wait and see tomorrow.
[commentator 2] Frédéric Vasseur
can smile for today.
Tomorrow could well be a different story.
[Sainz] By far, the best pole position
of my career.
Seeing everyone getting so excited
and... and cheering my name was
the best feeling
that you can get as a driver.
I just hope that I am able
to fight for that win.
Time to do the job. [chuckles]
[tense music plays]
[commentator 3] The banner is unfurled.
The Scuderia expect
and the tifosi demand a performance.
[Lambiase] Radio check.
-[Verstappen] Yep, radio check.
-[Lambiase] Radio is good.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 1] Pérez is P5.
Mercedes have Russell, P4.
In front of him, Leclerc, P3.
Verstappen, P2.
And Carlos Sainz has pole position
for Ferrari in Monza.
[Sainz] Red Bull are right behind me.
It's, uh, quite a lot of pressure.
I think it's gonna be a tight fight.
[Buxton] If you don't
convert pole into the win,
it... it is the biggest failure.
[Leclerc] You can hear,
"Forza Ferrari! Forza ragazzi!"
These are sentences that motivate you.
It's our duty to give our best
in order to win.
[tense music plays]
[Bird] Last car
joining the back of the grid now.
[tense music continues]
[Adami] All set and focus on the lights.
[commentary in Italian] Meanwhile,
we are on Carlos Sainz, in pole position...
He was unbelievable yesterday.
He can make it, but...
[man 1] Max is going to be crushed today.
-[man 2] Come on. Let Ferrari fucking win.
-[man 3] Stay calm.
[commentary] So here we are finally.
The traffic lights.
[fan] Come on!
[commentator 1 in English]
We're racing in Monza!
[tense music plays]
[commentator 2] Carlos Sainz
gets out of the chicane and into the lead.
[crowd cheers]
[in Italian] Yes, yes!
Come on, come on, come on!
[tense music continues]
[Adami in English] Max 0.5 behind.
Max, 0.9 behind.
[Lambiase] Gap ahead, 1.1.
Okay.
[Adami] We have a lot of top speed.
That's good.
-[Sainz] It's quicker?
-[Adami] We are faster everywhere.
[Verstappen] He's already
sliding a bit, so all good.
[Lambiase] Understood, Max.
Be sensible for the moment.
[commentator 4] Right now, Carlos Sainz
is about to come under a lot of pressure
down the pit straight.
[Lambiase] 0.4 behind.
[commentator 2] Max Verstappen
gets alongside Carlos Sainz
and then runs out of room.
[Verstappen] That was naughty.
[exciting music plays]
[Lambiase] Bide your time.
It's a matter of time.
[exciting music continues]
[commentator 2] Down the main straight
we go once again.
Carlos Sainz leads.
[Lambiase] He's struggling
with the rear, Max, a lot.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 2] Carlos Sainz locks up.
[Sainz] Fuck!
[Lambiase] Hit the overtake
if you want to.
[tense music continues]
No, no, no, no, no!
[commentator 2] Verstappen's
on the inside. Verstappen is ahead!
[groaning]
[Sainz] Fucking hell.
[commentator 1] Sainz has lost
his pole advantage.
Ferrari, now second and third.
[Padros] Gap to Pérez behind, 0.8.
He is with DRS.
[Bird] Yeah, no DRS for Leclerc.
You got him.
[in Italian] Bloody hell, he's close.
[tense music plays]
[Bird in English]
Keep pushing on. Push on.
[tense music continues]
[Leclerc] No, come on.
[commentator 2] One Ferrari dispatched,
another Ferrari to go.
[Sainz] He's trying to pass me
around the outside of the car.
[Pérez] He's not leaving any room, man.
Come on!
We cannot race like this.
[Bird] You're faster.
You're gonna get him. See him off.
[dramatic music plays]
[Adami] Checo, 0.1 behind with DRS.
[Sainz] Tires are nearly finished.
[dramatic music continues]
[commentator 2] Pérez got his man!
As Carlos Sainz locks up,
Sergio Pérez finally gets second place.
[Leclerc] Carlos is struggling a bit
with the rears.
[Padros] No risk, no risk.
[Adami] Charles behind with DRS.
-[Padros] We need to be careful.
-What?
I have to make the corner.
[tense music builds]
[Sainz] I think we both
feel like the corner.
[commentator 1] Charles Leclerc moves up
into the podium places
but locks up in doing so.
[Adami] Remember, no risk to both cars.
[exciting music plays]
[commentator 2] Sainz locks up!
And somehow they avoid contact.
Sainz is back ahead of Charles Leclerc.
That could have been nasty.
[exciting music continues]
[Padros] Be careful. This is the last lap.
No race to the end. No risk.
[exciting music continues]
[commentator 2] Oh, and Charles Leclerc
locks up,
goes straight on into the runoff area.
[shouting]
[commentator 2] Sainz is back ahead.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 3] That could've been
horrendous for Ferrari.
So easily could have gone
into the back of his teammate.
It's a one-two finish for Red Bull.
And Carlos Sainz comes home
by a tenth of a second
to beat his teammate, Charles Leclerc,
and take that final podium place.
[in Italian] They're not a team anymore.
They're not a cohesive team.
Today we risked not getting any points.
They could have gone out, both of them.
[Williams in English] I can't tell you
the pain a team principal will be feeling
watching your two drivers
battle on the track.
There is so much risk involved.
They could've taken each other out.
That's when the TP needs to step in
and tell their drivers,
"Dial it down a bit."
There's just too much at stake.
[Vasseur] It was not a good result
at all for us.
Passion around the team,
the expectation is always very high
and difficult to manage.
[man on radio in Italian]
Team Principal Frédéric Vasseur,
a man about whom there'd been many doubts.
Should we trust him?
[fan 1] I would have kept Binotto.
Facts are facts.
The reality is that we are losing.
[fan 2] We have hit rock bottom.
This is a bad year.
[fan 3] Jesus Christ.
[fan 4] We have to ask Vasseur
why the car is slow, eh?
But above all,
why is Verstappen going so strong?
[fan 5] His car is better.
[fan 4] Fucking hell.
-[Leclerc in English] All good?
-So far. Before the lunch, all good.
-[Vasseur laughs]
-Before they catch up.
[Vasseur chuckles]
[Vasseur in French] Come on.
What did you do this morning?
[Vasseur in English] How is the life?
Your life?
-[Sainz] My life in general?
-Yeah.
Still single?
Anyway, changing subject...
[laughter]
[Sainz] How is the team?
I think, in terms of mood,
it's, uh, much better.
[Vasseur in French] We have to behave
as a team in both the good and bad times.
And I think the team
needs to stick together.
We often forget what "team" means,
because it's very important.
[in English] We have to continue to push
in this direction. We are not far away.
I think we have to put everything together
to try to improve the situation
to work on every single pillar
of the performance.
We are all trying to do better,
you know, than what we maybe...
Probably that we are trying
to overshoot the railings.
[Sainz] That's what I mean.
[Vasseur] In Monza,
the fight on track between you,
it's too much.
We can't race like this.
Yeah, maybe that
was a little bit over-the-top.
[Sainz] Yeah.
[Vasseur] As a team perspective,
we need to work together to win.
Yeah.
We have to improve
and to put everything together
from Friday to Sunday.
[Leclerc] Yep.
[Sainz] It will be a lot better.
We couldn't do it in Monza.
Let's try and do it in Singapore, no?
[Vasseur] Let's push.
Let's fucking push.
[commentator 1] We're 85 miles
north of the equator.
Welcome to the Singapore Grand Prix.
Stand by for a hot one.
It feels like a sauna.
[fan 1] Carlos, you're so hot!
-[screaming]
-[fan 2] Carlos!
It's fucking hot.
It's cold. [laughs]
The Singapore Grand Prix is brutal.
It is a high-speed street circuit.
A race held at night
in stifling heat.
These aren't see-through, are they?
[Magnussen laughs]
Ferrari led at Monza. At home.
And didn't bring the win.
This year is
substantially worse than last.
There's a lot to prove in Singapore.
[commentator 3] We are all set for one
of the most important qualifying sessions
of the season
as we set the grid
for the Singapore Grand Prix
in very, very high humidity.
[tense music plays]
[Bird] Okay, fire up.
[tense music continues]
Let's make sure we are not near the back.
[Dudley] So it will be straight out.
[Lambiase] We need to get going, Max.
[tense music continues]
[commentator 3] Sergio Pérez
on his flying lap.
[Bird] Okay, keep on pushing on. Push on.
[Pérez] Copy.
[tense music continues]
[Bird] That looked good.
[Pérez groans]
[Pérez] For fuck's sake.
-[Bird] Okay, what happened?
-[Pérez] I went over the curb.
[Bird] That's got us P13, I'm afraid.
[Pérez] Fuck this shit!
[commentator 1] A rare mistake
by one of the Red Bulls.
Will Verstappen fare better?
[Lambiase] Keep pushing.
Okay, Max, so that was excellent.
Continue to keep positive.
[Verstappen] All good.
[tense music plays]
[Lambiase] Everything okay?
[Verstappen] Locked up again
in this shit corner.
Fuck's sake. Shit balance.
[tense music continues]
[Verstappen] The car is really bad.
Fucking shocking.
Absolutely shocking experience.
[commentator 1] At this rate,
neither Red Bull will make the top ten.
Here comes Charles Leclerc.
This could be
a rare opportunity for Ferrari.
[Padros] Push first corner.
[Leclerc] Yeah, copy that.
[tense music plays]
[Padros] Overall, quite a good job.
[commentator 2] Can Charles Leclerc
make it a 21st pole in Formula 1?
[Padros] You were fastest.
[cheering]
[commentator 3] George Russell
is right in the hunt here.
[Dudley] Okay. Nice work.
[tense music plays]
[Dudley] This looks solid.
[tense music continues]
[commentator 2] Can Mercedes
now seize the initiative?
[Dudley] Still doing a good job.
[Russell] Copy.
[tense music continues]
[commentator 3] It's a front row
for Mercedes!
Russell beats Charles Leclerc.
[Adami] Russell, currently P1.
Verstappen and Pérez are out.
[exciting music plays]
[Adami] Good job.
[exciting music continues]
[commentator 2] Sainz crosses the line!
-[Sainz] Tell me we have it.
-[Adami] We have it.
-[Sainz] We have it?
-[Adami] Yes!
[cheering]
[Adami] That was super close, yeah?
[commentator 2] Two weeks ago, Ferrari
had pole, couldn't convert it into a win.
Can Ferrari do it?
[Sainz] Let's do it tomorrow, guys.
Tomorrow.
[in Spanish] Come on.
[tense music plays]
[in English] We're out of position,
but we're just gonna give it everything.
And, you know, try something different,
you might get something different.
[commentator 1] Good news for Ferrari.
Red Bull are P11 and P13.
But Russell's Mercedes is P2.
His teammate, Hamilton, not far behind.
[Vasseur] I need to get results.
And the most important today
is for us to win.
[Sainz] It's about the mentality
during the race.
Putting your head down, not overreacting.
That gives you the opportunity
to fight for wins.
[commentator 3] Good launch
off the line for Leclerc,
who's trying to take second place.
[Dudley] Leclerc ahead.
[commentator 2] Ferrari, one, two,
going into the first corner.
[exciting music plays]
[Padros] Good job.
Gap to Sainz in front, 1.2.
[Leclerc] Pace is really good.
[exciting music continues]
[commentator 2] And Charles Leclerc
has Carlos Sainz in his sights.
[Adami] Charles, 0.7 behind.
[commentator 4] The worst thing Ferrari
could do is start racing each other.
[Lambiase] Leader is Sainz. Leclerc, P2.
Hopefully, we can reel these cars in.
[commentator 1] Verstappen's
made up a couple of places.
[Lambiase] Gap to leader, 9.7.
[commentator 1] Verstappen will go like
crazy to try and catch the Ferraris.
He's moved up into eighth place.
[tense music plays]
[Lambiase] Push this lap.
Close up the gap to Ocon.
[Padros] So gap to Sainz in front, 1.2.
Target, three.
[Leclerc] Then I'm at risk.
[commentator 1] Ferrari
are asking Charles Leclerc
to slow down
to help his teammate, Carlos Sainz.
[Padros] Target gap to Sainz.
We need three seconds.
At the moment, it's 1.0.
[tense music plays]
[Dudley] George, we expect the Ferraris
to open up a three-second gap
between themselves.
They'll start pushing you back.
[Russell] Is that what they've been told?
[Dudley] Yeah, it looks like
they're gonna sacrifice Leclerc.
[Padros] So gap to Sainz in front, 1.2.
Target, three.
Gap to Sainz, target three.
[Leclerc] I'd really love
to win this grand prix,
but I know that the race
is not about me this time.
I just have to help Carlos get the win.
Yeah, copy. I'll try to slow down.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 3]
Ferrari backing the pack up.
[commentator 4] He's gotta go as slow
as possible, but not be overtaken.
[Padros] So gap to Sainz in front, 3.1.
[Leclerc] Yeah, copy that.
[Padros] Really good job.
Continue like this.
[Adami] What you are doing is good.
[Sainz] I could go forever at this pace.
[tense music continues]
[commentator 1]
Carlos Sainz is flying ahead.
[Lambiase] Sainz, gap 13.4.
[commentator 2] Down at Red Bull, they
need to try and do something different
to win this race.
-[Jego] You okay?
-[Sargeant] Yeah, front gone.
[Jego] You have the wing under the car,
so watch out. Box, box. Slow in.
[Adami] Sargeant is coming to the pits
with the front wing on the ground,
so watch for that, please.
[Sainz] Okay.
[commentator 4] Could be a safety car.
A lot of debris on the track.
[Adami] Box, Carlos. Box.
[commentator 1]
Ferrari have most to lose in this,
but they are out in the pit lane
for Sainz.
[commentator 4] That might be
the first jeopardy for Ferrari.
[commentator 2] And Charles Leclerc
is coming in.
They are double stacking at Ferrari.
[dramatic music plays]
[commentator 2] They've had to hold.
[Leclerc] What happened there?
[Padros] We had to hold you for traffic.
[dramatic music continues]
[Lambiase] Max, everyone pitted
apart from yourself, Checo, and Bottas.
[Adami] Try to get clear
of Verstappen, coming through.
[commentator 3] Can they get
Carlos Sainz out ahead of Verstappen?
[commentator 2] Charles Leclerc down
in sixth after losing four places.
That could be catastrophic.
Verstappen will be desperate
to get past that Ferrari.
[Adami] Safety car in this lap.
Max behind you.
[Lambiase] Max, keep the pressure on.
Safety car in pit lane.
[commentator 3] Can Sainz hold on?
[Adami] Verstappen, one second behind.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 2] Max Verstappen
now under pressure from George Russell.
[Verstappen] Tires are so dead.
It's like driving on ice.
[Lambiase] Understood, Max.
Keep at it. Maybe one more lap.
We are looking at our options.
[tense music plays]
[Dudley] Nice job, mate.
[commentator 1] Max Verstappen
losing another place.
And the Red Bull's
under big, big pressure.
[commentator 2] The other cars around them
have made their pit stop.
That might have cost Red Bull dear
in this race.
[tense music plays]
[Padros] Gap to Russell behind, 2.8.
[tense music continues]
[Dudley] Leclerc ahead, 2.3.
[commentator 2]
Leclerc's looking in his mirrors,
and he'll probably be able to see
quite nicely now
George Russell coming at him
in the Mercedes.
[Padros] Gap to Russell behind, 1.4.
And Russell with DRS.
[Dudley] Gap ahead, 1.1.
[tense music continues]
[commentator 1]
Russell is ahead of Leclerc.
He has a chance to win this race.
[Adami] Russell passed Charles.
Russell is 5.7 behind.
-Laps?
-[Dudley] Two remaining.
[Sainz] My tires are finished.
[commentator 1] At this pace,
Russell will overtake.
[Dudley] You're doing really good.
[Adami] Last lap.
[commentator 2] Carlos Sainz
has just under three miles to go
to try and win out in Singapore.
[Dudley] Overtake, final lap.
I'll leave you to this.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 2] Into the barrier
goes Russell!
[Russell] Fuck!
[Russell groans]
[Adami] Russell in the wall at turn ten.
Head down to the end.
[commentator 2]
Ferrari have controlled this race.
And Carlos Sainz, who started on pole
and didn't get the win in Monza,
does it tonight in Singapore.
Come on!
[commentator 2] Carlos Sainz
wins the Singapore Grand Prix.
[upbeat music plays]
[Adami] P1, baby.
[Sainz in Spanish] Come on! Come on, Fred.
[Vasseur] Congratulations, Carlos.
You made a good job.
[Adami] What a smart race. You nailed it.
[Sainz] This is my first smooth operation
in Ferrari.
-♪ Smooth operator ♪
-[Adami] ♪ Smooth operator ♪
[Sainz] We won Singapore, my friend.
-Cry. I'm gonna cry. [laughs]
-[Adami] What a legend.
[Sainz] That was perfect, guys. Come on!
[Sainz laughs]
[Sainz] This is the best feeling
that I've had as a racing driver
because, this year, the chances
of winning a race were incredibly slim.
[Adami] In the pit lane, P1.
-[Sainz] Say it again.
-[Adami] In the pit lane, and P1.
[Sainz] Again, again. P1, P1.
[Adami chuckles]
[Sainz] But we put together
the perfect plan, and we nailed it.
[Padros] P4.
[Leclerc in Italian]
Very well done, Carlos.
[Leclerc in English] It's frustrating.
I want to win, but at the same time,
the best thing I can do as a driver
is to try and help us be a better team.
[cheering]
I think Fred's really modified
the mindset within the team for better.
[Leclerc] Well done, mate.
[Sainz] Both Charles and I
are more united than ever.
We've realized
we can put some pressure on Red Bull
if we work together.
Fred managed to keep the team motivated
after a difficult start,
and score much better results
thanks to his leadership.
[commentator 3] Ferrari have ended
Red Bull's run
of 15 consecutive grand prix wins.
[Vasseur in French]
A victory is always like
a breath of fresh air.
It was a relief for me
and for everyone downstairs.
It's the best thing we can have
in a hard season.
For the team, it's a success
because of the race, of course,
but it's also a success
in terms of collaboration.
I was very proud of the result.
[Buxton in English] Fred's done what no
other boss has been able to do this year.
Beat Red Bull.
He has that distinct and unique honor.
[cheering]
[man on radio in Italian] Who would
have thought it, guys? A Ferrari victory.
Sainz wins the Singapore race!
Not only impeccable. Exceptional!
I have a lot of faith in Vasseur.
-[fan 1] He can bring back...
-[fan 2] Ferrari.
-[fan 1] Where it deserves to be.
-[fan 2] Exactly.
[fan 3] Ferrari is fighting.
That is, if Ferrari wins.
[fan 4] Everyone is happy.
-[fan 5] Always "forza Ferrari."
-[fan 6] Always.
I'm back.
Fuck.
[Horner] Oh shit.
It's game over.
[Verstappen] Get ready.
[Buxton] It's on Liam to prove
he deserves the seat.
He's probably shitting himself.
[commentator 2] Yuki Tsunoda
and Liam Lawson are going wheel to wheel.
[Tsunoda] Shit! Liam is so aggressive.
[Buxton] They now have three drivers
for two seats.
[commentator 3] Welcome
to the season finale.
[Buxton] There's a huge amount
to play for.
[Wolff] We gotta beat the Ferraris.
[Vowles] It comes down to one last round.
[commentator 3] We have reached
the concluding chapter.
Game on.
[closing theme music plays]
[music stops]