[Walsh] Hope isn't a strategy.
We've gone backwards.
The brand cries out for more performance.
I mean, we did go backwards last year.
No denying.
[Stallard] Okay, Daniel. That's P17.
Not the race we wanted, to be honest.
[Ricciardo groans]
[tense music plays]
[commentator 1] Lando Norris
really wrestling that McLaren.
[Joseph] P13.
[Norris] No one's gonna like
being where we are, so far back.
In Formula 1, if you're not
moving forwards, you're going backwards.
And... And all the headlines
became driver related.
It was interesting though.
There was a lot of discussion
that it was purely drivers.
What was really going on there?
[tense music continues]
Daniel Ricciardo has been axed by McLaren.
[reporter] He is set to be replaced
by 21-year-old young gun Oscar Piastri.
[tense music continues]
-[Walsh] We knew we had to make changes.
-Yeah.
But the important thing is,
having made those changes,
this season,
we've gotta show real progress.
Uh, first of all, we all feel
the pressure. We have some fixing to do.
But I've got
a lot of confidence in this team.
I think we need to give them
some... some time.
Things don't happen overnight.
It's got to work.
[wheel guns whirring]
[engine revs]
[tense music fades]
[Norris] I want the rice cakes.
Then can I have some water?
Wow.
Season six.
All right.
It's gonna be a... a fun year.
[producer] That was terrible. One more.
[Norris laughs and sighs]
[producer] Did you break it?
[funky music plays]
[Brown] See you later. Cheers.
Launch days are always fun.
And long.
[man] And long.
[Norris] Every season you start,
you get excited.
You're like, "Maybe this is the year
that we can turn things around,
and I can be in that position where
I'm standing on the podium more often
and fighting against Ferrari and Red Bull,
fighting against Mercedes."
I'm excited to see how things go.
We've had a lot of changes
within the team.
[funky music continues]
[music fades]
[woman 1] Can you go in the side door?
[Norris] Oscar Piastri.
Uh, another Aussie.
He's probably got one of the best CVs
out of any young driver
almost ever coming into Formula 1.
For a day-one car launch,
6 a.m. call time,
I'll forgive a couple of minutes late
because that's quite brutal, I appreciate.
-[Piastri] Morning.
-[woman 2] Morning.
Right, we're just in here.
[Piastri] Has Lando rocked up yet or...
[woman 1] He has, yeah.
And he did make a point that he beat you.
Arrived before you.
[both laugh]
-[man] Bienvenido.
-[woman 1] Morning.
[Brown] What's going on?
Glad you could join us.
[Piastri] Sorry I'm late.
[laughter]
[Norris] I'm gonna be the veteran.
I'm the old guy. He's the young guy.
It's the first time in my career
I've kind of had that sort of pressure.
...in F1 with McLaren.
Um, I've been building up to it,
and like you said...
Oscar's quite tall, huh?
Your apprentice.
He doesn't look tall, but he is tall.
...so it's been really good.
Everyone's been really welcoming.
[Norris] He's only, like, 15.
Where do you want us?
We have a new driver lineup this year.
Super excited to have Oscar.
Uh, 22 years old.
Uh, very mature, very smart, very fast.
Oh, hello.
And, uh, I'm excited to see
he and Lando, uh, racing each other hard
and pushing our team forward.
To be an F1 driver,
it's, uh, a very exciting prospect,
and, you know, definitely pinching myself
because it's something
I couldn't have dreamed of,
uh, even a couple of years ago.
[Stella] Welcome
to the private team reveal of our car.
Right. Show us the MCL60, please.
[Buxton] Coming into 2023,
Zak has everything he wants.
From a driver perspective,
he has two young future world champions
at his team.
But the worry is he doesn't have the car.
[applause]
[Brown] Hello.
I love the offseason.
Uh, it's a great-looking car.
Um, we still have work to do,
as... as we know,
so as much as I'd like to sit here and go,
"This is the championship contender,"
we're, uh, still a little bit
aways from that.
We have some concerns over our race car,
especially some of the data we're seeing.
We know we're not where we want to be
and we've missed some of our targets,
so I am concerned
coming into the start of the year,
but we'll take some time to fix that.
Time to get the show on the road
in Bahrain.
Let's go racing.
[applause]
Car looks bitchin'.
McLaren cannot recover this
in the short-term.
It's going to take time.
It's going to take months.
[Norris] The floor's the same
as last year, isn't it?
That's bigger. That's about
all I can see that's different.
Yeah.
[Buxton] The question mark for Zak is
how are you gonna keep
two ambitious drivers loyal and committed
when you're launching a car
and you're telling everyone,
"We're not going to be competitive until
at least halfway through the season"?
[applause]
[Norris laughs]
[woman] Were you happy with the launch?
[Norris] If we can do more than three laps
in a row, we've made a step forward.
-[laughs]
-[Norris] That was a joke. I'm joking.
I remember my first car launch.
-Been there, done that.
-Yeah.
Cut to Bahrain.
[tense music plays]
Starting your F1 career, it's exciting.
It's very nerve-wracking as well.
But it's something you've dreamed of
since you were a little kid.
It all comes down to... to that moment.
[Stallard] 30 seconds to go.
-[García] And radio check, Lando.
-Yeah, all good.
Going into my first race of the year,
there's a lot of pressure on.
Before you know it, you're on the grid.
[commentator 1] Green flag at the back
means that it is finally time.
[Norris] Hard racing, the lights
are coming on, the revs coming up.
[tense music builds]
And you're like, "Shit. This is real."
[commentator 2] It's lights out
and away we go!
[exciting music plays]
[Norris] What's wrong with my car?
[Joseph] Lando, we are
managing an issue. Box now, box now.
[commentator 3] Lando's got
an engine problem.
[dramatic music plays]
[commentator 1] Oscar Piastri
trying to score points on debut.
[Piastri] I've lost the gearbox.
[Stallard] Copy.
Oscar, we'll box this lap
and swap the steering wheel.
[tense music plays]
[Piastri] I've still got nothing.
[commentator 4] He's shaking his head.
What a start.
What a miserable first grand prix
for Oscar Piastri.
[Norris] Fucking hell.
[Joseph] Box this lap.
[commentator 1] Lando Norris
is really struggling.
[commentator 4] He's coming into the pits
for the fifth time!
[Joseph] This will be a slow stop.
Twenty-five to 30 seconds.
[Norris] Whoa.
[commentator 1] Max Verstappen dominates
the Bahrain Grand Prix
to lead home a Red Bull one-two,
and they will take some beating this year.
[commentator 4] Norris comes home in 17th.
And Piastri doesn't even finish
his debut race.
I do one little thing. I under rotate.
Fucking corner, giving up.
Knife-edge.
Like, it's... it's still...
As soon as I do one thing wrong,
it's just garbage.
I think every team goes
into every new season filled with hope.
And if your car is not
where you want it to be...
your heart just sinks.
'Cause you know it's going to be
the hardest of years.
[Brown] There's Lando.
And? Same as last year?
Similar limitations, basically.
Yeah.
Similar issues. Similar problems.
[Brown] All right.
We'll keep pushing.
At every single point
in your career as a driver,
you think,
"I need this year to go really well."
You don't feel like
you ever have a year to burn.
There's never a point in time
as a driver where you're thinking,
"Oh, no problem."
Like, "I'll be happy
to wait the rest of the season,
or until next year,
or a few more months for this to go well."
You need a good car now.
I might just walk into Red Bull
and steal their car.
-[man] Yeah? Okay.
-[Norris] Just steal their front wing.
-[man] They won't care, will they?
-[Norris] Pick it up, walk straight out.
Is it too soon to call it a crisis?
I know we're far from where we wanna be.
Um, but we have a very clear plan,
uh, what we need and want to achieve.
[Norris] Guys, something's not right
with the front end.
I got too much understeer.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 2] The two McLarens,
last in the Constructors Championship,
and not doing much tonight
to get themselves
off the bottom of the table, it seems.
[commentator 1] It's a real shame
for Lando Norris,
a phenomenally talented driver.
[Buxton] It's been clear for a long time
that Lando Norris
is the focal point of this team.
That he's their future.
But when you consider how poor
the car is that he's been given,
how long until he tries to find a way out?
[Horner] Lando's one of the most
talented drivers on the grid.
In the right car, he would be
a winning driver. No doubt of that.
Can his career take another year
of being in the doldrums?
A driver's career has
a finite amount of time to it,
and he needs to make the right decisions
for him at the end of the day.
We'd certainly be interested in him.
If he's delivering,
he's not gonna be short of choices.
He's gotta make sure
he makes the right choice.
[upbeat music plays]
Yeah, it's huge, huh?
How cool is that?
[music stops]
-[Brown] How are you?
-Good.
-Good luck.
-Thank you.
What's going on?
Coming into Miami, I think Zak
has every reason to be worried.
Because those clamors
for Lando Norris's signature
are only going to get louder.
[Williams] People in F1
love to see other teams' weaknesses.
If team principals see the cracks
and they think,
"Lando Norris might be available,"
you know, his head might be turned
by a phone call from Christian Horner.
And why wouldn't it be?
[Horner] I admire
Lando's loyalty to McLaren,
but, at some point, that will wear thin.
I think he would fit
in our environment longer term.
Uh, he and Max have a good respect
and good relationship together.
So you could see that being
a combination that could work.
[both laugh]
[reporter] Zak, great to see you.
Thanks for joining us.
[Brown] Good to be here.
[reporter] What's all this talk about
having to say, "Lando is with us to stay"?
Doesn't that seem too early?
Yeah, it's very early.
But, you know, people get
asked a question and, uh, speculate.
You have a bad two races,
and, "Oh my God.
He's off to another team."
A lot of times in this sport,
people will put certain rumors out
to try and, uh,
put fractures into relationships
to destabilize, uh, teams
and... and drivers.
-Thank you very much, Zak.
-You're welcome. See you later. Cheers.
I just wanna make sure Lando stays focused
and that we block out all the nonsense
that, uh, some of our competitors
like to create.
[woman] I think this will be quite quick.
The first order of business is obviously
it's not as bad as it looks
after the first races.
I think that's quite important.
As a team,
we wanna improve the performance.
-We know we're not where we need to be.
-Yeah.
And I think that's probably as deep
a level as you need to get into it.
The only other thing to flag
is on Lando's contract.
So Zak got asked specifically outright
by Sky if there was any exit clauses,
to which we said no.
I'm probably dead
by the time your contract is up.
[woman] Yeah. Just avoid it.
Um, just anything that you can say again
which is just... cementing
that, as a team, we're knuckling down.
We're not listening to any noise
going on in the media.
-We're just focused on our journey.
-Contract or not, we're all on a mission.
That's it.
Um, any other questions
or concerns from your side?
[both drivers] No.
[woman] Zak, do you have anything else
you want to add just from your side?
-No.
-[woman] Cool. Let's have a good one.
[Piastri] Yeah.
[woman] Are you gonna be
in your room, Lando?
I shall be, yeah.
[Norris] At times I would love to know
what it's like
to be in other people's positions.
I think, like, "Hmm."
"What would happen if I went here?"
Or, "What if I went there?"
I guess I think of those things.
Who wouldn't think of those?
Every driver has conversations
with as many people as they can
to give themselves options.
I should be in a better car, but I'm not.
Things are always shit, you know.
It's rare you get one driver that sticks
with the same team their whole career.
If you were a betting man, would you say
you'd still be there next year?
[Norris] Um...
-[man chuckles] That's a bit of a no.
-No comment.
There's no smoke without fire
in Formula 1.
These rumors exist
because the interest is there.
To be Max's teammate in the future
would be something I'm definitely up for.
The pressure on Zak will be building.
-[man 1] Better. Better now.
-[man 2] Nice.
[Brown] What's up, dude?
-Get some warm-up.
-One sec.
Someone tell you we were going bowling
or are those golf shoes?
[Norris] Lovely golf shoes.
[Brown laughs]
-[Brown] Cool. Game on.
-[man] Good luck. Let's play.
[Brown] Nice drive.
Oh, that's not good!
I'm not in the water.
[man] Went over the water.
Yeah. Other side. Next to the alligators.
Let's see if I can find it.
How we gonna go in Miami?
I don't know.
We're so slow on the straight.
[Brown] So look,
I know this year's a tough start.
-[Norris] Yeah.
-But, um, the car not being fast enough,
I would imagine it is
pretty frustrating.
[Norris] Yeah. Like, we're McLaren, right?
So... we should be a team
that's fighting Ferrari and...
[Brown] Yeah.
...Red Bull, Mercedes.
-Like, we should be up there leading them.
-Yeah. No, I get it.
[Norris] So when we come into a season,
and it's a bit,
you know, we're not gonna be fighting
for top, you know, four teams...
-Yeah.
-...it's tough.
[Brown] We need to give you
a better race car.
I know there's been a lot of noise,
but we've been doing this now together
seven, eight years?
I think we'll, uh, we'll get there,
and then it'll be so much more sweet.
Let's beat all those guys.
I'll do my best, as always.
Let's hope our racing's
better than our golf.
[laughs] 100%!
[both laugh]
[Norris] I can't imagine
what it's like to be in Zak's position.
You know, running McLaren. Um...
Of course, it's...
There has to be a huge amount of pressure
that comes with it.
Shit, that went much further
than I thought.
[Norris] But when you put
so much effort into it,
and the best you can do is,
like, a 17th or 18th,
it feels like you're racing for nothing.
Fuck. This is quicker than our car, this.
[tense music plays]
[team member 1]
We should put those in there.
[team member 2]
It's like we've done it before.
[tense music continues]
This, by any metric,
has been a horrible start
to the season for McLaren.
Do the drivers want to stay
and race for you?
Do the sponsors want to hang around?
With where McLaren are now,
Zak's hoping for a miracle.
[Brown] All good.
Good luck. Yeah?
Let's... We'll need it.
[commentator 4] It's time
to go racing in the USA.
From Miami in Florida,
welcome to the fifth round
of the Formula 1 World Championship.
[chanting] Red Bull! Red Bull! Red Bull!
Red Bull! Red Bull!
[Brown] Fucking hell. We need points.
[commentator 1] Just look at the crowd.
Everybody's turned up,
everybody's looking excited.
Cars are on the grid. We're getting close.
[commentator 4]
There's Lando Norris down in 16th.
He will desperately be looking for
a turnaround in fortunes here today.
Oscar Piastri starting
on the back row in 19th.
How must he be feeling
about his awkward debut season?
[García] Radio check, Lando.
All good.
-[Stallard] Have a good race.
-[Piastri] Cheers.
[suspenseful music plays]
[Norris] I got hit. Rear.
[Joseph] Lando,
everything looks okay.
Sargeant is now ahead of you.
Early overtake available.
[Norris] Yeah. I'm... I'm trying.
[tense music plays]
-[Norris] I can't get past him.
-[Joseph] Understood.
[commentator 1] Lando Norris knows
it's going to be a long afternoon.
[commentator 2] 200 miles an hour
down the back straight,
Pérez puts his car
to the middle of the track.
[commentator 4] On board Max Verstappen.
Verstappen round the outside.
He's done it. He's got back in front.
[tense music continues]
[Verstappen] Do I just keep it up for now?
[Lambiase] Yep, copy.
You've got Piastri ahead.
[Stallard] Okay, the car behind
is Verstappen. That's the race leader.
[commentator 1] Say goodbye
to the Red Bull.
The car, in another league!
It's an uphill battle
if you're driving a McLaren right now.
[Becker] Ahead, we have Norris,
and he's currently struggling.
You are much quicker than him.
[tense music plays]
[Norris groans]
[Norris] Fucking hell. We clearly
don't have the pace of the cars around.
I don't know
what race I'm in at the minute.
[Joseph] I know this is frustrating,
but this is a good place for us.
It's just a patience game.
[Norris] Ha ha. Okay.
LOL.
[commentator 2] Max Verstappen
approaches the checkered flag.
He wins the Miami Grand Prix.
It's another one-two for Red Bull.
[commentator 1] Disastrous stuff
for McLaren, finishing 17th and 19th.
[Stallard] And, Oscar,
that was not the afternoon we wanted.
[Piastri] Yeah. Just struggled for pace.
[Norris] Felt pretty terrible,
but best we could do today.
I'm not suggesting it may look bad.
I'm suggesting it is bad.
[Horner] I think Zak's under pressure.
Inevitably, Formula 1's
a pressure business.
If you're not delivering,
you're under pressure.
He's been talking a big game.
When you don't deliver
and you get found out,
that's embarrassing, and it hurts.
The drivers, it's tough for them.
When we see drivers in Formula 1,
you... you tend to forget
that the journey started
when they were five or six years old.
And this sport is all about winning.
Lando can win.
If the car is capable of winning,
from a talent point of view,
uh, absolutely.
[reporter] There goes Lando.
[Norris] I don't have time.
[Patrick] It's a tough one in racing.
The loyalty that you have with your team
and the passion to win.
Um, but if the right opportunity
comes knocking...
sometimes you just go.
-[Russell yawns]
-[Norris] I love an early morning.
Oh, fucking hell. We've got
a McLaren logo on the side of a jet.
Let's go.
-[Russell] This is really nice. Wow.
-[Norris] Yeah, mate. It's frickin' mint.
[Russell] Silky.
-Need to have a word with Toto.
-[laughs] Yeah.
-Okay?
-[Russell] We good?
How are you? Very good, and you?
-[Norris] Let's go out tonight.
-Out out?
[Norris] Joking.
I'd never do such a thing.
[Russell] It was in my Williams contract.
You weren't allowed to drink
during the weekend.
Not gonna say names, but there's
definitely some people who drink.
-[Norris] You think?
-I know!
[chuckles] I've seen it.
-During a normal race weekend?
-[Russell] Yeah!
They're paying me off not to... not to tell.
-Not you, Lando.
-Oh! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
[Russell] Yeah. I was
rewatching, um, Miami.
-[Norris] We were so bad.
-Yeah, you... [laughs]
-Like, we were last.
-Yeah. I didn't wanna say it, but yeah.
I mean, it was bad, wasn't it?
Horrendous.
-That's every weekend, man.
-[Russell] I know.
And away we go.
[Norris] This is the worst start
to any season I've had.
I wanna be the best driver there is
in Formula 1.
That's why I started my whole journey.
Hi. I'm Lando Norris.
I'm European champion,
and I race KF-Junior.
[older Norris] This is what
we're born to do, what we've grown up
spending pretty much our whole life
trying to achieve.
I need to be stronger.
Um, and not make so many mistakes.
[older Norris] I'm in that position
that I saw on TV and dreamt of being in.
[tense music plays]
[Brown] Lando and I go back a long way.
Prior to McLaren.
First time I met Lando,
he was a small 14-year-old.
He and his father came in,
and he was very nice.
He was very shy,
as you would expect a 14-year-old.
He was very fast.
I think the first time
he drove a race car,
it was probably mine.
The dream is
to win world championships together.
So if we fall short of that
and see him do that in someone else's car,
that would be
personally quite disappointing.
You know, we've done so much together.
[Norris] My goal is to win races.
I would love to create the story
and finish the story and everything
with McLaren.
I really would love that.
Sometimes, you gotta make decisions
that are the best for you and your career.
If you wanna achieve success,
if you wanna win races, win championships,
sometimes things have to change,
as much as you don't want them to.
[man] Hearing rumors around Lando.
You know, given the performance,
the driver rumors...
We thought it might be useful
to come together.
I mean, it's been
a... tough start to the season.
I think just... we just need to take back
the... the story to the team.
Look, I know you're concerned,
and you have reason to be concerned.
[Rafique] Look, Zak,
you know I support you.
I support the team.
But this is our biggest sponsorship.
We're getting a lot
of questions asked internally.
"Was this the right move?"
"How long does
the performance stay at this level?"
I know you placed, um, a few big bets.
And this is a big one.
And it needs to, uh, pay off.
And we need to get results for you.
[Buxton] Zak's got a lot of questions
to answer right now.
Sponsors, they're gonna want to see
that step up the ladder
towards the competitive,
consistently performing edge
that Zak will have promised them.
-Good. See you guys later.
-Bye, Zak.
[Buxton] They will want a guarantee
Lando Norris is going nowhere.
[tense music plays]
[Brown] Morning.
You know, we're under big pressure, um...
Everyone's expected
a much stronger season.
Emotionally, it... it makes you frustrated.
Uh, makes you angry.
But also, at the end of the day,
you gotta fix the problem,
so what I am is highly motivated
to fix the problem.
-Morning, guys.
-Morning, Zak.
All good?
How, uh... How are we coming along
with the upgrades?
[man] Well, development is going well.
Um, but the redesign of the car is, um,
kind of bigger than what we anticipated,
because, uh, we are redesigning underneath
quite a lot of the mechanical part.
So it is a big undertaking for the team.
There's also,
from a mechanical point of view,
some risks associated
with having redesigned the car so much.
And, obviously, there's the reliability.
The reliability aspect with the redesign.
[Brown] Yeah.
So, due for Silverstone, you reckon?
Um, we are working hard
to have two cars in Silverstone.
Fingers crossed, yes.
There's still, uh, a few challenges
that we need to overcome
to actually deliver,
physically, the project on track.
-We will see soon.
-Yep. Thanks, guys.
[Williams] The likelihood of a team being
able to turn around their performance
to any kind of significant degree
during a season,
I can't tell you how difficult it is.
It's pretty much unheard of.
[Brown] I always have worries.
I know the consequences
for us not performing.
If you don't perform, you're not gonna
have top-line drivers that wanna race.
If I don't deliver,
I think we all know what happens.
[Paul] Just tell me
where we're at because,
you know, it hasn't been
the most impressive start.
[Brown] I think we started slower
than I'd anticipated.
How do the drivers feel?
Pretty frustrated.
I think Lando more than... than Oscar.
I... I get it. I'm frustrated.
Uh, partners are frustrated.
Everyone's frustrated.
Realistically,
what if these upgrades don't deliver?
[Brown] We'll have
pretty upset drivers
that we'll need to manage.
It's not lost on me
where we're at right now.
-You gotta keep the pressure on everyone.
-[Brown] Yep.
Uh, I don't wanna be brutal,
but we... we need to deliver.
-Yeah.
-We've put a lot of investment.
-We need to see the results.
-[Brown] Yeah.
Loud and clear.
[upbeat music plays]
[commentator 4] Qualifying for the 74th
British World Championship Grand Prix
is all set to take place
on the Silverstone circuit
in the heart of the United Kingdom.
[fan 1] Lando!
-[fan 2] Lando!
-[fan 3] A selfie?
[fan 4] Lando!
-Thanks. Good luck today.
-Thank you.
[camera shutters clicking]
[photographer] Can you get out
either side of that thing?
-What's that?
-[photographer] You get out either side?
-It's not easy.
-[man] No, I saw that.
[all laughing]
[Brown] What are they gonna say
in the press conference?
There'll be a little bit about, uh,
the progress that we've made
with upgrades.
[Brown] Yeah.
[team member] That's of huge interest
to the media at the moment.
Being a team boss when you're
not scoring points, it's horrific.
I can't describe the pressure
and what it feels like.
You've got the media writing stories.
TV cameras on you.
[Brown] We're showing up.
We wanna move forward, not backwards.
And then everyone that works for you
looks to you for change,
and you've gotta deliver it.
[Brown] This is a defining moment
for us to prove
to the world, to ourselves, our drivers,
that we're turning this team around.
We've tried to improve the car
in the areas in which
we know we have weaknesses.
But you start to beg the question of,
you know, how good are the upgrades?
[Norris] Success is your motivator.
So when you don't have any of it,
it's extremely tough.
You've kinda just gotta have faith
in your own abilities
and the team.
Maybe this car's... decent, you know?
Maybe we've turned a corner here.
But it could be
that it's the complete opposite.
[tense music plays]
[Piastri] There's always pressure.
When things are not going
as well as you hoped,
the pressure is... is even higher.
[tense music continues]
[Brown] I feel very responsible
for everything that happens at McLaren.
At the end of the day,
the buck stops with me.
[commentator 2] And the green light is on
at the end of the pit lane,
and we can get underway.
[Bono] Lewis, let's pick the pace up.
[commentator 4] How fast will Hamilton go
on his home track?
[Bono] Okay, Lewis. That's P7.
[Hamilton] We're so slow.
[commentator 4] Here comes Verstappen.
And Verstappen goes fastest.
[Lambiase] That's P1.
[cheering]
[commentator 1] Time to see what
Lando Norris can pull out of the bag.
[García] Okay, Lando.
It's now or never time.
Yeah, loud and clear.
[tense music plays]
[García] More full throttle if possible.
[tense music continues]
-Come on!
-Come on, lad.
[García] Keep the speed up.
Here we go, then.
[García] P2.
-[cheering]
-[commentator 2] Listen to the roar there!
Lando Norris gets second position.
[García] Well done, mate.
Great drive. Very good.
[Norris] Yeah, baby!
[dramatic music plays]
[commentator 2] Piastri
goes third fastest for McLaren!
Yeah!
[dramatic music continues]
[Stallard] Oscar, P3.
Well done, buddy.
[Piastri] Well done, everyone.
Not bad at all.
[cheering and applause]
[man] Yes!
-[Brown] Was he watching?
-Oh yeah.
Yeah, he will be. Yeah.
-There you go.
-That was good, eh?
-Well done.
-That was good.
Zak will celebrate this like a win.
But it's only Qualifying.
That's one lap.
The only true barometer
is the race.
And the drivers know that.
Do you think a podium
is on the cards, Lando, at all?
-Um, on pure performance, no.
-Right. Okay.
[Norris] Got P2, but then
the race is a different story.
[reporter 1] This is supposed to be
your most major upgrade.
How optimistic are you about it?
I never get my hopes up, so...
[reporter 2] 'Cause you've had
too many false dawns?
You've had too many false dawns?
Yeah.
[reporter 3] Cheers, Lando.
[Brown] The performance
in Qualifying was awesome.
But we need to validate that in a race.
Have we made the upgrade,
the step forward that we think we have?
Now we need to close the deal.
-[Joseph] Okay, Lando. Radio check.
-Yeah, loud and clear.
-[Stallard] Oscar, good luck.
-[Piastri] Cheers.
[Norris] P2 in front of my home crowd.
Big day for us as a team.
We're a bit in the unknown
of how well we could do.
[Piastri] I'm starting third on the grid.
But the car honestly
doesn't feel that much different.
When you compare it against other people,
you really see the difference.
[commentator 4] Lando Norris is
quick off the line into that first corner.
[Norris] Yeah, baby!
[commentator 2] Lando Norris
leads the British Grand Prix!
[Norris] Let's fucking go!
-Come on!
-Yeah! Let's go!
[cheering]
[commentator 4] McLaren in dreamland!
-[Norris] Gap?
-[García] 0.8.
[tense music plays]
[García] Gap, 0.6.
[commentator 2] Max Verstappen,
on the inside,
takes the lead of the British Grand Prix.
Oscar Piastri currently running
in sixth place.
[Stallard] Car ahead, Gasly.
[Loos] Piastri one second behind.
[tense music continues]
[commentator 4]
Oscar Piastri is up into fifth.
Yeah!
[Stallard] Well done, Oscar.
Keep this pace, keep going.
[Piastri] Copy.
[tense music plays]
[García] Okay, Lando.
Hamilton behind you.
How is the pace?
-[Norris] I'm happy. It's consistent.
-[García] Understood.
[commentator 5] Lando Norris
looks very comfortable.
[Joseph] Hamilton, ten seconds behind you.
So just best pace to the end now.
You're doing a great job.
[Slade] What's up, Kev?
[Magnussen] Engine died.
[Slade] Stop the car.
[commentator 1] Oh, that's
an engine problem for Kevin Magnussen.
[Stallard] Safety car, safety car.
Magnussen stopped on track.
[Piastri] Copy.
-[García] Safety car.
-Wonderful.
[commentator 2] It's a full safety car,
which means the field will bunch up.
This offers the likes of Mercedes
a little bit of a... a way back in.
[Joseph] Hamilton will be
very close at the restart.
[Norris] Yeah, yeah.
I know.
[Norris] I'm in the worst position
I could possibly be in.
With ten laps to go,
if there's any driver
I don't want behind me, it's Lewis.
Fifteen years ago,
I was watching Lewis doing this race.
Now I'm in that position
racing against him.
If I make one mistake now, it's game over.
[García] Safety car ending.
Safety car in this lap.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 2] There's a green flag.
Safety car's in.
We can get going.
Lando Norris might have been
a touch slow to react,
and Hamilton is right on him.
[tense music plays]
[García] He has DRS, he has DRS.
[tense music continues]
[Bono] Overtake is available.
[commentator 2] That was stellar defending
from Lando Norris.
-[Norris] Gap?
-[García] 0.1.
[tense music continues]
[music fades]
[tense music resumes]
[commentator 2] Norris,
defending absolutely brilliantly,
keeps Lewis Hamilton at bay.
That McLaren is fast in a straight line.
[Bono] Copy.
[García] P2. P2 Great job, man!
[Norris] Woo!
Awesome! Woo! [laughs]
[García] Yeah, man. Fantastic.
[Norris] Podium in my home race.
Podium in our home race.
[commentator 2] McLaren coming home
in second place with Lando Norris.
[Bono] Unlucky against Norris.
Just too strong for us.
Hey, that McLaren's a rocket ship.
[Stallard] Checkered flag. P4, baby!
[commentator 2] Oscar Piastri
comes home fourth for his best result.
[Piastri] Thank you for all the hard work.
Thanks for all the updates.
We're back, baby.
Let's go get 'em!
[commentator 4] Epic moment for McLaren.
What a brilliant weekend for them!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Come on, baby!
[Brown] Yes!
[laughs]
Yes!
[Brown] To have both our guys
right up at the front was awesome.
Never in doubt, never in doubt!
And to think here we are
after the season we had is... is phenomenal.
We've earned it.
We've done it the hard way.
And so it is,
I think, to a certain extent,
more fulfilling
than if we started the season strong.
All right, let's go to a podium!
Let's go see my boy Lando!
-[man] Good job, Zak.
-[Brown] Thank you.
Let's go see him!
Dude, I didn't wait this long
to walk to the podium!
[laughter]
[Brown] Excuse me.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
[Brown sighs and laughs]
How'd you like those hard tires, man?
[Brown laughs]
Finishing second in Silverstone
was one of the best days of my life.
Like, without a question.
[uplifting music plays]
[cheering]
Emotional, just 'cause
it's a lot of stress and relief
for everyone.
Yeah! Woo!
I can literally
picture it all so perfectly.
And we did what we needed to do.
We put ourselves
back on the map as a team.
I have no idea what it's like
to win a Formula 1 race.
Um, 'cause I've never done it.
[photographer] One, two, three.
[all cheer]
Gonna just bide my time,
but, uh, I know my time's coming.
It's definitely gonna come, yeah. 100%.
Not here to be last.
-[Hülkenberg] Engine's gone.
-What the fuck?
Williams have taken a massive gamble
on a new team principal.
When you get data right,
that's how you move forward.
[Urwin] P9. That's a bloody good job.
[Steiner] Williams, boom, from nowhere.
We need to do something different here.
[Buxton] Ferrari wanted a new direction,
and Fred represents that.
[commentator 2] Sainz locks up,
and somehow they avoid contact.
That could have been awful for Ferrari.
Watching your two drivers
battle on the track,
the TP needs to tell their drivers,
"Dial it down a bit."
[closing theme music plays]
[music fades]