Finishing my breakfast.
It's not always like this. No.
It gets worse.
[upbeat music plays]
I'm here with Guenther Steiner
for our audio recording.
[woman] Come to the first floor.
We'll sign you in.
Perfect. Thank you.
[music fades]
[Steiner] Guenther. Nice to meet you.
[man] So, um, have you done
any reading, anything...
[Steiner] Yeah, I can read. Yeah.
[laughs]
Fantastic. That's always
a useful skill to have anyway.
Do you want to try on
that set of headphones in there
and we'll start in earnest.
Cool. Let me know
whenever you're ready to go.
-I'm good.
-[man] Okay, fantastic. We're rolling.
"It probably won't surprise many people
that I'm starting my book
with a swear word."
"But all I can say is
thank fuck that season is over."
[engines roar]
-[tires screeching]
-[loud thud]
[commentator 1] Oh, that is the Haas.
Fuck.
I don't need any of this.
We had a few difficult years,
the darkest years of, uh, Haas.
[Mazepin] He absolutely turned into me.
[Steiner] It never rains, it pours.
[Grosjean] Fuck!
[explosion]
"I don't drink very much,
but this year, I've been tempted
to take it up professionally."
"Whiskey on a fucking drip."
"That's what I needed sometimes."
This year, we have to prove
that we can do better
than being at the back of the field.
Otherwise, it's no point to be there.
What I would do, look for another job.
[engine revs]
-[fan 1] Picture? Picture?
-[Steiner] Quick. Yeah, quick.
[fan 2] Thank you.
[fan 3] You are hilarious.
I love your work.
You are the funniest guy.
And your mate, uh, Ferrari, we love it.
[Steiner] Quick, we need to go.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 2] We are here
on the shores of the Red Sea in Jeddah.
It's round two of the Formula 1 season.
[electronic music plays]
[in Italian] Feet in front.
[electronic music continues]
[in English] Good afternoon.
[woman] Absolutely loved the book!
Thank you.
[Buxton] Coming into this season,
Haas have one objective.
To escape the fight
at the bottom of the championship table.
[speaks German]
They put their faith
in a couple of rookies
over the last few seasons,
and it absolutely hurt their performance.
-[commentator 3] It's Nikita Mazepin off!
-[Steiner] Fucking hell.
[commentator 3] Schumacher on the inside
of Vettel. They make contact!
[engine revving]
[Steiner] Fucking hell.
[Buxton] This year, Haas need no stress
to try and launch themselves
back into midfield contention.
[Steiner] You know
where the sandwiches are?
Yeah, an espresso, please.
I'm rookied out in the moment.
We need an experienced driver
back in the team.
[Hülkenberg] Where do you want me?
I thought, if we can replicate
what we did with Kevin,
bring somebody out
which hasn't been racing for a few years...
[commentator 3] Hülkenberg
crosses the line in sixth.
-[Ricciardo] Hülkenberg.
-Hülkenberg.
Hülkenberg. Hülkenberg!
[Hülkenberg] I've missed this black room.
Nico Hülkenberg, MoneyGram Haas F1 team.
Guenther hired me
to bring experience to the team,
and the target and the mission is to bring
Haas further up the midfield again.
Last year, we spent a lot of time
just chasing our own tail, fixing things,
and we couldn't think about development.
That is why I wanted
this combination of drivers,
you know, to help,
to make the team better.
We need to get a better platform to start,
that we are ready for better drivers.
Once you have a better platform,
he wants to get rid of us.
-Did you hear that? Hm. Hm.
-That's what I heard.
You're a fucking smart-ass. [laughs]
[laughs]
Nico Hülkenberg and Kevin Magnussen,
two drivers
with huge experience in the sport,
but there's no love lost, that's for sure.
[commentator 4] Magnussen on the inside
with Hülkenberg.
[Hülkenberg] Magnussen
just ran me off the track. What a cock.
Everyone's expecting it to kick off.
[interviewer] Can you tell me
what was said?
Play the clip.
Once again, the most unsporting driver.
Suck my balls, mate.
[Steiner] Hopefully,
they don't kill each other.
Jesus Christ.
-[sighs] Are you in the Chevron Hotel too?
-Yeah.
-You never come down for breakfast.
-Just later than you, I think.
-Oh really?
[Hülkenberg] We are older.
We're both actually young fathers.
There is no tension between us.
We're gonna get you and Nico
to walk down the corridor.
[woman] Yeah, basically,
we'll give out 10,000 burritos.
[Hülkenberg] Woo!
One incident was five years ago.
We've moved on.
-I'm Nico Hülkenberg.
-I'm Kevin Magnussen.
-And if we score points this weekend...
-You score burritos.
[man] Time.
[Steiner] Gonna close the door.
Hi, Gene.
[Gene Haas] Hülkenberg was a good choice.
[Steiner] Yeah, I think we took
the right one. He will be fighting.
I mean, he wants fucking podium,
Gene, you know?
[Gene] It's all good.
[Steiner] Until tomorrow
when it all goes to shit.
[laughs]
No. We try to do our best,
Gene, you know? Yeah.
[Gene] All righty,
well, good luck tomorrow.
[Steiner] Okay. Thanks, Gene.
Bye now. Bye-bye.
With Gene, I mean, the target
is always to be successful.
He just doesn't want to be a backmarker.
He wants to be here to fight
and to get better every year.
Watching your team finish last is
one of the most painful experiences
in Formula 1.
Things can really quickly
spiral out of control,
and to try and get yourself
back out of that spiral is so difficult.
And in the last five years, the only teams
to finish last more than Haas
are my old team, Williams.
Uh, do you know when that goes off,
the red lights come on?
-Oh, yeah?
-[man] That stayed on.
Everything else tripped.
[Buxton] Over at Williams,
there's big investment.
They're gonna want to see
a move up the field.
And they've taken a massive gamble
with a new team principal.
He hasn't come
from a place of team management.
[upbeat music plays]
I'm James Vowle...
Ooh, can't even say my own name.
That's a great start. Okay.
A little bit more liquid.
I need more swearing in there,
like Guenther, I think.
[chuckling]
I'm James Vowles. I'm 44 years of old.
No, still not...
One more time.
I'm James Vowles. I'm 44.
And I'm the team principal
for Williams F1.
Actually, it's still not right.
Williams Racing.
Oy.
Morning, everyone.
Morning.
The world has changed slightly. I... I know
we have been suffering for a while.
But we have a car that if we get things
correct, we can deliver with.
And that's a very different situation
than what you had,
perhaps, the last few years.
Enjoy the challenge that's in front of us.
We're here to grow and expand
and basically become
better and better year on year.
I can promise you where we are today
is not where we're gonna be
in two to three years.
Haas are the closest rivals.
This year, they have
a tremendous wealth of experience.
I'm the youngest TP in Formula 1,
and I have a younger driver lineup.
Alex, do you want to add to that?
Yeah, maybe just, uh, more so that, um,
I do think we are in a good place.
We do, weirdly, have a car
that seems to go quite well around here.
It's all about the fine details,
and if we execute as planned,
I think we'll be in a good place.
[Vowles] Very good.
You guys need to, like, make it
less depressing in these rooms.
It does feel like an electric chair.
Five years at the back of the grid
dents everyone's confidence.
As a driver, you know,
that motivation, that desire,
it just gets trampled on,
but that's why James is in.
[applause]
We've also got a rookie this year
in Logan Sargeant.
I'll be giving my everything
for everyone here
and, um, a lot to learn for myself.
I think, as a team,
we're moving in the right direction.
My name's Logan Sargeant,
Formula 1 driver for Williams Racing
in 2023.
And then am I meant to do that? Sorry.
All right, thanks, everyone.
Have a good race.
[man] He's like,
"What is your coffee order?"
[Vowles] A decaf,
but not this morning, actually.
-Can I have a tea with some honey?
-[woman] Tea?
I'm really particular
on the caffeine input.
I don't put any caffeine in my body
until Sunday.
[man] Ah.
[Vowles] Because then you get
the real benefit of the caffeine.
The studies that go on about it,
after a period of time,
actually, what happens is you need
caffeine just to get to a normal state.
You don't get to an elevated state.
That's where you are.
The role of the TP, I think, has migrated.
I will be the first to admit,
I am pretty geeky.
Decaf still has caffeine in it.
-Oh really?
-Yeah.
It's just not 120 or 200 milligrams.
Data, for me,
is the foundation of Formula 1.
There's no human judgement involved.
You've got to get
your foundations right in data.
When you get that right,
that's how you move forward.
Quick look at timing.
Yeah, avocado.
-Yeah, no worries. Of course.
-Thank you very much.
James was a key part
of Mercedes' run of world championships.
[applause]
[Buxton] A brilliant engineer
who has learned
at the Toto Wolff School
of Team Management.
Hi. I'll have a cappuccino pumpernickel.
James, you know, do this.
You know, you need to learn this.
Like this.
Uh, apologies. There's...
There's a lot that I can...
[Toto] But you're getting there.
The shirt is proper.
James is one
of the most intelligent people
that I've worked with at Mercedes.
He was in charge of strategy.
In this sport, you need to get
the balance right between data
and then your instinct, um, as a leader.
The main part, nevertheless,
is running people that run racing cars.
And that is gonna be tough.
Remember what I told you
when I was at Williams in 2012.
When someone comes with energy
and ambition and determination,
you can turn around a team
that's even lacking infrastructure
by sheer, uh, energy.
[Buxton] You've got two different
methodologies going here
in this battle at the back.
Old school, new school.
Age and experience
up against a gamble on youth.
Traditional management versus
a new generation of team principal.
Today, we're doing two different crews,
so crew one and an alternate crew.
I am what I would call a micromanager.
Are you getting
enough feedback afterwards?
I can't remember the last time
I've screamed or shouted.
They need their fucking confidence.
-Yeah.
-[Steiner] I'm a pretty straight talker.
I do my way. If it works, fine.
If it doesn't, at least I'm responsible.
[Buxton] Guenther and James Vowles
are under pressure.
Neither one of them
can afford to finish last.
[tense music plays]
[Vowles] If we get ahead of them,
we're racing.
[tense music continues]
[Slade] Radio check, Kev.
Radio's good.
-[Gannon] Okay, Nico?
-Let's do it.
-[Jego] Have a good one, mate.
-Copy that. Let's do it.
[Urwin] Let's go race when you can.
Yeah, copy.
[commentator 2] Here come the lights
for the second grand prix of the year!
[tense music plays]
[engines screech]
[Urwin] Currently P12.
[Gannon] You've got Albon ahead. Push.
Okay, good job, Nico.
Oh my God, brake failure.
[tense music plays]
Jesus Christ, man.
Fucking dangerous.
[tense music continues]
[Urwin] We'll push you back in the garage.
Don't even stand in front of the car,
'cause I can't even stop.
[Jego] Look at the Haas. Catch them.
[Gannon] Sargeant behind, very close.
[commentator 1] This is a cracking battle
from a man in his 182nd start
up against a man in only his second start.
[Jego] Early overtake.
[Sargeant] I have nowhere to go.
[Gannon] Keep doing
what you're doing, Nico.
Doing an amazing job.
[Slade] Doing a great job, Kev. Gonna keep
off the radio to let you concentrate.
[commentator 2] Magnussen in 11th here.
If he can overtake Tsunoda,
he'll be in the points.
[tense music plays]
[Slade] Super job, Kev.
[tense music continues]
[commentator 2] This could be
a rare point for Haas.
[Slade] That's it, Kev. P10.
Fantastic, mate. Superb.
[Steiner] Good job, Kevin.
You can be proud of yourself.
[Magnussen] Yeah, you too, Guenther.
You too.
[Gannon] Checkered Flag, Nico.
Checkered flag. Good job.
Kevin got tenth, so we got
the first point for Haas today.
Great. Good job, guys.
[commentator 4] Superb drive by Hülkenberg
there, just outside the points in 12th.
[Buxton] It's the perfect start for Haas.
That car is lightning-fast.
Scoring points gives you the positivity,
the belief that you can score
in every race.
[Jego] Checkered flag. Checkered flag.
[Sargeant] Uh, thanks, guys. Tough one.
[commentator 4]
No points for Williams today
as the remaining car of Sargeant
comes in a lowly 16th.
[Buxton] Williams is struggling.
James has taken on what is inarguably
one of the most difficult jobs
in Formula 1.
You're taking a gamble on youth.
And if Williams don't start to improve,
will they ask the question of,
"Did we put our eggs in the wrong basket?"
That's an emotional roller coaster
I don't wanna go through again.
[commentator 1] And it's Alex Albon off.
And Alex Albon out.
Nico Hülkenberg's finished seventh
and he's scored some big points
for the Haas team.
[Steiner] Very happy
to have Nico this year.
How can we make the biggest step forward?
Experienced drivers.
And Nico is one of them.
I hit my front wing. I think it's off.
I'm so sorry.
[Vowles] It's fair to say
I've walked through the door
and I've seen what's in front of me,
and... it's worse than I expected.
[Slade] P10, one point, we'll take that.
Fighting the big boys today.
They're expecting this to be
Sunday Times bestseller list.
And to do that,
you're looking at about 50,000 copies.
Yeah.
Prince Harry sold 400,000,
so you know, that's...
-[Steiner] Good lad.
-Yeah. Good on him.
-[Steiner] Yeah.
-Look at what he had to go through.
[both laugh]
[upbeat music plays]
[man] Guenther! Guenther!
Can I get a picture? Guenther!
Oh my God, what are you doing in London?
-Good luck in the season, buddy.
-Thank you. Thank you. [chuckles]
-[Stuart] Making people happy.
-[Steiner] That's what I'm here for.
Hi, guys.
Oh my God!
[Steiner] You're welcome.
-Hello.
[woman 1] Could you draw a tire?
And I'm gonna get it tattooed.
[Steiner] A tire?
[woman 1] If I see you at Silverstone,
I'll show you it.
[woman 2] A good start to the season,
so you're smiling.
[laughs] I'm still smiling.
You know, I'm still smiling,
so hopefully, I can keep the smile.
[Buxton] Guenther's star has never
shone brighter than it does right now.
At this point of the season, Haas are
sitting seventh in the world championship.
That's genuine midfield.
And he's a rock star.
[woman 3] Well done to Haas,
and you've got points already
in the Constructors, so keep it up.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
-[woman 4] Nice to meet you.
-[Steiner] Nice to meet you. Thanks.
The best morale booster
for a team is results.
There is nothing like it.
-Thank you very much. Thank you.
-You are welcome.
People thought our destiny is to be last.
We are not here to be last.
We are here to compete.
[man] Could you write,
"We look like fucking legends"?
[laughter]
"The Ferrari boys may be pretty,
but we have real men."
Oh!
Our story this year will be there is
no story. We are not looking for drama.
So please don't jinx us,
and keep away the drama.
Morning.
When your rivals around you
are moving forward and outscoring you,
it is painful. There's no doubt about it.
That's a good thing. It should be painful.
You should care about it.
If you want success,
it's all about the psychological approach
and the confidence
the driver has in that moment.
And my job in that is to create
the environments where they can grow.
[Albon] What is today?
[man] Power.
It's a little bit of contrast work.
Yeah.
[Albon] I'm not always the most outright
confident person that you will see.
We've just come off a dead run of races
where we've been falling back.
We're not anywhere close
to... to fighting for points.
[Harding] Three, two, one.
Has James articulated how much
of a bigger job it is than he expected?
[Albon] Yes. I think there's, like,
short-term things he can do.
We don't want to be fighting Haas
in the future.
That's also not where I want to be.
Teams are pulling away from us.
James has gotta try to make this work.
-Hi, Mr. Vowles. All right?
-Yeah, very, very good.
I never asked you what,
in your mind, success looks like.
Right now, in this team,
it's progress. It's seeing progress.
The reason why I joined here
was 'cause I really do believe
we can be back at the front.
-Yeah.
-Competing for winning championships...
[chuckles]
[Vowles] You joke and laugh about it,
but it's important to realize
that's the quality and caliber
that you have available to you.
Hm, okay.
You need to be turning up with a car
that's being updated several times a year.
-Yeah, sure.
-[Vowles] And it will keep getting better.
Prior to this, I think
there was a lot of resistance to change.
It needs to be completely
break everything again
and make sure we keep moving up.
Because of the data I've gone through,
we have made a number of changes
which I can't wait to see.
So I think that's gonna raise the bar
and improve performance.
This weekend,
you'll get a much better race car.
It's down to me now to make sure
that I prove myself to the world
that I'm capable
and can take this team forward.
[commentator 3] Good afternoon
and welcome to the Canadian Grand Prix.
Morning, everyone.
[man 1] Can I get you breakfast?
Um, just the... Just the normal thing.
Avocado and some... A smoothie.
-So not the açai today.
-Yeah, sure. No problem.
Although, we will try that...
maybe tomorrow.
[man 1] Tomorrow?
I just feel the risk of getting
this white shirt exposed is fairly high.
-[man 1] Right. No problem.
-[Vowles] Thanks, Harry.
I ate a lot of Chipotle yesterday.
[man 2] Did you? How's your tummy?
-[man 3] Best boss ever.
-[man 4] Absolutely.
Oh, he's over there. Look.
Ah.
-[laughs]
-Fancy seeing you here.
Big changes.
Hopefully they work.
-Yeah.
[electronic music plays]
-[man] Are you gonna win this today?
-I hope so. That's the plan.
[commentator 2] It's a great opportunity
for points for the Haas team
as Hülkenberg starts fifth on the grid.
-How the fuck did you do that?
-[Steiner] What?
Yesterday. Very good.
Anyway, never mind. You're in
a good position until you fuck it up.
Fuck off.
-Every time I...
-Fuck off!
[Buxton] This could be
a huge race for Haas
because they start it with
a legitimate chance of scoring big points.
If Haas make the most of their advantage,
they will tighten their grip
on that midfield placing.
[Vowles] This is the part of the race
where you're like an expectant father.
You know what's gonna happen,
but there's not a lot
you can do to control it.
[Buxton] Williams are stuck, tethered
to the bottom of the championship table.
James Vowles is still trying
to establish himself,
but the more you let go
through your fingers,
the fewer opportunities remain.
[engineer] Okay, Logan. Radio check.
Yeah, I got you.
[Gannon] And radio check.
Yep, radio good.
The law of driving and racing
doesn't change.
I know it inside out
because I've been doing it forever.
I know what I have to do
and when I have to do it.
[tense music plays]
[Urwin] Thirty seconds.
[Albon] When you get into that car,
the noise goes away,
and you feel very isolated.
The pressure's all on me to deliver.
[commentator 1] It's lights out,
and away we go.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 2] Nico Hülkenberg
under pressure from Esteban Ocon.
They're wheel to wheel.
Ocon overtakes Hülkenberg,
who drops down to sixth.
[Hülkenberg] Shit.
[Steiner] Fucking hell.
[tense music plays]
[Urwin] Alex, pick up the pace.
Keep with them.
Copy.
[tense music continues]
[Slade] Mode push when you're ready,
Kev. Mode push.
[commentator 2] Here comes Magnussen
in P13, closing in on Pérez.
[tense music continues]
[Slade] Watch out.
[Magnussen] Shit.
[commentator 2] Into the wall
goes the Haas of Kevin Magnussen!
[Slade] Are you okay, Kev? Are you okay?
[Magnussen] Yeah.
[commentator 1] That was almost
a race-ending moment.
We lost two positions.
[Gannon] Nico, rear brakes are a bit hot.
[Hülkenburg] We pushed
that tire quite hard already.
[commentator 4] Hülkenberg
struggling with the car.
[tense music plays]
[Gannon] Box now, Nico. Box now.
[tense music continues]
[commentator 4] This will
cost Hülkenberg places.
He'll come out
right at the back of the field.
[Slade] Okay, so Nico has boxed.
You are currently P7.
[commentator 4] Alex Albon in P8,
right behind Magnussen.
That Williams
is suddenly looking competitive
in its first race since the design change.
[Urwin] Gap behind at 0.6.
Overtake available.
[Slade] Albon behind has DRS.
[tense music plays]
[Urwin] You've got the pace to pass him.
[tense music continues]
[Albon] The car feels really good.
There's that inner confidence.
In some ways,
the pressure actually goes away.
This is what I'm born to do.
[tense music plays]
Yes, guys!
[Urwin] Wow!
[man] Let's go, Alex. Come on, mate!
[commentator 2]
Incredible move from Albon!
[tense music plays]
[Gannon] Ten laps to go.
Obviously we need some help.
[Hülkenburg]
How many seconds are we behind P10?
[Gannon] Eighteen seconds up the road.
One-eight seconds.
[music fades]
[tense music plays]
[Slade] De Vries behind.
Stay ahead of de Vries.
[commentator 4] Nyck de Vries
going wheel to wheel here.
They're so close to banging wheels!
Magnussen and de Vries still going at it.
[Slade] Okay, Kev, push.
[tense music continues]
[commentator 4] Lock up and contact!
[music fades]
[Magnussen] What the fuck?
[commentator 4] There will be no points
for Magnussen today.
[Steiner] Replay this.
It's fucking done.
[commentator 1] And down the straight,
Alex Albon.
[Urwin] Okay, starting the last lap.
You can push.
[Albon] Copy.
[tense music plays]
-[Urwin] Get in there, P7.
-Yes!
Come on!
Yes!
[commentator 4] Alexander Albon
is performing heroics out there.
[Vowles] Really, really impressive drive.
You guys, the upgrades...
This is for all the hard work. Thank you.
[cheering and applause]
[Gannon] Checkered flag, Nico.
Checkered flag.
P15.
[Hülkenburg] All we had left, hey?
It was just clinical.
It was absolutely beautiful.
Literally nothing else you could've done.
Executed it perfectly.
Absolutely clinical.
[Albon] This is like a race win.
That buildup of emotion,
just being under pressure for so long,
it all dissipates.
It's a great moment. It's a great weekend.
Brilliant stuff.
[indistinct chatter]
Worth it. Every second of it.
Well done. Really well done by you guys.
[man] Hey, hey! Wahey!
Congrats!
[cheering]
What the fuck?
[Buxton] Haas have had
a really good start to the season.
[Steiner] Bullshit. Bullshit.
[Buxton] But now, that Haas car
seems to have issues.
Guenther's gonna be hoping
it's something specific to this track.
If it consistently happens,
then that's something
intrinsically wrong with the car.
[upbeat music plays]
[commentator 1] Oh dear!
[Hülkenberg] Oh, I lost power.
Engine has gone.
[commentator 1] Brakes smoking,
engine smoking.
[Steiner] It's fucking embarrassing.
Engine's gone bang. Whoa, whoa, fire.
[Slade] Assume the car
is not safe, Kev.
Developing a car,
extracting everything from it
is such a key facet of this sport.
That was three times shit.
Shakira, shit engine, shit car.
Haas are in a really difficult spot.
It's not bringing a knife to a gunfight.
They're bringing a spoon.
[Steiner] Fuck.
With our promising start,
uh, I expected more.
I think our biggest downside was
we didn't make any progress
in developing the car.
The lemon has been squeezed.
There's no more juice in it.
Buon giorno. Ciao. Ciao.
Hello. Can you hear us?
Yes, we can in England. Yes.
We are in a situation, as you all know,
that if there is no improvement,
we're a little bit in, uh, no-man's-land.
The cooling flow ducting
is substantially improved.
We increased the flow rate
from very small to small but purposeful.
[Steiner] What the fuck, man?
Jesus Christ, you don't convince me.
I'm not expert in looking at our cars.
Look around what other people are doing.
That's very important.
Williams, where they were
and where they are now,
uh, taking a very short time,
made a lot of progress.
Again, I have no idea how they did it,
you know? But they did a good job.
If they are able to do it, why would we
not be able to do it, you know?
I mean, look at the step they made.
One upgrade, boom.
You know? From nowhere.
[tense music pulsates]
When you see your competitors
making progress, it's difficult,
because it's always, "Why can we
not do what the other ones are doing?"
We need to make a step forward.
I'm not an engineer by trade.
I'm not gonna do that myself.
I mean, I've got people doing it.
We need to do something different here.
We need to make gains, and then
keep on making gains over the season.
In Formula 1,
times change very, very quickly.
So today's team principal is having
to deal with big data, big tech,
and have a true depth of understanding
and knowledge of these cars
and what's going on underneath the hoods.
[engine revs]
[Albon] I'm getting
quite big balance shifts
depending on which corner
I'm going through.
Yeah. Potentially,
this might change things.
So it's... it's not A, B, C, A.
It's B, C, A.
[Vowles] My background is in mathematics,
physics, the science-type subjects.
And I went into, uh,
an engineering degree,
and those really created the foundations
behind my passion for this sport.
Data drives what you're trying to do.
You're just running a million simulations,
trying to predict what's gonna happen.
It helps us because I'm very much
always trying to think ahead
to how I can get an edge.
[engine revs]
[upbeat music plays]
[Urwin] Checkered flag. P8.
-We've got really strong pace.
-[Vowles] You drove admirably.
You brought home some really good points.
[upbeat music continues]
[commentator 1] Alex Albon
takes the checkered flag.
[Urwin] Nice job. P7.
-Yes!
-[Urwin] You make this look easy.
[commentator 4] That's the sixth race
in a row
that Haas has failed to score any points.
[Steiner] It's a fucking embarrassment.
I'm fucking done with this shit, you know.
Something is wrong here.
Something needs to change on this car.
We cannot keep on trying to do this
if then nothing comes out.
Still need to phone Gene.
Fucking hell. That will be
fucking something that I hate to hear now.
Hi, Gene.
We look like fucking idiots out there.
I'm badly... I'm badly embarrassed, yeah.
I'm... I'm fucking...
I'm... I'm not proud of myself
here, you know.
There's something inherently wrong
with this fucking car, Gene.
Look, they couldn't get past
a fucking Williams, Gene.
[melancholy music plays]
[Steiner] It is getting tougher
and tougher in F1. Everything has changed.
If you know that you are last every year,
it's no point to do it.
It's too hard work for no joy.
[in Tyrolean] If only the season
were as good as the wine. [laughs]
-That'd be great.
-[woman] True, but at the moment...
Yes, we struggle at the moment,
in plain language.
Everyone made progress,
and we have problems.
You have to find a solution.
It's not about giving up,
but searching for something.
There are many minds involved.
[Guenther in English] We have
the last races of the season.
We have to get some points.
We have to prove that we can do better
than Williams at the back of the field.
[commentator 4] Welcome to round 20
of the Formula 1 season.
This is Mexico City.
[Buxton] Coming into these last few races,
Haas have to have changed direction
or at least fixed the base problem.
[man] Yay, the new car is here.
[Buxton] The entirety of Haas's season
rests on this upgrade.
We need more performance to battle.
-[reporter 1] The guys've done a good job.
-Good.
-[reporter 2] It's a pretty big upgrade.
-[Magnussen] A lot of changes.
It's a very different-looking car,
but it's exciting
because, on paper, it looks very good.
[Steiner] The Constructors Championship,
it's more than tight.
One lucky circumstance
can get you four or five points.
There is nothing in between us.
[Vowles] So your biggest concern
was just the weird drop?
Yeah, but it was just like...
It felt very odd to me.
The championship is down
to a matter of points.
The only thing you can do is do
the best result you can with your car
and get every single point
out of it you can.
When we look to the performance,
I think you were the fastest on the grid,
so don't... don't go too far away
from what we already know.
-That's the only thing I'd say.
-[Albon] Okay.
Thank you for checking.
I want to finish seventh
in this year's championship.
I wanna show the world
that we have stepped forward.
Haas have a complete change
of car philosophy,
and you don't know where that's gonna hit.
[Steiner] The car is the last opportunity
to score points
and keep up with our opposition.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 4] Haas will be hoping the
new car will turn around their fortunes
and help them gain some much needed points
in the battle with Williams.
The Mexico City Grand Prix is go!
[commentator 1] Great start
from Hülkenberg, into eighth.
Alex Albon stuck in the middle
of an Alfa Romeo sandwich.
[tense music plays]
[Slade] Okay, Kev, I'm afraid it
looks like brakes are hot. Please confirm.
[Magnussen] Um, I am struggling now.
[commentator 4] Oh, Magnussen
running very wide there.
[tense music plays]
[Slade] We see
the under-steer level rising.
[commentator 4] He's really struggling.
[Slade] Kev, are you okay?
[Magnussen] Rear left
has just completely gone here.
-[engine sputters]
-[commentator 2] Rear left failure.
-Rear left broken.
-[car thuds]
What the fuck?
[Slade] Are you okay, Kev?
Are you okay?
[tense music plays]
[music fades]
[Urwin] P9.
That's a bloody good job. Well done.
[cheering and applause]
Yes!
[Vowles] Well done, Alex.
Really, really solid drive again.
Points. Just tally adding up.
-Yes!
-Done!
[Vowles] We've moved ourselves
into a better place in the championship.
We've demonstrated to the world
that we can bring performance to the car
and that we can fight amongst our peers.
And another one.
-[man] Well done.
-Well done, chap.
[Vowles] I'm incredibly happy
for the team.
But for me,
I want more.
[ominous music builds]
[music fades]
[Steiner] Hi, Gene.
[Gene] Kind of a waste of time.
[Steiner] Fucking hell.
That was some fucking day.
I'm doing this a long time, you know?
It's a difficult game, you know?
[Gene] Yeah, but next year,
it's gonna be the same story.
[Steiner] I've fucking had enough.
I'm fucking done with this.
[somber music plays]
Once again, you find yourself
at the bottom of the order.
You're facing ridicule.
You're facing a slating.
The pressure on you is
inexplicably phenomenal.
At what point do you question the future?
[somber music continues]
[Steiner] Sometimes,
I think about the end of my career.
I don't have the success
I want to have in Formula 1.
Sometimes, I say,
"Why I'm doing this actually?"
"You know, this is not worthwhile."
[somber music continues]
[Guenther in Italian] Where are you?
Oh.
-[Mattia Binotto] How's it going?
-[Steiner] Good. Not as good as you.
Look. Can you see the difference?
You're already...
How are you?
[Steiner] What's up?
What's up with you instead?
[Mattia] Look, really.
Try it. Eat.
Take off the skin.
[Steiner] I eat everything, unlike you.
So now, instead of going to the track,
you can come here every week?
Instead of the races.
Yes, I'm here every week now.
Before, I was traveling to the track.
Now I travel to the vineyard.
What's better,
coming here or going to the tracks?
You don't have to justify
if you finish last or second to last.
It's all about slowing down, Guenther.
-Okay, shall we go taste the wine?
-[Steiner] Shall we go?
Cheers. To you.
Obviously, everything has changed
for me this year.
How do you feel about it?
You can feel where it's time to...
You focus on what you'll be doing next.
Of course, you know, I think you don't
get to make all the choices in your life,
but if some choices are made,
you have to accept.
There's nothing to be scared of.
Finished.
[Guenther in English] This year,
it's been pretty tough.
I don't know
if I will I do this for another year.
Maybe you have to bite the bullet.
There is life outside of F1 as well.
Maybe it's time to do something different.
We expect both drivers to work together.
[commentator 1] Contact!
[Ocon] Oh my God.
[groaning]
We both know we'll never be best friends.
[Buxton] Otmar's gotta
pull his drivers in line.
Division within the team
can rip it apart at the seams.
Let's get on with it.
My contract is up for renewal.
[man] Lewis, please come back.
[commentator 1] The worst thing Ferrari
could do is start racing each other.
[commentator 1] Oh,
and Charles Leclerc locks up!
[Sainz] Fuck.
Surgery is really
the only way we can fix this.
[closing theme music plays]
[music fades]