[tense music plays]
-[Leclerc in Italian] It snowed a bit.
-[man] Yes.
[Leclerc] The powder is nice and fresh.
[tense music continues]
[Leclerc] We made it.
Are you nervous for the last part?
No. Can't wait.
[chuckles]
[Leclerc in English] As much as it's been
a very difficult season...
[Leclerc] No, no, no, no, no! Come on!
-No power.
-[Padros] Sorry about that.
-[Sainz] We're gonna crash.
-[Adami] Yeah, copy.
The second part of the season
has been much more positive.
[Adami] P1, baby. P1.
[in Spanish] Come on!
[man in Italian]
This part is the steepest.
[Leclerc] Yes.
[Leclerc in English] In the fight
for second place in the Constructors,
the main target is to beat the Mercedes.
I've seen the progress of the team
and how much everybody has been pushing.
I can really feel
that momentum is with us.
[exhales deeply]
[Sainz] We've been closing the gap
to Mercedes over the last few races.
We still have
a good chance of beating them.
I give everything to... to see
if we can get that second place.
We're gonna give it our best shot.
[Buxton] Two races left.
Failure is not an option for Ferrari.
And you put your money on black,
or you put it on red.
[grunts]
It's Mercedes versus Ferrari.
[wheel gun whirring]
[engine revs]
-[Gertraud] Thank you.
-[Steiner] Thank you.
-[Gertraud in German] Nervous?
-[daughter] Yes.
You have to take a deep breath.
[pilot in English] All good, yeah?
Let's go.
[Spaghetti Western music plays]
[Ricciardo] We're out
in the Nevada desert.
We're about to go head-to-head
with Max and Checo.
Woo!
[laughter]
[Ricciardo exclaims]
[Ricciardo] Are you okay? [laughs]
[man] Nice and quiet everywhere here,
guys. We're rolling.
Here we go. And camera's set.
[helicopter blades whir]
[man] Here we go, and...
[pilot] We're 600 feet
above the ground right now.
As we're climbing up,
you're gonna see the F1 paddock
coming up straight ahead of us here.
The track's just below us here.
Oh yeah, I can see it. Yeah.
See where the grandstands are?
Now it's a traffic jam.
In a few hours, it's an F1 race.
[big band music plays]
[commentator 1] Welcome
to fabulous Las Vegas, Nevada.
We're blasting down one
of the most famous miles on planet Earth.
Hey, baby, what's going on?
Formula 1's first ever wedding chapel.
You may kiss the bride.
[cheering and applause]
[big band music continues]
Oh, Las Vegas, baby. [laughs]
There is so much put into this race,
from building the paddock,
closing down the Strip.
1.1 miles was literally driven on
by cars and buses
just hours before you were on track.
It's a big deal.
[big band music plays]
That is the glitz and the glam.
-[photographer 1] Yuki! Yuki, right here!
-[photographer 2] This way!
[Russell] I think Vegas is just gonna be
absolutely crazy.
You're absolutely buzzing for it.
[Elvis impersonator] Viva Las Vegas, baby.
[Leclerc] I came to Vegas before
with, uh, my best friends.
I cannot really remember anything from it.
But it was, uh, a very fun trip.
[photographer] Carlos.
Vegas is the race, I think, Formula 1
has been looking forward the most
over the last couple of years.
-Grazie. Thank you, guys.
-[man] Good luck.
[upbeat music plays]
[Horner] Hello?
Is... Is that, uh, Daniel?
It's Christian here.
[Ricciardo] We are rolling in now,
so I'll see you shortly.
[Horner] Are you finally
leading a fucking race?
-[Ricciardo] That's a bit harsh, but yes.
-[Horner chuckles]
It's more about having
a bit of fun, and I'm super excited.
Hey, man.
[laughs]
How are you doing? You okay?
-[Ricciardo] Very well.
-Good.
Vegas.
[chuckles]
-You look sharp.
-You know, it's Vegas time, so...
[commentator 2] Formula 1
has finally arrived in Las Vegas.
This is the first ever
Formula 1 Las Vegas Grand Prix
opening ceremony.
[Norris] Yuki, why are you so sad, mate?
You look so really depressed.
[Yuki] I was here early.
[woman] Way too early.
[Norris] I'll join you.
[Verstappen] How's it going?
How are you, mate?
[Norris] I didn't do any practice.
-[Gasly] Why not?
-[Norris] It was my birthday.
I got drunk in a casino.
What else do you expect?
Charles played roulette
and got his number twice.
He, like, tripled it and then lost it.
[man] Can I get all the drivers up?
So we're gonna be doing a 28-minute show.
And then at the end, we reveal
all of you guys coming up the lifts,
super rock-star style.
If you wanna just feel like a rock star,
that would be amazing.
Just, you know, you could play
to the grandstand side.
What are we playing?
-[man] Uh, playing as in acting to it.
-Ah, right.
[man] Acting like a rock star.
[dramatic music plays]
Can we hide?
[man] You could. You can.
I don't know how, but... [laughs]
-Yeah. I appreciate y'all.
-[Russell] We're pumped.
-[man] Yeah, you're pumped.
-[woman] We are.
[commentator 2] Ladies and gentlemen,
please put your hands together
for your 2023
Las Vegas Grand Prix drivers!
[Buxton] Vegas has brought the sparkle
and the showmanship
with the glitz and the glam
and everything that Sin City holds.
But on track,
there's a huge amount still to play for.
[Hamilton] Ferrari have been really strong
the last couple of races.
They're pushing big time to beat us.
On one side, it's exciting. On the other,
it's definitely nerve-racking.
[Leclerc] Vegas is just incredible.
[commentator 2] Team Ferrari.
But we are aware
that Vegas can be a big opportunity.
[tense music plays]
[Sainz] There's a lot of hype around it.
But I think
the most important thing for us
is to put ourselves in the position
of fighting them.
[music stops]
[suspenseful orchestral music plays]
[exhales]
[producer 1] Sorry, Fred, almost there.
[producer 2] Fred, we need to make you
look the most handsome we can.
[scoffs]
It's too late. Far too late.
[producer 2] Who do you think
the most vain team principal is?
[suspenseful music continues]
This is an old shirt that Hannah...
That is an old shirt
that is too tight on my... belly.
[producer 1] Too much time in the gym.
No, the belly.
[producer 2] Toto's a handsome man.
[suspenseful music continues]
[team member] Good evening,
we'll start with Fred's introduction.
Yeah, a quick one.
This event will be difficult.
And perhaps a strange one
with the track layout.
But I think the most important will be
for us to stay
completely focused on the event
and, uh, not to be focused
on what's happening outside.
[Vasseur in French] We arrived
in Las Vegas 20 points behind Mercedes.
But we know it's the money time
with the races remaining.
[in English] We want to be
in front of Mercedes.
Thank you.
[reporter] After all the hype,
we're finally gonna see some cars
in the first ever practice session
on this circuit.
[Adami] All clear.
[Sainz] Copy.
The practice sessions are so important.
[reporter] Pit exit is open.
Carlos Sainz taking to the track
for the very first time.
[Williams] For the drivers, it's their
first opportunity on that circuit
to learn every nuance
for Qualifying and for the race.
[dramatic music plays]
[Padros] Track clear. Mode race.
[Leclerc] Free practices, they are
all about trying to understand the track
and to achieve the best car setup
and strategy
that will come out on top.
[Patrick] Las Vegas is a track
that none of the drivers have driven.
And what this does
is it levels out the playing field.
[Chan] Mode charge.
Mode charge. And keep the pace up.
[Bottas] Yeah, the grip is...
Grip is pretty shocking here.
[Verstappen] It's really very cool
driving on the Strip.
Is it the best track on Earth?
Yeah, I have very little grip.
No, for sure not.
[Lambiase] Okay, understood.
[Hamilton] Vegas turned out to be
incredibly slippery.
-I don't have that grip.
-[Bono] Okay, copy.
So I do anticipate
it's gonna be a difficult weekend.
Especially with Ferrari.
We've got a lot of work to do.
[Sainz] I'm struggling with traction.
There's a lot of hype around Vegas.
I would like to open a lap
just to confirm my feeling.
[Adami] Okay, understood.
[Sainz] There's obviously a lot
of uncertainties about the racetrack,
but everyone's excited to see how it goes
and see if we can put on a good show.
[thudding]
[Sainz groans]
[groans]
[Sainz] Fucking hell.
What was that?
[groans]
My back.
[commentator 3] Carlos Sainz has stopped.
We got a red flag.
[commentator 4]
That was severe, wasn't it?
[Adami] Are you okay?
[Sainz] Yeah, but fuck's sake.
I hit a drain cover, I think.
[commentator 2] Sainz appears
to have hit a drain cover,
and that could be some serious damage.
[Sainz] The floor is gonna be destroyed.
[tense music plays]
[music fades]
This is a... a nightmare scenario
for... for Carlos and Ferrari.
[commentator 2] The team
are now watching that back in the garage.
Man, that was a big hit.
[Buxton] That is not
a small amount of damage.
And where it's hit the car,
Ferrari now have to build
a brand-new car from scratch.
But you have a certain allocation
of engines, gear boxes
that you can use throughout the season.
And they've used
more than their season's allocation.
There is no waiver.
There is no route around it.
Ferrari now face a ten-place grid penalty
for the race.
[Williams] It's not an easy situation
to be in.
And if you're Ferrari
and you're competing
against your arch rival, Mercedes,
for P2 in the championship,
it is the last thing that you want.
[woman] You're gonna be late
for the press conference. You need to go.
[man 1] Have you seen this video of Sainz?
Watch. Hang on. It replays in a second.
Watch up there.
It goes off like a bomb.
[reporter] It's been a very unfortunate
start to the on-track proceedings.
And, Fred, perhaps
we could start with you.
Have you had a chance
to look at the car yet?
The situation is that, uh,
we damaged completely the monocoque,
the engine, the battery.
And, uh,
I think it's just unacceptable.
Well, let's look bigger picture because...
But this one is a good one.
I don't need to have
a bigger picture than this one.
[reporter] Okay.
But, Fred, I did just want to ask you
about this event,
if we can just talk about
the Las Vegas Grand Prix.
Yeah, guys, but I... [chuckles]
I'm not sure
that is the topic for me today. Not, uh...
We had a very tough FP1.
This will cost us a fortune.
With a fucked-up decision for Carlos.
But we have to change the chassis,
half of the car,
or two-thirds of the car.
Okay, the show is the show,
and everything is going well, but, uh,
I think it's just unacceptable
from the F1 today.
-[reporter] Okay, well, this is the last...
-Fred is upset.
I am, Toto,
but you would be upset in my situation.
Fred, let's look at 2023 as a whole, okay?
Your first year
as team principal of Ferrari.
You're putting yourself into more trouble.
-No, but...
-I've known him for 20 years. He has...
[Toto laughs]
-[reporter] Fred, can we just...
-Can I leave now or...
-[reporter] Can we reflect on the year?
-Ask a question to Toto about something.
[reporter] All right. Well, look,
we'll come back to you, Fred.
-We'll come back to you.
-Sure.
[rock music plays]
[commentator 5] It's fast
approaching midnight here in Las Vegas,
and it's all about Qualifying.
Tonight, you can put
your money on red for Ferrari,
black, maybe, for Mercedes.
Who can hit the jackpot of pole?
Carlos Sainz,
he's had a ten-place grid penalty.
Not his fault, but the stewards couldn't
do anything about the regulations.
[commentator 6] It does seem hugely unfair
on Ferrari and Sainz.
[Sainz] We are a bit surprised
with the bad luck we had with the drain.
We know it has made overtaking Mercedes
for P2 this weekend tough.
But I'm focused.
[commentator 1] The green light at the end
of the pit lane, 20 cars embark
on to the racetrack.
[exciting music plays]
[Padros] Mode push, mode push.
[Leclerc] Copy.
Unfortunately,
we've been very unlucky.
It's a moment where, I think, as a team,
we need to work as hard as possible
in order to recover.
[exciting music continues]
[music fades]
[Padros] And at the moment, you are P1.
[commentator 5] Charles Leclerc
sets the benchmark for the rest to chase.
[commentator 6] A very quick lap.
[Bono] And circuit's all clear.
Good to go.
[exciting music plays]
[Hamilton] Ferrari's always gonna be
up there. This makes it difficult for us.
But it is what it is.
You just have to keep your head down
and just keep... keep rolling.
[exciting music continues]
[music fades]
[Bono] P11.
[Hamilton] Couldn't go faster, mate.
[commentator 1] A massive
disappointment for Mercedes.
They were expecting better than that.
[dramatic music plays]
[commentator 5] Here comes the Ferrari
of Carlos Sainz.
[Adami] Push, yep. Push.
[dramatic music continues]
[commentator 6] It's so close
between him and Leclerc at the moment.
[music fades]
-[Adami] Currently, you are P2.
-[Sainz] All good.
[commentator 5] Out comes
the Mercedes of George Russell.
[Russell] Where's Lewis?
[Dudley] He's P11.
[dramatic music plays]
[Russell] Ferrari are looking
really strong,
but you always believe you're gonna
go out there and achieve a big result.
[Dudley] You're on target,
so push your way through.
[commentator 2] Can Russell
put the Mercedes in front of the Ferraris?
[music fades]
[Dudley] That's, um... Yeah, P4.
[Russell] Are Ferrari 1 and 2?
[Padros] And P1.
[triumphant music plays]
[Leclerc] P1, you said?
[Padros] Yes, P1. Good job.
[Leclerc exhales]
Good job, guys.
[commentator 2] A great battle
between the scarlet Ferraris,
but it's Charles Leclerc's day.
He's edged his teammate.
[Adami] And P2.
[Sainz] Congrats to everyone
and thank you for yesterday.
[commentator 2] A Ferrari one-two,
but that ten-place grid penalty
for Carlos Sainz
means he starts tomorrow's race in P12.
That was good.
Fucking penalty.
[scoffs]
[commentator 5] Here we go.
The penultimate round of the season.
And it looks absolutely epic
here in Vegas.
F1, Vegas, baby!
It don't get better than this.
There's so many of y'all motherfuckers.
[laughter]
-[Horner] Hey! How are you, man?
-[Shaquille O'Neal] I like your car.
-[Horner] Do you wanna drive?
-[Shaquille] No. No!
[Wolff] It's mega, no?
Toto, I just want to thank you for saying
all the nice things about Las Vegas.
-Yeah, it was necessary.
-[woman] It was very kind of you.
Too many naysayers.
All right, well, showtime.
[commentator 1] Second place
in the Constructors up for grabs.
Mercedes in second, Ferrari in third.
[commentator 2] Carlos Sainz,
with one of the more unfair penalties
you will ever see in Formula 1,
from the front row down to 12th.
He will be aiming
to fight his way through the pack
and finish ahead of the Mercedes
of Hamilton, who starts tenth.
And George Russell starts P3.
[commentator 1] And then
it's Max Verstappen on the front row.
And it's Charles Leclerc on pole.
Can he convert that
into a race victory tonight?
[tense music plays]
[Dudley] Ninety seconds. Fire up.
[Adami] Focus on the lights.
[commentator 5] And it's lights out
and away we go.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 5] Charles Leclerc gets away
well, but Verstappen's coming at him.
[Leclerc] He pushed me wide.
[commentator 2] Chaos in the middle
of the pack!
Carlos Sainz facing the wrong way.
-[Adami] Are you okay with the car?
-[Sainz] I think so.
[commentator 1] Terrible start
for Ferrari.
Sainz at the back,
Charles Leclerc in second,
and Max Verstappen, leads.
Ferrari have got a mountain to climb.
[commentator 6] The two Aston Martins
hunted down by Sainz's Ferrari.
[Adami] The race is still on for us.
DRS enabled. Fernando, 0.6 in front.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 5] Alonso's under pressure
from Carlos Sainz,
who goes down the inside.
[tense music continues]
[Adami] Good job, Carlos.
[Sainz] Right now, it's time
to forget about mistakes
and just focus with our heads down.
[tense music continues]
[music stops]
[commentator 2] A good recovery drive,
this from Sainz.
He's now closing in
on the Mercedes of Hamilton.
-[Hamilton] Position?
-[Bono] Currently P9.
There's Piastri ahead.
[Hamilton] Oh shit! I got a puncture.
Fuck. Oh damn.
[Bono] Box, box. Box, box.
[tense music plays]
[Adami] Hamilton with a puncture in front.
Hamilton with a puncture in front.
[Sainz] Copy.
[tense music continues]
[commentator 5] Hamilton
is really struggling here.
[music stops]
[commentator 5] That is absolute disaster
this evening for Mercedes.
[commentator 1]
Ferrari will be pretty happy.
Both their drivers
ahead of Lewis Hamilton.
[commentator 2] This is the battle
for the lead at the Las Vegas Grand Prix.
[dramatic music plays]
[Verstappen] The tires
are really fucked, mate.
[Lambiase] Confirm. Box.
[dramatic music continues]
[commentator 1] Charles Leclerc
is closing in on Max Verstappen.
Leclerc's gonna pull the move.
[commentator 2] Charles Leclerc takes
the lead of the Las Vegas Grand Prix!
[Padros] You are doing a good job.
[commentator 5] And there he goes.
Very quick stop indeed.
[dramatic music continues]
[Lambiase] So that's Russell ahead, Max.
[Dudley] You've got
Verstappen's car behind, 1.5.
[dramatic music continues]
[Dudley] You've got
Verstappen now behind at 0.5.
[Russell] Copy.
[dramatic music continues]
[commentator 2] Max Verstappen
fancies a chance here!
There's contact!
Verstappen into the side of Russell.
[Russell] Fuck! Wing cover damaged.
[Dudley] Box, box. Box, box.
Position?
[Adami] P7, P7.
[commentator 1] Carlos Sainz
having an incredible race.
He's now ahead of both of the Mercedes.
[Adami] And Gasly in front
is struggling quite a lot.
Should be doable.
[Sainz] Copy.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 1]
Leclerc still leads this race,
but he has the two Red Bulls
right behind him.
[tense music continues]
[Verstappen] Let's work together here.
We can get him.
[Padros] Verstappen behind with DRS.
Behind him, also Pérez with DRS.
[Leclerc] They've got new tires.
It's going to be difficult.
[Padros] Yeah, copy.
But you are doing a good job, okay.
Continue like this.
[Lambiase] 0.4.
[tense music continues]
[commentator 2] We go down the Strip.
Max Verstappen takes the place back.
Look at how brave Charles is.
Verstappen takes the lead back once again.
[Padros] Pérez behind, 0.6.
[Bird] He's starting to drop back to you.
[Leclerc] Oh no.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 2]
Having led this Grand Prix,
Leclerc has been passed by both Red Bulls
and he finds himself in third.
[Padros] And last lap.
And Pérez in front.
Stay as close as possible.
[Leclerc] Yes, yes.
[commentator 5] Here we go,
down the straight.
1.2 miles for Charles Leclerc
to try and get past Sergio Pérez.
-[Pérez] What's the gap behind?
-[Bird] Leclerc, 0.9, has DRS.
[tense music plays]
[Padros] Try to maximize full throttle.
[Leclerc] Come on.
[Bird] 0.7.
[music stops]
[cheering]
[Pérez] Ah, fuck.
[commentator 2]
But Checo's still fighting!
It's Charles Leclerc
who takes second place.
[cheering]
[Leclerc] I'm pleased with second place.
I'm pleased with fucking second place.
You did a fantastic job.
Where are the Mercedes?
[Padros] So P7, Hamilton.
P8, Russell.
And, uh, Carlos?
[Padros] Sainz, P6.
Ah, good, good, good.
-[Vasseur] Good job, Carlos.
-Thank you, Fred.
Is that it?
[Bono] That's it, mate. P7.
That's been
a tough day at the office, mate.
[Dudley] P8.
[groans]
[Russell] Honestly,
sums up the season, this race.
[cheering]
[in French] I think, personally,
Carlos had a great performance.
Now we're four points behind Mercedes.
We know what we have to do in Abu Dhabi.
[Hamilton in English] We lost
a lot of points today to Ferrari, um,
which is really unfortunate.
But we'll go to the last race,
we'll fight and give it everything we got.
[Wolff] We have a problem.
Clearly, we've underperformed.
Certainly not what, uh, what we aimed for.
So this is, let's say,
a dynamic situation.
Fighting for P2
is a formidable challenge against Fred.
So obviously, the pressure, um, is big.
We just gotta beat the Ferraris.
[commentator 1]
There are now just four points
between Mercedes and Ferrari
for that second place.
[horns honk]
-[Norris] The final one.
-[Piastri] Final one.
[Norris] And then we're going home.
Go and see my parents.
[man] You've got a job
to do first, though.
Oh yeah, I've got a race.
Yeah, true.
[man] I thought there'd be
some fighting talk.
-[Piastri] Oh.
-No, we don't do that.
No.
-We're not that type of team, you know?
-We do our talking on the track.
Bang on, Oscar.
He may be young...
[Piastri chuckles]
...but he's not dumb.
[Piastri laughs]
[commentator 1]
The season finale has arrived.
After a relentless journey
around the world,
we have reached
the concluding chapter of 2023.
[in German] Morning.
-[woman in English] How are you feeling?
-[Horner] Yeah.
Jet-lagged. Fucked.
Other than that, all good.
-[in French] The last one.
-[man] Yes.
[laughter]
[in English] The Formula 1 season
is an intense ten-month schedule.
It's relentless.
[Ricciardo] Hey, guys.
[Buxton] Thousands of laps completed.
And there's still plenty to fight for
in this last race of the season.
And it's not just the fight for second
in the Constructors Championship
that's at stake.
[tense music plays]
[Buxton] There's also this intense battle
between McLaren and Aston Martin
for fourth place.
[reporter] Morning.
Morning.
[Zak Brown] I wish
we weren't racing Fernando
'cause he's capable of pulling off
some miraculous... results.
Fourth will be amazing
given where we started.
I think if it's fifth,
we're all gonna be pissed off,
especially 'cause the last couple races,
we've clearly been quicker,
but we've had some problems.
-[man] You heard from Lawrence?
-[Brown] I've had a text from Lawrence.
I wouldn't say that was friendly... banter.
I would say it's probably not made
for PG TV either.
[man] Yeah? What did he say?
Uh, why don't you ask him?
Big weekend here in Abu Dhabi.
We have an 11-point lead over Aston Martin
for fourth in the championship.
It's hotter today, no?
I would've never thought
we would have been here.
You know, they started the season
second-quickest team,
and we started the season
probably the ninth quickest.
-It's gone very quick.
-It has gone very quickly.
I believe we have the faster car,
we have the better driver lineup.
But now we need to close the deal.
[producer] Any messages for Lawrence?
Game on.
Good to see you.
[Lawrence Stroll] We definitely hit a lull
in the middle of the season.
Uh, we made some mistakes,
and we were just too slow.
I think it made everybody
a little bit hungrier
to finish stronger in the last race
than our competitors.
How are you?
P2 or P3?
P3.
Where are you starting, seventh?
If I push on his rear, you crash into him.
Good for you. Good for you.
[Alonso] I think the team really deserves
this year to finish fourth.
And I feel motivated.
McLaren is doing
an outstanding job this year.
Ten-pin bowling.
[Alonso] So it's gonna be a tight fight.
[Norris] Everyone thought
they'd be title challengers.
But they started strong.
And we went up.
They went down.
Who knows?
What?
I send you bad luck.
[laughter]
-Bad luck!
-[laughter]
[Norris] Our final job
is to finish ahead of them.
There is more pressure
going up against Fernando Alonso.
But if there's one team
we really want to beat, it's them.
This is it.
It all comes down to one last round.
But it's pretty tight between all of us.
[Buxton] Further back down the paddock,
every team's objectives
are to finish ahead of their rivals.
I think we have a faster race car
than we expected here.
I'm looking forward to it.
See you later on.
[tense music plays]
[Steiner] Going into Abu Dhabi,
the car will not be a lot different.
So we need some help from something
to get some points.
Otherwise, we finish last.
But you always go out there, do your best,
and try to make the miracle happen.
[commentator 1]
Welcome to the season finale,
the Abu Dhabi Grand Prix,
where the story remains incomplete
for this season in so many areas.
Okay, here we go.
Beautiful.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
How do you find it at Alpine?
Somehow, the team has so much more
potential than what we're showing.
You know, like...
[Gasly] Everyone was disappointed
with the performance
we showed since the start of the year.
But there've been quite a few changes.
Well, being on the podium in Zandvoort
was, uh... was amazing.
Now, with Esteban,
the best it's been since... since ten years.
It's a good place to... to be in.
[Wolff] Still not in a good place,
the car.
-I'll see what I can do with it.
-I'm sure you can do something with it.
I don't wanna see this car again
after today.
[Wolff] It's the last one. Last one.
Let's do the best
out of the last 90 minutes of the season.
Yep. I'll give it everything.
[Wolff] We're coming to the last race
with Ferrari four points behind.
George and Lewis wanna give it
all they have
to finish second
in the Constructor Championship.
-Ready for it?
-[man] Yeah. You?
Yeah, I'm excited.
Gonna be a good one.
So it's about
who can do the better job, uh, here,
who can score more points.
[commentator 1] If Mercedes can get
one car on that podium today,
that will give them the best chance
to secure second place
in the championship.
Charles Leclerc starts second on the grid,
but his teammate, Carlos Sainz,
is way back in 16th.
George Russell starting fourth,
while Lewis Hamilton's down in 11th.
-Good luck today.
-Thank you. You too.
All right, see you soon.
-[Cronin] Radio check, Fernando.
-[Alonso] Loud and clear.
[commentator 2]
Aston Martin have it all to do
in the fight to beat McLaren to fourth.
Fernando Alonso starts seventh,
and his teammate, Lance Stroll,
is down in 13th.
For the McLarens,
Lando Norris starts fifth.
Oscar Piastri up ahead, P3.
[Stallard] Thirty seconds.
-Good luck.
-Good luck. Grazie.
[Hamilton] This is the time
where we really need to push even harder.
[tense music plays]
[Leclerc] We know that it is going to be
a huge challenge.
We have to do
absolutely everything perfect.
[Dudley] Last car on the grid.
[Russell] The fight between us and Ferrari
is within touching distance.
It's gonna be a tight battle.
[tense music builds]
[Russell] I'm gonna have to drive
the race of my life.
[deep breathing]
[commentator 1] And the Abu Dhabi
Grand Prix is go!
[commentator 5] Norris and Russell
going wheel to wheel.
[exciting music plays]
[Russell] Fuck.
[tense music plays]
-[Russell] What position are we?
-[Dudley] Currently P5.
[tense music continues]
-Position?
-[Bono] Currently P9.
-DRS has been enabled.
-Okay.
[commentator 1] Both the Mercedes
desperately chasing down a podium finish.
[tires screech]
[Hamilton] I've just damaged
my front wing.
He locked up ahead of me.
[tense music plays]
[commentator 2] Leclerc in second,
keeping Ferrari's hopes alive.
[Padros] Gap to Verstappen in front, 1.5.
You are doing a good job,
so continue like this.
[Dudley] Gap ahead to Piastri, 0.4.
[Stallard] Suggest more speed.
Keep protecting.
[Dudley] You have DRS.
[tense music plays]
[Dudley] Good job.
[commentator 1] Fourth for Russell, who's
carrying the hopes of that team right now.
[Dudley] Nice job, mate.
So 2.4 ahead to Norris.
[commentator 1] At this moment in time,
Mercedes need George Russell
to get himself onto a podium.
[tense music continues]
[dramatic music plays]
-[Cronin] Piastri ahead.
-Copy.
[dramatic music continues]
[Stallard] Alonso, 0.6.
-[Cronin] Push everything now.
-Okay.
[Stallard] Use the pace, Oscar.
Use the pace.
Defending well.
This is good, Oscar.
[commentator 2] If it stays this way,
McLaren take fourth place
in the Constructors over Aston Martin.
[Dudley] This is really good stuff, mate.
Let's close that gap.
[Russell] I'm pushing.
[commentator 1] Lando Norris in third,
being chased by George Russell.
[Norris] Gap?
[Joseph] 0.6 behind.
We are managing an issue.
Okay, Lando, we are box this lap.
Box this lap.
[Norris] Confirm.
[Dudley] Norris just pitted.
Box, box. Box, box.
[Joseph] Could be
close to Russell at exit.
[commentator 4] Oh no, it's a slow stop!
[commentator 2] George Russell up to third
and a podium spot.
Enough to secure second
in the Constructors Championship.
[dramatic music plays]
[Dudley] Four laps remaining.
Car behind now, Pérez, 4.4.
Just keep driving
the fastest laps you can.
He must not finish in front of us.
[commentator 1] Russell
desperately clinging to third,
but Pérez fast approaching
in the Red Bull.
Tell me the gap between Checo and Russell.
[Padros] Gap, 2.7.
[dramatic music continues]
[Bird] Gap to Russell, 2.4.
Come on, Checo.
[commentator 1] Pérez is on the attack.
Sergio Pérez attacking George Russell.
Can he hold on to secure second?
[dramatic music continues]
[Bird] Russell, 1.4.
[Padros] Last lap, last lap.
Last lap?
[commentator 2]Max Verstappen
wins the Abu Dhabi Grand Prix.
Charles Leclerc comes home second.
[Padros] Mode to slow, please.
Mode to slow.
I don't care about mode slow.
Where are we in the Constructors?
[tense music plays]
[Dudley] Perez, gap 1.1.
[tense music builds]
[music stops]
-[Wolff] That's P2 in the championship.
-[Russell] Oh my goodness.
[commentator 5] Mercedes take second place
in the championship by three points.
For fuck's sake!
[triumphant music plays]
[Leclerc] Agh! I wanted
that second place so bad.
Fuck!
[Bono] P9.
[Hamilton] Thank you guys so much.
You really deserved second place.
[Wolff] I know it was
a super difficult race with that car.
[Joseph] That's P4
in the championship as well,
which, as you know,
means a lot to the team.
Tough season. Even in a tough season,
we still managed
to get three top threes,
so I'm sure next year, we'll see
each other on the podium more often.
Well done, Alex. Your hard work this year
is what brought us
seventh in the Constructors Championship.
It's a proud moment.
Thanks, James.
This is just the start
of really good things.
[Slade] Kev, usual story.
I'm afraid we were P20.
[Magnussen] Thanks
for all the effort this year.
It's been a tough old one.
[commentator 1] It's a bottom-of-the-table
finish for Guenther Steiner and Haas.
The dominant Dutchman,
winning for the 19th time this season,
and Red Bull end the season
beaten just once in the grand prix format.
In the battle for P2, Mercedes held on.
Can I do some burnouts, okay?
[Padros] No burnouts, please.
No burnouts to the grid.
[Leclerc groans]
Not even this, for fuck's sake.
[Dudley] I'll see you up there
on that podium. It's been a while.
[Russell] Oh yeah.
We're on a path back to the top.
Come on, guys.
[upbeat music plays]
[team member] Fucking hell,
give me a hug. That is fantastic.
[upbeat music continues]
George, you made 2,500 people happy.
[Russell] I thought you were gonna tell me
that was my bonus, 2,500.
[Wolff] P2 is an... is an important one,
but at the same time,
this sport is all about... about winning.
And that's the mentality in the team.
Next season,
we start with a completely new car.
Hopefully back to success.
[Leclerc yells]
Fuck!
I think that in those moments,
as much as you are disappointed
by not achieving your targets...
as a team, we also need to be happy
of what we have achieved.
I also believe we finished
that season on a high
with good momentum for next year.
[cheering]
[Vasseur in French] For me,
the DNA of a race team
is to always improve and get better.
It's reflected
in the work we do every day,
our points, our number of wins,
our ranking in the tournament.
Although that depends on the others too.
My main goal is that the team works
even better next year than this year.
Well done, guys.
What an incredible season.
Have a good break,
and we'll come back stronger next year.
[Lawrence Stroll] We haven't even begun.
There's a tremendous amount more to go.
-[Vowles] Are you all right?
-I'm okay. You?
[Vowles] Just really well done.
Very impressive
what you've done this year.
Anything we can help, we're there.
[Vowles] I'll let you know.
Just keep doing what you're doing.
That's what we'll try to do.
[Vowles] Fair enough.
[Lawrence Stroll] We made some mistakes,
but as far as next year goes,
stay tuned because you'll see us
take some major steps
and, I believe,
fighting for world championships.
-[Brown] Well done, guys.
-Great job.
[Brown] Strong season.
[Brown] Next year, I think
we can be fighting at the top.
Our intention is to keep going,
keep making the car faster.
So I see no reason why both our drivers
can't be challenging for wins next year.
[music intensifies]
[commentator 1] Max Verstappen
wins 19 grand prix in a single season.
[commentator 5] It is another victory.
What a year it has been for him!
We've won 95.4% of the races.
We won all of them bar one.
We've had 30 podiums.
Max is the most successful driver
in a season.
It's been unbelievable,
uh, for a sportsman to hit
that kind of form for that period of time.
It's... It's outstanding.
We'll never see
this kind of winning again,
certainly in, probably, my lifetime
or in any of our lifetimes.
And even if we won 50%
of what we've achieved this year,
that might be good enough
to defend the championships next year.
[cheering]
[triumphant music plays]
[music stops]
[Steiner] Fucking hell.
It's been a long season.
We finished last.
It doesn't feel good, you know?
[somber music plays]
[Steiner] I always said, "We are not here
to be last. We are here to compete."
The buck stops here,
and I have to do the best for the team.
I need to phone Gene up.
Hi, Gene.
Fucking hell.
Fuck, man, this year...
[producer] Thank you, Guenther.
You're such a pleasure to chat with
in this chair.
I mean that genuinely. Thank you.
[Steiner] No problem. You're welcome.
And you know, if I wouldn't like it,
I wouldn't speak.
[laughter]
[somber music plays]
[music fades]